His date gives a thumbs up, mouths SOMEONE Mayer, and rushes inside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS15
SOMEONE's date hugs her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS16
A Castle Rock Entertainment Production.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS17
Behind SOMEONE and her friend a flyer reads Friends with Benefits. Now the web designer rides in an airplane. A flight attendant
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS18
flirtatiously close.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS19
She jerks his seat up and turns away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS20
In a hired car, SOMEONE uses her cell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS21
She changes clothes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS22
As the driver eyes the building, she changes her top.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS23
Now at the airport, she approaches a driver holding a name card.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS24
She takes the card and writes SOMEONE on the back with lipstick. As the web designer walks through a sliding door, an air gust blows the sign from her hands. It lands on a baggage carousel.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS25
She chases after it.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS26
She removes her shoes, climbs up on the conveyer, and runs past suitcases.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS27
SOMEONE notices her handing a man a suitcase.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS28
She trots down to the other end of the carousel, hopping over bags.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS29
She and SOMEONE both reach for her sign.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS30
Now they sit in the car.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS32
He hands her an iced green tea beverage and goes inside. SOMEONE takes a sip, then spits it out. Rinsing her mouth with water, she spits again, nearly hitting a passerby.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS33
As we peer out from the lobby through its glass doors, day becomes night. SOMEONE leaves the building. Seated at a nearby cafe, SOMEONE springs to her feet at his approach.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS34
As he checks his phone, she suddenly puts hers away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS35
He turns away, staring at his cell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS36
She pouts and lifts her brow.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS37
She starts across the street, but SOMEONE remains on the sidewalk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS39
Later they sip drinks at an intimate table.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS40
They share a smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS41
SOMEONE walks by.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS42
He bumps into the table.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS43
He hugs SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS44
Later on a sidewalk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS45
They reach a gyros stand.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS46
Now at a partially open security gate.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS47
SOMEONE rolls underneath.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS48
SOMEONE follows suit. Now SOMEONE leads him up a stairwell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS49
She carefully swings her legs over a security gate at the top and strides onward. SOMEONE opens the gate and steps through. Now SOMEONE leads him through a door. Both clutching their gyros they step out on a high rooftop overlooking Manhattan.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS50
They walk to a corner with a view of the Empire State Building.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS51
Later they eat.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS52
SOMEONE's chewing slows and he averts his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS53
SOMEONE steps away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS54
She sits down.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS55
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie back side-by-side.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS57
They move through a crowd.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS58
SOMEONE halts.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS59
Nearby a man holds up a boom box while another starts break dancing. The crowd parts for them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS60
Two other dancers join the first. All three strike stylized poses and nod their heads in unison. As they move into a Broadway style dance number, young people approach from all over the crowd. The performers slump down.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS61
As they spring up and break into another set of moves, the dozens of young people join them. SOMEONE looks around bewilderedly.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS62
He spots a huge monitor broadcasting the flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS63
She raises her arms and waves them in unison with the dancers.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS64
The dancers lean over and back up, edging close to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS65
They bend over, too. The dancers straighten and point skyward. A forward leaning pose radiates from the back of the flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS66
The boom box holder stands erect among the participants, as onlookers watch delightedly. The dancers straighten and raise their arms skyward, some with jazz hands.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS67
They clap along as they converse.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS68
The dance concludes with a flourish.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS69
On a plane, he talks with someone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS70
Now at night, a New York City cab drops SOMEONE off in an urban neighborhood.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS71
He gazes about, full of wonder.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS72
He grabs his bags.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS73
Later he enters a sleek apartment, decorated in grays and browns. SOMEONE drops his bags. He steps past a black granite galley kitchen and descends into a sunken living room. A gift basket of bed sheets includes a note, SOMEONE, welcome to NYC. In case you shit the bed. Excuse the expression. Best, SOMEONE. SOMEONE runs to his bed and vaults hard on the mattress, jamming his shoulder. Now at GQ.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS74
SOMEONE removes the door from its frame.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS75
A fit balding guy greets him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS76
He strokes SOMEONE's cheeks.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS77
He starts off, then backtracks.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS78
SOMEONE peers off, stunned. Later, as he works, SOMEONE enters his office.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS79
He shows her a web video of a woman dunking her breasts in cake batter.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS80
Another shows the Time Square flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS81
The rows of dancers form the GQ logo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS82
SOMEONE takes a look at the inch-thick stack of documents.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS84
Later in a corner diner.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS85
He gets a call from SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS86
They share an amused smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS87
Later SOMEONE opens her door to SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS88
Later they play virtual table tennis. Now SOMEONE and others stick playing cards to their foreheads.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS89
His reads Curious SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS90
Playing Jenga, SOMEONE intentionally topples the block tower. SOMEONE swigs beer, then passes out. SOMEONE graffities his face with marker. At GQ he notices traces of the graffiti. Now as SOMEONE holds up a lipstick sign at the airport, she sees SOMEONE's GQ flash mob ad on a kiosk. She photographs herself with it. At home SOMEONE grins at her email. At a party they view a canvas that features industrial looking stenciling.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS91
SOMEONE passes out. As SOMEONE draws on her face, the marker leaves no apparent lines.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS92
SOMEONE now addresses three executives.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS93
As she dims the lights for a slideshow, glow-in-the-dark graffiti shows on her face, including eyebrows, the word Loser and cat whiskers. SOMEONE rubs her nose. Glowing ink transfers to her hand and she gawks.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS94
Now in a movie, SOMEONE and SOMEONE co-star.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS95
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch together.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS96
In the movie, the leading man runs with flowers.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS97
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE lip sync every word.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS98
SOMEONE drops the flowers and kisses SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS99
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a hansom cab.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS100
They both swig a beer.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS101
In shorts and a tank top SOMEONE bends over to clear some clutter. Her cute butt mesmerizes SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS102
He watches her rear as he is sitting on the couch.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS103
SOMEONE steps away then return.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS104
He puts his hand on the virtual Bible. SOMEONE adds hers, and SOMEONE tops it.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS105
They peer closely at each other.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS107
He cups her bosom.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS108
She walks away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS109
They get undressed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS110
With her back to us, she faces SOMEONE and ditches her bra.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS111
SOMEONE drops his briefs. We view his bare butt, SOMEONE his front.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS112
Now they fall back onto the bed, making out.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS114
He pulls a shaggy teddy bear out from under the sheets.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS115
She grabs his head by the hair, pulls his head to hers and pinches his tongue.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS116
Now SOMEONE shuts her eyes ecstatically.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS117
SOMEONE surfaces from the bed sheets then gives her a smug smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS118
He flops down beside SOMEONE. Now she dives under the sheets.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS119
He makes an Oh-face.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS120
SOMEONE emerges from the
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS121
She kisses him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS122
They flop down beside each other.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS123
Now at the GQ offices, SOMEONE compares to cover mockups, one featuring SOMEONE, the other President Obama.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS124
SOMEONE goes to a waiting area where SOMEONE sits.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS125
They greet each other with a
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS126
Now the two stroll past artists.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS127
Central Park, each avoiding the others' gaze.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS128
SOMEONE gestures for her
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS129
An artist holds up a sketchpad. Now SOMEONE clutches a caricature of him and SOMEONE, as they burst into her apartment, kissing passionately.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS130
They collapse on a chair.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS131
Undressing her he spots a dog tattoo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS132
He shows his own tattoo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS133
A series of images show SOMEONE and SOMEONE having sex on numerous occasions.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS134
Now they watch a Mets game in their underwear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS135
They high-five, slap hands, and bump chests. SOMEONE leaps into SOMEONE's arms. Later they have sex in his bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS136
Now they make out on a couch.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS137
At another point he wears his socks in the shower with her. Now she lies on top of him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS138
They chew gum as they have sex.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS139
Their legs flail awkwardly under the covers as he rolls on top of her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS140
In her bed, SOMEONE lies with her back to SOMEONE as their hips ungulate.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS141
SOMEONE totters naked to the bathroom with one hand cupped over his crotch. He leaves the door open as he steps out of view. In bed, SOMEONE puffs out a breath, then frowns.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS142
She shrugs and taps her abdomen. Looking into the bathroom, she finds SOMEONE sitting on the toilet.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS143
She starts to lie down.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS144
She sits up again.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS145
The doorway shows one of SOMEONE's legs jerking upward.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS146
He leans over awkwardly, bracing a hand on the bathtub.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS147
He finishes and returns to the bedroom.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS148
He dashes bare ass back into the bathroom. Now he stretches his legs.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS149
A naked SOMEONE joins him in bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS150
She grins and they start to have sex. An older woman saunters in.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS151
She hugs SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS152
She eyes SOMEONE's crotch.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS153
SOMEONE leaves the room.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS154
He carries her shoes past the
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS155
Now SOMEONE plays basketball.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS156
He passes the ball high and SOMEONE jams it into the hoop for a slam-dunk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS157
Later he dribbles and passes to SOMEONE who shoots and scores.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS158
Later they sit at a SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS159
SOMEONE leaps over a railing, separating the peer from the water. SOMEONE dashes over and finds him in a motor boat.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS160
SOMEONE drily lowers his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS161
Grinning SOMEONE puts on sunglasses then speeds of across the water. Now in her living room, SOMEONE sits on the floor in front of her mother, who arranges her hair into a chaotic mass of thick braids as they drink wine.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS162
She joins SOMEONE on the sofa.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS163
Her mother hugs her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS164
SOMEONE eyes her hair in a mirror.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS165
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE remove their jewelry as they lie in his bed in their underwear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS166
Her gaze grows pensive as her
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS167
some friend leans over her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS168
They pick through clothes, strewn about the room.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS169
Now in Central Park they carry sandwiches
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS170
Bethesda fountain.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS171
He hands SOMEONE his sandwich. She looks on as he approaches the beauty.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS172
SOMEONE rolls her eyes and looks away. SOMEONE shakes the beauty's hand.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS173
SOMEONE smiles and spreads her arms as he rejoins her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS174
He knocks the sandwich out of her hand. Later.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS175
She heads over.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS176
She pauses to shoot SOMEONE a glare before reaching the stranger.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS177
He waves cordially at her friend.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS178
SOMEONE looks around then waves back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS179
She rejoins her friend.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS180
They high-five.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS182
On her date. He mimes surgery.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS183
He pretends to peek under the patient's sheet. A waitress brings the check.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS184
SOMEONE covers his eyes with her hands, then removes them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS186
SOMEONE lays a sympathetic hand on SOMEONE's.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS187
Now a lunch date.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS188
She gets a text from SOMEONE. It reads, How's it going with Stares at Trees? @ GQ.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS189
SOMEONE gets a photo message showing SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS190
Now SOMEONE makes out with SOMEONE on her couch. She falls back and smiles at him, meaningfully.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS191
He moves in for another kiss. SOMEONE lies back and he leans over her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS192
She switches off a lamp.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS194
A woman snarls amorously in his ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS195
In short shorts she straddles his leg.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS196
As SOMEONE picks up his cell phone, his date lifts his arm, smells his armpit and licks his tricep. SOMEONE puts the phone to his ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS197
She grins, licks her fingertip, and strokes his ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS198
The woman plants kisses down his lifted arms toward his armpit. Moving his sleeve aside she sniffs deeply.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS199
She exhales in SOMEONE's face. He raises a finger, gesturing for her to pause. She demurely backs off.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS200
The woman runs her fingers through his hair as he ends the call.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS201
She takes SOMEONE's hands and pounds them against her chest.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS202
Now sunlight shines on SOMEONE's hair as she sleeps, spooning with SOMEONE on her sofa. She wakes and gets up groggily. Clad in a T-shirt and panties, she digs behind a sofa cushion, pulls out her cellphone. The display shows SOMEONE's photo and she
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS203
She finds SOMEONE conked out on her bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS204
SOMEONE pulls on cut-off jeans shorts.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS205
With a bra in one hand, she open a door and glances at him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS207
As she shuts the door he stirs and stretches.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS208
Now SOMEONE arrives on the sidewalk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS209
SOMEONE buys coffees.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS210
SOMEONE spies SOMEONE on the move, buttoning his shirt.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS211
She jogs over with the coffees.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS212
She drops his coffee in a trash bin, then marches off drinking her own. SOMEONE stares after her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS213
He goes. Later she visits SOMEONE as he packs for his trip.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS214
SOMEONE presents a large graphic art canvas, featuring a rider on a horse. In one corner stenciled letters follow the @ symbol with ftail.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS215
SOMEONE glares, then paddles her feet on the bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS216
He grabs her ankles. Later SOMEONE arrives home with the painting.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS217
She sets it down and crosses her home.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS218
Heading back through the kitchen she spots a hand scrawled note posted on the fridge. It reads, SOMEONE, sorry, back to Cleveland with Lombard Victor, xoxo, love mom. SOMEONE digs her cellphone from her bag and photographs the note. On his way to a cab, SOMEONE receives the photo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS219
Now beyond Griffith Observatory's Hilltop, downtown L.A. spans the horizon. An aerial view glides over rows of houses, boats in a marina, and a freeway interchange. SOMEONE occupies a window seat on a plane, SOMEONE's on the aisle.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS220
Two young girls in front of them look at SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS221
They turn away. Now we float over Hollywood, then track a car on a meandering frontage road boarded by luxury homes. We arrive at an upscale Oceanside neighborhood.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS222
SOMEONE gets their bags.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS223
They enter a friendly stylish home where open double doors reveal a beachfront patio.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS224
They go out to the patio.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS225
He hugs a boy in a tuxedo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS226
SOMEONE produces a flame from his fingertips.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS227
His sleeve bursts into flames. SOMEONE and SOMEONE remove his jacket.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS228
A tall blond woman arrives.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS229
SOMEONE high-fives them and goes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS230
She lifts him in a hug.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS232
by the ocean, SOMEONE kisses her father's cheek.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS233
As his father goes inside in his shirt and skivvies, SOMEONE shoots a look at SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS234
SOMEONE escorts SOMEONE down to the beach and SOMEONE goes inside. Later the two friends throw stones at the curling waves, then trot off over the sand. At night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on the patio, looking through a photo album. A fire burns in a nearby sandpit.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS236
SOMEONE goes inside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS237
Later, SOMEONE checks on SOMEONE who reads in bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS238
He unties his bathrobe.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS239
He peels it back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS241
Everyday math for dummies. Now the friends drink wine and dance around the room. Later SOMEONE kneels on the bed and swigs from the bottle. Later still, as he snoozes, she dips his hand in a glass of wine, then hides. He wakes and rushes out, holding his crotch. As he returns she pops up.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS242
Now they lounge in bed, barefoot.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS244
She catches SOMEONE smiling fondly at her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS245
He shyly zips his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS246
SOMEONE gives a wry, knowing smirk, and sets his wine aside. Facing SOMEONE again, he finds her staring longingly at him. Holding his gaze, she leans in, lays a hand on his chest and plants a tender kiss on his lips. SOMEONE kisses her back then gives a
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS247
Her lips coyly brush his.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS248
Cradling his head in her hand, she draws his mouth to hers again. SOMEONE's hand slides down his chest.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS249
SOMEONE slips her hand beneath his robe. She pushes it open, caressing his chest and looks up at him coyly.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS250
They lock gazes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS251
Playful smiles fade.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS252
SOMEONE leans close, bringing her lips to him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS253
SOMEONE's hand brushes under her hair and his gentle kisses grow more impassioned.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS254
Later he lies on top of her as their mouths meet in a series of light caresses.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS255
With SOMEONE between her legs SOMEONE brings one leg toward her chest.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS256
Now he rests a hand on her heaving chest as he plants kisses along her thigh.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS257
Later they lie beneath the sheets as they kiss with mounting intensity. As SOMEONE lies on his back, SOMEONE plants a row of kisses down his abdomen. His hand caresses her back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS258
Now the two gaze into each other’s eyes emotionally as their lips brush. Later SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE, regarding him with a tender smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS259
He draws her into a kiss and their interlocked hands drift off the mattress.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS260
Later, SOMEONE's leg pokes out from under a sheet.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS261
SOMEONE's arm lies draped across his stomach, her hand to his, as she sleeps with her
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS262
SOMEONE slumbers.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS263
In the hall, SOMEONE groggily walks into the Saw a Woman in half box.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS264
SOMEONE wakes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS265
As his sister limps down the hall, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, who slumbers on.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS266
He gingerly removes her hand and sits up.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS267
He slips out of bed without waking her and pulls his hand.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS268
SOMEONE glimpses SOMEONE sneaking out of SOMEONE's room in his robe.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS270
In the morning, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and their dad have breakfast on the patio right in front of ocean.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS271
Mr. SOMEONE lets SOMEONE take his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS272
SOMEONE's sleeve dispenses coffee.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS273
SOMEONE bows, then leaves. Smiling SOMEONE wipes the corner of SOMEONE's mouth. SOMEONE and Mr. SOMEONE just
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS274
He aloofly sips his coffee. SOMEONE's smile fades.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS275
Now on jet skis.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS276
The two riders cruise by floating kelp. Two dolphins swim near.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS277
At night, they all dine by a marina.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS278
He angrily pushes away from the table and stands, then trips and falls.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS279
A stranger tries to help. SOMEONE intervenes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS280
SOMEONE keeps his hands off and looks helplessly to SOMEONE. Their dad walks away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS281
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a parting caress then hurries after her dad. SOMEONE uneasily notices diners staring.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS282
SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS284
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hike a city overlook.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS285
The Hollywood sign stands tall downhill of them behind a fence. SOMEONE climbs the fence.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS286
He gives the cameras a thumbs up.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS287
An airborne view orbits the huge white letters. SOMEONE and SOMEONE dangle their legs from the second O.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS288
A helicopter rises in front of them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS289
SOMEONE stares at the chopper.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS290
Later a newscast shows SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS291
They fight for the remote.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS292
Now SOMEONE lies in a long box.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS293
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE enter. SOMEONE ducks completely inside the box.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS294
SOMEONE stares.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS295
SOMEONE steps out toward the beach. SOMEONE slouches then follows.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS296
Left alone, SOMEONE lifts away a top panel of the box and climbs out. She replaces the cover, glances outside and jogs out of the room in the opposite direction.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS297
Nighttime. SOMEONE and his family occupy four of the five chairs around the table.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS298
SOMEONE enters the room.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS299
SOMEONE steps over to SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS300
She leaves the house. SOMEONE gawks at his family and shrugs.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS301
He shakes his head and hustles after her. SOMEONE glances tentatively at their dad.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS302
SOMEONE returns to the dining nook.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS303
He retakes his seat at the untouched
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS304
spread of wine, salad, pasta, and bread. SOMEONE takes a resigned breath.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS305
SOMEONE smiles.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS306
His smile fades and his eyes grows wide.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS307
In New York City, morning sunlight washes across the horizon of buildings. In an airport concourse, SOMEONE walks sadly within the flow of travelers. Later she enters her apartment.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS308
She checks her cellphone. A text from SOMEONE reads, Get home okay? She exits the screen and puts down the phone. Now at GQ SOMEONE works at his desk. SOMEONE arrives in his open doorway.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS309
In another office, SOMEONE reads up on Chelsie Shallenburger on her laptop.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS310
An IM comes in from her mom. So sorry I bailed last weekend, can I please come back?
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS311
SOMEONE sends a cell call from SOMEONE to her voicemail.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS312
Now SOMEONE and her mom play the table
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS313
Her mother sees SOMEONE's face on SOMEONE's cell display.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS314
SOMEONE ignores the call.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS315
SOMEONE gives her daughter an unassuming glance and plods away with her drink.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS316
SOMEONE picks up a game controller.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS317
She talks into it like a microphone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS318
Now on a busy sidewalk, SOMEONE tries calling.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS319
The glass face of his smart phone reflects
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS320
A steeple and high-rise behind him. He turns to look at the actual structures. Now SOMEONE peers out from the rooftop overlooking Manhattan. SOMEONE joins her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS321
As SOMEONE strides away, SOMEONE
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS322
nonplussed in the stark sunlight.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS323
A nearby security guard sees
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS324
At night, SOMEONE cries as she crosses a street.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS325
Now the SOMEONE and SOMEONE movie plays on SOMEONE's TV.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS326
SOMEONE swigs a beer watching their screen kiss.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS329
Now SOMEONE gets a call from the office.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS330
She hangs up and speed dials a number
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS331
She hangs up and strides out of the lady's room. Later at GQ, SOMEONE marches over to SOMEONE's office. He's not there.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS332
She indicates her nose.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS333
At the photo shoot.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS334
Male models pose with sports items held in front of their flesh colored jockstraps.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS335
Topless females join them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS336
He takes SOMEONE aside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS337
As she leaves, SOMEONE frowns to himself. SOMEONE directs a Caucasian male model.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS338
An Asian male model spreads his arms as the other man holds him horizontally.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS339
That night, SOMEONE walks into his kitchen, throws down his bag and turns on the lights. He gets a beer from his windowed refrigerator. As he goes to open it, he notices the note he received with the gift basket of sheets. SOMEONE, welcome to NYC. In case you shit the bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS342
SOMEONE faces his reflection in a window.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS343
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in Central Park together.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS344
Sitting side-by-side on a boulder, they hug.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS345
Now SOMEONE waits at the airport.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS346
Through a wall of windows he watches his dad get pushed up a boarding ramp in a wheel chair. SOMEONE follows and meets them at the gate.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS348
He approaches a hostess at the airport restaurant.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS349
SOMEONE turns away and finds his father gone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS350
Returning to the hostess stand he peers inside the crowded restaurant, then proceeds inside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS351
He finds his father hanging his trousers over a railing, then sitting down at an empty table in his shirt, jacket, and boxers. SOMEONE frowns. As Mr. SOMEONE casually opens a menu, his son trudges over.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS352
SOMEONE takes a heavy breath. Patrons at the nearby tables begin to stare. A man and woman trade a sober look. Standing frozen to the spot, SOMEONE narrows his eyes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS353
He removes his shoes, pulls out a chair at the table, and takes off his own pants.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS354
Later the father and son eat lunch together in their boxers. Mr. SOMEONE notices a young woman using her cellphone outside the restaurant.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS355
She walks away obliviously.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS356
As the other patrons look over at Mr. SOMEONE again, he lowers his befuddled gaze. SOMEONE studies him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS357
Mr. SOMEONE snaps out of his reverie and takes a few deeps breaths.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS358
He gestures to his head.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS359
He sees SOMEONE's somber face.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS360
His son hangs his head. Mr. SOMEONE stares at him with a knitted brow.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS361
Now SOMEONE uses his phone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS362
His dad bumps into SOMEONE and drops his bag.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS363
SOMEONE bumps into him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS364
He indicates SOMEONE,then himself.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS366
He tucks a loose lock of hair behind Shaun's ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS367
Now traffic comes to a standstill where seven lanes merge into two.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS368
SOMEONE sends a text message.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS369
Now he and his dad speed across the Hudson river with SOMEONE in his boat.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS370
SOMEONE makes a phone call on his cell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS371
That night in his apartment he gives his father his business card.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS372
He eyes a copy of GQ.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS373
He passes a guy in the kitchen.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS374
Akron, central  terminal.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS375
The bustling crowd around SOMEONE suddenly stops and dances.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS376
In her apartment her mother smiles.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS377
SOMEONE looks at the stairs and sees SOMEONE standing there. He shrugs at her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS378
The people in the flash mob stop their frenetic jumping and square off.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS379
SOMEONE mouths the lyrics.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS380
He beams. The flash mob performs a choreographed routine.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS381
Watching the dancers twirl their partners all around her, SOMEONE allows an emotional smile. SOMEONE stands watching her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS382
He comes down from the stairs and walks closer to her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS383
He takes her hand and leads her to a balcony, overlooking the ballroom dancing flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS384
He kneels before her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS385
He stands facing her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS386
The flash mob freezes mid dance.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS387
He cuts her off with a deep, passionate kiss and lifts her off her feet while the performers remain perfectly still below them. With their lips still pressed together, SOMEONE opens her eyes and smiles.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS388
The members of the flash mob abruptly disburse as if they're just commuters going about their business.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS389
SOMEONE wipes tears from her big almond shaped eyes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS390
Outside, a horse drawn carriage waits at the curb.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS391
SOMEONE and SOMEONE cross the street to Pershing Square Central Cafe and have their date.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS23
SOMEONE jogs after the hurrying stilt-walker.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS25
Still in his Uncle SOMEONE jacket and beard, the young man races across a building's roof. He halts at its edge and eyes a police van below.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS26
At ground level, SOMEONE sprints past the burning parade float. On the roof the young man scampers one way then races back the other way with SOMEONE on his tail. The rugged man chases his target to the roof's edge where the young man leaps off. SOMEONE follows. They land on the police van, then hit the ground hard. Police surround them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS27
SOMEONE hands an officer his badge and ID.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS28
SOMEONE gingerly gets to his feet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS29
SOMEONE grabs the young man and cuffs him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS30
The officer cuffs SOMEONE. Now, SOMEONE steps off an elevator - phone in hand - and strides past a reception desk. Golden letters behind it read, Daily News.  She passes a colleague.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS31
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's rear.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS32
SOMEONE enters a newsroom. As she heads to her desk, a mustached man watches her shapely bottom. SOMEONE finds a print-out of her mugshot taped to her computer.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS33
A sticky-note reads, Don't forget court tomorrow. Mr. Ed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS34
The mustached man sits by her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS35
Meanwhile, police officers mingle at a bar. The bartender answers the phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS36
SOMEONE jots on a coaster.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS37
In a stall, SOMEONE hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS38
She claps her feet together.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS39
As she bursts out of the stall, SOMEONE exits a different one.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS40
She leaves. SOMEONE grins at the mirror.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS41
He plucks a tissue from a box. Later, SOMEONE strolls across the roof of an apartment building.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS42
Reaching a corner, she leans on a railing and peers over the edge. She shakes her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS43
She takes her phone from her bag and answers it as she returns to the roof's corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS44
At a spa, SOMEONE talks on phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS46
Nighttime at a police station, a man in a sport coat approaches a jail cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS47
He shows a badge on his belt. An officer releases SOMEONE from the cell. Now, SOMEONE and his police friend eat at a diner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS48
As SOMEONE chomps into a taco doused with hot sauce, his friend swigs a coke.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS49
SOMEONE drops his taco on his plate.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS50
Now at a courthouse, a man uses his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS51
A cab pulls up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS52
She answers her phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS53
He hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS55
the judge follows SOMEONE's gaze to the closed double-doors.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS56
Meanwhile, in the parking lot of a Dunkin' Donuts and a Baskin Robbins plaza,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS57
SOMEONE sits in his car, nervously tapping his steering wheel. He glances over his shoulder and blows out an impatient breath.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS58
A man smashes his window with a crowbar.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS60
He pulls SOMEONE out of his car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS61
He shoves him into an SUV.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS62
As he slams the door, a cab pulls into the parking lot. SOMEONE climbs out and sees the chiseled stranger speeding away in his black SUV.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS63
She frowns. Now, in another neighborhood a portly man exits the front door of a house with an adjoining storefront.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS64
He opens a gate. As he follows the sidewalk, he roots around in the pocket of his cargo shorts and pulls out a set of keys. Stopping at the storefront's glass door, he unlocks it and heads inside. A sign on the window reads, Sid's Bail Bonds. The portly man flips on the lights and finds SOMEONE asleep, sprawled across a leather loveseat.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS65
SOMEONE groggily opens his eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS66
SOMEONE sits up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS67
Later, SOMEONE packs his station wagon.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS68
He reaches for his pocket.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS69
He hands SOMEONE a folded piece of paper. The bounty hunter opens it and finds SOMEONE's mugshot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS70
He meets SOMEONE's gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS71
SOMEONE grins.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS72
SOMEONE does a dance.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS73
He hugs SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS74
He kisses him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS75
SOMEONE takes the check from SOMEONE's red-headed assistant and gives her a long, deep kiss.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS76
SOMEONE takes it from his mouth and puts it in hers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS77
Now at his place, a freshly showered SOMEONE grins at his reflection in a bathroom mirror as he brushes his teeth. Later, he packs a Taser and two guns into a bag. He heads outside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS78
Now, he rings SOMEONE's bell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS79
He jiggles the locked door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS80
SOMEONE scales a wall and lands in a muddy flowerbed. Tracking footprints, he enters SOMEONE's apartment through a back door and eyes her tasteful decor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS81
As he strolls into the spacious living room, SOMEONE notices his muddy footprints on a light rug. With a grin, he steps to the side dragging his foot and tracking a long smear. In the bathroom, he drops SOMEONE's toothbrush in the toilet, then places it back in its holder. In the bedroom, he lounges on SOMEONE's bed - his muddy shoes on her duvet. He snacks on a pile of nacho cheese Doritos, spilled conveniently within reach.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS82
SOMEONE deletes saved episodes of Weeds and 30 Rock from SOMEONE's TiVo. Meanwhile, SOMEONE keys into a clean white front door. As she enters, SOMEONE freezes on the bed and glances toward the hall. Chewing Doritos, he tosses down the remote and wipes his mouth and hands on a pillow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS83
SOMEONE searches a small pink-tiled bathroom. SOMEONE draws his gun and creeps into the hall.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS84
SOMEONE peers around a corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS85
SOMEONE skulks down the stairs.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS86
SOMEONE defensively grabs a picture frame and presses her back to a wall by a white-trim doorway.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS87
As she turns the corner, SOMEONE reaches the white door frame at the bottom of the stairs. They both turn the corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS88
SOMEONE scares a cat.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS89
SOMEONE aims his gun at SOMEONE. SOMEONE's at a completely different address.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS90
Back at her place,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS91
SOMEONE aims at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS92
SOMEONE cocks his head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS94
the cat hides under a chair.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS95
SOMEONE frowns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS97
he swigs juice from a carton.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS98
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS99
SOMEONE's grin vanishes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS100
SOMEONE grabs the phone and hits redial.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS101
He hits the disconnect button.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS102
Now, in SOMEONE's pink-tiled bathroom, SOMEONE searches a vanity then picks through dirty laundry strewn around the tub. She finds a bar coaster in a pair of jeans. A note on the back reads, Audit Evidence Depository. Missing shit.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS103
Now, on her cell, she crosses the Verrazano-Narrows Bridge.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS104
SOMEONE exits an evidence locker while on his cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS105
Now, SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE's building. As he gets into his car, SOMEONE creeps outside and scurries over to a red MINI Cooper.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS106
Now, a bird's-eye view shows SOMEONE's car exiting a tunnel and approaching a toll plaza. Later, the baby blue ragtop crosses the bridge.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS107
Later still, it drives beneath an overpass sign reading, Welcome to Atlantic City. A billboard, featuring SOMEONE's mother, reads, Kitty Borgata.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS108
Now, we glimpse lavish buildings housing Atlantic City's hotel casinos. In a lounge, Kitty stands in the spotlight on a stage.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS109
SOMEONE enters and smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS110
Shading her eyes, Kitty peers out at him, he waves.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS111
She slaps him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS112
Kitty gives him a big hug.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS113
she slips off her pumps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS114
SOMEONE brightens.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS115
At a racetrack, people crowd the stands. An older woman rubs sunblock on her bare arms. A young woman in a flowered hat eyes her tickets. Jockeys ride their horses toward the starting gate. The race begins and the animals burst onto the track. Two young women cheer. Sitting alone on a long bench, SOMEONE thoughtfully pieces through her collective notes, which include the coaster.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS116
She digs her cell from her purse and answers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS117
Standing near a corral, SOMEONE grins.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS118
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE sharing her bench.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS119
He affects a nonchalant shake of the head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS120
SOMEONE's brow nits distrustfully.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS121
SOMEONE looks away, shifting her wary gaze then frowns at him again. He smirks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS122
Standing, he steps before her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS123
SOMEONE smiles and shakes her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS124
She starts to go. His leg blocks her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS126
A race starts and SOMEONE runs too.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS127
She hurries up an aisle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS128
The horses race down the track.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS129
SOMEONE rubs his hands together, inhales through them, and dashes off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS130
As SOMEONE trots through a picnic area, SOMEONE sprints through a lobby. Emerging outside, SOMEONE finds him blocking her path.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS131
She runs off the other way. We glimpse the racing horses' legs, SOMEONE's high heels, and SOMEONE's sneakered feet. At a concession stand, he cuts SOMEONE off and offers popcorn.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS132
She bats it away and flees. On a patio, SOMEONE intercepts her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS133
She passes him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS134
SOMEONE's four-inch stiletto heels carry her out to a drop-off area.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS135
She approaches two rows of waiting cabs parked along a curb. SOMEONE's convertible arrives, blocking them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS136
SOMEONE gets out, steps in her path, and draws a gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS137
She brushes past him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS138
As SOMEONE swaggers over, she tensely faces him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS139
He steps in close.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS140
Finding herself head to head with her ex, SOMEONE backs up a pace.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS141
He hefts her over his shoulder.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS142
She slaps at his back as he carries her to his car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS143
He pops the trunk and dumps her in.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS144
SOMEONE hurries toward him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS145
In the trunk,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS146
she smacks the lid. Her ex-husband backs the car up then pulls away. SOMEONE watches helplessly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS147
He rushes off. Now, a storefront sign reads, Blue Ink Tattoos.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS148
Inside, SOMEONE's captor readies a needle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS149
Duct tape holds SOMEONE's head in place.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS150
His captor waves the needle in his face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS151
The chiseled thug blinks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS152
At Sid's Bail Bonds, Teresa chews gum as she strolls to the phone and answers it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS153
SOMEONE checks his cell display.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS154
SOMEONE takes the incoming call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS155
The thug holds him at gunpoint.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS156
She hits her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS157
The thug flips SOMEONE's phone shut.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS158
Outside, the thug makes a call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS159
Reaching his SUV, he ends the call and gets in. He sets down a newspaper article featuring SOMEONE's name and photo as the credited writer.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS160
In his car, SOMEONE notices smoke wafting from the back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS161
Later, he pops the trunk. SOMEONE throws the flare aside and punches SOMEONE in the crotch. He chases her down the shoulder then tackles her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS162
Now, In Atlantic City, a storefront sign reads, Souvenirs, SOMEONE's Gifts. The hulking goateed guy, SOMEONE, arrives sporting two black eyes and a gash across his nose He heads inside and lumbers to the rear.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS163
He enters a dingy backroom where bookies work at stations along a table. As he arrives at a desk, an aging blonde swivels to face him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS164
SOMEONE shifts his sheepish gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS165
At night at a gas station, SOMEONE sits handcuffed to SOMEONE's passenger door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS166
SOMEONE washes the windshield.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS167
She gives a resigned shrug.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS168
SOMEONE imagines Teresa chewing her gum and popping a bubble.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS169
He replaces the gas nozzle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS170
He leans on his open window.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS171
Later, Atlantic City's hotel casinos gleam in the night air. SOMEONE works his jaw driving his blue convertible past them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS172
She offers him a wad of cash.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS173
She studies him skeptically.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS174
She smells the cash.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS175
SOMEONE pouts then licks his lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS176
Later, he unlocks her handcuffs and lets her out of the car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS177
Now, from his MINI Cooper, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE's car arrive at the Taj Mahal Casino.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS178
With SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS179
SOMEONE checks his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS180
He hits a button
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS181
In the casino.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS182
Now, SOMEONE drives into the Taj Mahal parking lot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS183
Out of his car, he creeps up alongside SOMEONE's Delta '88.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS184
He knocks on the trunk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS185
He presses an ear to the trunk and listens.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS186
He opens the driver side door and pops the trunk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS187
He finds it empty.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS188
SOMEONE looks on.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS189
He points at the car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS190
SOMEONE slams SOMEONE's head against the trunk. SOMEONE crumbles. Now, at a craps table,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS191
he shows her the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS192
SOMEONE frowns. SOMEONE quirks his brow at her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS193
She reluctantly purses her lips and blows on the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS194
He rolls a seven.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS195
A croupier's hand nudges a tall stack of chips toward SOMEONE. Later, SOMEONE blows on the dice again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS196
She gawks and SOMEONE points excitedly. The stickman returns the dice to him, a croupier adds two more stacks of chips to his winnings, and SOMEONE and SOMEONE both blow on the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS197
The bounty hunter rolls a seven.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS198
SOMEONE fans herself nervously.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS199
The croupier awards SOMEONE two more stacks. Now, SOMEONE blows on the dice repeatedly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS200
SOMEONE cheers throwing her hands in the air.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS201
She starts off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS202
He grabs her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS203
He shows the dice but she keeps her lips together.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS204
The stickman eyes SOMEONE, who throws the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS205
He rolls.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS206
Later, in a hallway.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS207
Now, they enter a spacious and eclectic suite.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS208
SOMEONE weaves past boldly upholstered furniture.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS209
She admires the chic lamps and mod accessories.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS210
He cuffs her to the headboard, plops down their bags, and heads out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS211
As he stalks out, she flings a vase after him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS212
Trapped by the handcuffs, she plops onto the bed. SOMEONE struts out of the room and presses an elevator call button. He rubs his hands together then primps in a mirror.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS213
He boards the elevator, presses a button, and snaps open the check from Teresa.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS214
He kisses it and the elevator closes. Later, it opens revealing a disheveled SOMEONE clutching a drink. His shirt half untucked and his collar sticking up, he staggers out and drains the glass.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS215
Now he stumbles down the hall, leaning against a wall for support. The drunken man takes a rest then hobbles forward and bends over his door lock. He disappears inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS216
In the bedroom, SOMEONE lies asleep. Her handcuffed arm leaning vertically against the headboard. SOMEONE eyes her, swaying, then sets his gun on the nightstand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS217
Later, on his side, he turns off the light.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS218
He flops onto his back fully dressed and in his shoes and scooches around getting comfy.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS219
Later, SOMEONE's eyes spring open.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS220
Raising her brow, she looks around thoughtfully, then sits up and peeks over at SOMEONE. Just past him, she spots his gun on the nightstand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS221
SOMEONE lies on her back then rolls toward him,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS222
sliding the handcuff along the top rail of the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS223
She props herself up on her hands and knees then inches closer and reaches for the gun with her free hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS224
Her fingers fall short. She tips off balance but catches herself before landing on top of SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS225
SOMEONE braces herself on the headboard, digs her feet into the comforter, and makes her downward facing body as stiff as a board.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS226
She carefully straddles SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS227
He drowsily opens his eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS228
She musters a smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS229
She playfully smacks the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS230
She cranes her lips close to his.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS231
He raises his gun in front of her face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS232
She rears back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS233
She climbs off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS234
She turns her back to him and punches her pillow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS235
He eyes her, smiling.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS236
Daytime. A mural on a slim, brick building bears SOMEONE's name. SOMEONE enters the back room with a pizza.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS237
SOMEONE raises a golf club to let Ray pass.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS238
He leads SOMEONE into a grungy bathroom where SOMEONE sits handcuffed to a pipe.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS239
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the golf club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS240
SOMEONE hits him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS241
Now, in the suite.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS242
SOMEONE finds herself alone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS243
A maid enters.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS244
She peeks into the bedroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS245
SOMEONE glances at the handcuff.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS246
In the bathroom, SOMEONE steps out of the shower, tucking a towel around his waist.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS247
In the bedroom, SOMEONE zips up SOMEONE's satchel. She tugs at the handcuff then hunkers down and winds up swinging the bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS248
She flings it across the room.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS249
It misses the ottoman and lands on the floor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS250
In the bathroom, SOMEONE looks up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS251
As he opens the door, SOMEONE lies down and mimes a yawn.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS252
She sits up and looks around.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS253
She points at the handcuff.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS254
He unlocks her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS255
Massaging her wrist, SOMEONE strides to the bathroom. She sees SOMEONE following her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS256
He glances at her low-cut top then ogles her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS257
She shrugs theatrically and enters the bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS258
He steps up to the doors.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS259
In the bathroom, SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's Taser from under her skirt.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS260
She turns it on.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS262
She tasers him in the neck. SOMEONE convulses and crumples. SOMEONE skips over him and grabs her bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS263
Later, at the elevators, she presses the call button.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS264
One opens behind her and she hurries aboard, shoes in hand. Another elevator opens and the chiseled thug strides out. He glimpses SOMEONE as her elevator closes. He quickly presses the call button.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS266
as the thug searches for her a pedicab pulls up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS267
SOMEONE hops into the shaded seat.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS268
They ride away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS269
SOMEONE looks in her bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS270
The driver checks her out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS271
SOMEONE looks off and gives a half-wince, half-smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS272
Later, SOMEONE pedals the stolen pedicab by herself.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS273
The teenager chases her on foot. She rides down a ramp. Now, in the hotel suite's bathroom, SOMEONE awakens on the floor. Holding his head, he sits up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS274
Later, an aerial view shows his baby-blue Delta driving away from the Taj Mahal. Behind the wheel, SOMEONE eyes the two-inch red SOMEONE on his neck in the rear-view mirror then touches it and winces.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS275
Now, SOMEONE struggles to pedal down a highway. Cringing, she leans wearily over the handlebars.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS276
SOMEONE spots the pedicab from a block behind and gives a vengeful smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS277
SOMEONE spots him and scowls. She pedals faster.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS278
He drives up and taps the back of the pedicab with his bumper.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS279
SOMEONE gapes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS280
SOMEONE accelerates and taps her again. Several other vehicles speed past them. SOMEONE drives up close behind her then backs off. SOMEONE pedals exhaustedly then halts, slumping. SOMEONE stops inches behind her then scoots forward and bumps the pedicab again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS281
SOMEONE sneers. A sedan passes them and she climbs off the bike.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS282
She grabs up her purse and glares at him, then stalks around to the passenger door and reaches for the handle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS283
SOMEONE backs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS284
He shifts into park and raises both hands innocently. SOMEONE glances around. She treads back to the door, her eyes locked on SOMEONE's.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS285
As she reaches for the handle, the car lurches forward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS286
SOMEONE winces, stifling tears, then stares off. SOMEONE eyes her churlishly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS287
Her lips tighten and she shakes her head, looking skyward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS288
She claps a hand to her mouth.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS289
SOMEONE glances away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS290
SOMEONE brushes her hair out of her face then sobs into her hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS291
He shifts the car into park, gets out, and faces his ex-wife.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS292
She stays put. Her posture wounded and childlike.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS293
He knits his brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS294
SOMEONE tugs on the door handle, which sticks, then gives.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS295
She climbs into the seat and slams the door shut.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS296
SOMEONE looks over his shoulder and spots a billboard in a field.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS297
It reads, Cupid's Cabin and shows a picture of a bed and breakfast in a Victorian style mansion.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS298
The bounty hunter purses his lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS299
He shuffles back alongside the car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS300
In the passenger seat, SOMEONE wipes her eyes then rests her forehead on the back of her hand, hiding her face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS301
SOMEONE sheepishly opens his door and takes his seat at the wheel.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS302
He glances at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS303
He backs the car away from the pedicab, steers around it, and drives off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS304
Now, SOMEONE leads an elderly man with fuzzy hair into the grungy bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS305
SOMEONE rests his leg on the toilet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS306
The man takes out a giant syringe.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS307
The vet jabs the needle into SOMEONE's neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS308
Now, in SOMEONE's car, SOMEONE rides with one wrist cuffed to the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS309
SOMEONE spots a luxury pick-up in her side mirror then eyes it over her shoulder.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS310
SOMEONE aims the rear-view mirror at it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS311
The pick-up pulls up beside them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS312
As the chiseled thug aims a gun at them from behind the wheel, SOMEONE jams her foot on the gas pedal. SOMEONE veers onto the shoulder, then into oncoming traffic on a one-way street. The thug shoots at them from the parallel two-way road.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS313
Drawing his gun, SOMEONE returns fire. SOMEONE cowers. The pick-up swerves onto the one-way street and jams itself alongside the Delta, mangling the convertible's headlight and SOMEONE. The vehicles separate. SOMEONE bashes the pick-up and takes aim.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS314
As they speed forward, shoving against each other, SOMEONE spots an SUV headed straight for the thug's vehicle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS315
Swerving, the chiseled man bursts through construction barricades then ramps up a stack of barricades and launches into mid-air. The pick-up lands on its roof and skids across the two-lane road. Reaching a grassy field, it tumbles onto its side. SOMEONE pulls over.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS316
She wrenches her cuffed arm.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS317
He gets out and surveys the damage.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS318
As SOMEONE jogs toward the luxury pick-up, the thug wriggles out through a window on the other side. Nearing he vehicle, SOMEONE slows and aims his gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS319
His assailant gets to his feet, using the pick-up as cover.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS320
The bounty hunter ventures toward the vehicles tail-end and the thug edges around its front. SOMEONE arrives on the other side and finds no sign of the gunman.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS321
Turning back, he finds himself aiming at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS322
She clutches her door's broken-off inner panel.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS324
On the one way street, the thug yanks a woman from her mini-van, gets in, and speeds off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS325
SOMEONE gawks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS326
Later, they search the pick-up together.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS327
He opens the covered bed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS328
He finds a golf bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS329
She hurls the cup at him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS330
SOMEONE climbs out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS331
SOMEONE notices a tag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS332
SOMEONE glares then yields a smile. Now, SOMEONE's ragtop follows a winding road toward a mansion perched atop an immaculately landscaped hill. At the mansions entrance, they surrender the car to a valet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS333
Inside, a pristinely quaffed woman works a reception desk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS334
Her red painted lips primly stifle an excited smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS335
They follow her through the lobby.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS336
The woman frowns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS337
The woman scowls suspiciously.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS338
SOMEONE smiles tightly and SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS339
The couple steps out back and wanders through a festive picnic.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS340
He walks her to the party's edge.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS341
They find some caddies.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS342
One rumples his lips then flees.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS343
He scurries down some steps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS344
SOMEONE gives chase.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS345
The caddy leads him down a hill and across a grassy driving range. The bounty hunter frantically dodges golf balls as they whiz toward him. He leaps over one then ducks another. One ball buzzes low over his head and a fourth whips past his nose. As he leaves the range and runs onto a green, SOMEONE drives up in a golf cart.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS346
Elsewhere, the caddy peeks out from a sunken sand trap.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS347
The caddy crawls out from hiding.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS348
As he holds the flag for putting golfers, SOMEONE spies him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS349
SOMEONE steers the cart in the caddy's direction. The young man spots them and his polite smile fades.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS350
Dropping the flag, he dashes over a hill.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS351
Cresting the rise, the cart speeds toward a pond.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS352
SOMEONE leaps out, tackles the caddy, and tumbles with him into the water.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS353
The out of control cart plunges in beside them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS354
SOMEONE dunks him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS355
SOMEONE dunks him again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS356
He shows his tattooed chest.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS357
SOMEONE swaps looks with SOMEONE then releases the caddy.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS358
Now, at the tattoo parlor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS360
she pulls her hair back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS361
He plucks it from her neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS362
SOMEONE digs out his cell and holds it up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS363
He answers it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS364
SOMEONE frowns uneasily at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS365
He ends the call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS366
In the convertible
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS367
at a turnoff, they pass a sign reading, Cupid's Cabin.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS368
Later, they face a three-story Victorian style house with a wrap-around porch.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS369
A curly-haired woman answers the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS370
A chubby man arrives.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS371
SOMEONE smiles sadly at SOMEONE, who gives a nostalgic nod.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS372
SOMEONE and SOMEONE muster smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS373
SOMEONE stares, her features frozen in a thoughtful gape.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS374
The older woman gawks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS375
Nighttime. In frumpy clothes, SOMEONE and SOMEONE dine on a patio.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS376
He eyes the adjoining building.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS377
They share a warm smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS378
SOMEONE drops her gaze, fiddling with her silky honey-brown hair.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS379
She shrugs a hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS380
SOMEONE lifts his brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS381
Looking away, she shrugs again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS382
SOMEONE blinks at her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS383
SOMEONE regards him thoughtfully.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS384
He gives a boyish half-smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS385
She raises her champagne glass.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS386
SOMEONE follows suit.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS387
They tap glasses. SOMEONE sips his sparkling wine with a knitted brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS388
SOMEONE's smile fades to a tight smirk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS389
SOMEONE gives a sad shrug.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS390
Resting her cheek against her hand, SOMEONE shakes her head and gazes skyward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS391
SOMEONE looks away then faces him defenselessly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS392
SOMEONE tearfully tightens her lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS393
Now, the two stroll down a hallway lit cheerily with glass-shaded lamps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS394
SOMEONE pauses to eye an inscription on one of the doors.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS395
Reaching another door, they find a lavender heart-shaped sign that reads, Bliss in rosy cursive letters.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS396
SOMEONE and SOMEONE chuckle at the frilly placard then share a warm lingering gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS397
SOMEONE starts to open her mouth, then shakes her head and smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS398
Staring at her intently, he nods.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS400
As he unlocks the door, he steps in close and leans his face toward hers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS401
SOMEONE opens the door, revealing a narrow four-post bed on a lavender carpet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS402
Table lamps cast their soft glow against the rosy wall.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS403
SOMEONE gestures her inside and SOMEONE precedes him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS404
At the Borgata lounge, Kitty takes a phone call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS406
SOMEONE drops by.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS407
SOMEONE accepts a tray.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS408
Checking SOMEONE's wallet, he finds their wedding photo.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS409
It shows SOMEONE and him beaming as bride and groom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS410
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, who waits in the hall.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS411
He shuts the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS412
SOMEONE moves from the door, his eyes fixed on the photo, and his lips parted.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS414
she slugs back an entire cocktail and gives a bracing twitch of the brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS415
SOMEONE and Teresa talk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS416
SOMEONE enters with his kids.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS417
SOMEONE picks up the phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS418
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS419
SOMEONE hangs up then stares at her reflection in the mirror.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS422
SOMEONE lights candles around the room and pops a CD into a player.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS423
SOMEONE peeks out from the bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS424
His back to SOMEONE, SOMEONE hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS425
His ex-wife returns to the bathroom unnoticed. Now, she steps out wrapped tightly in a bathrobe.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS426
She avoids SOMEONE's gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS427
Marching to the bed, she blows out a candle on a bedside table, turns off the CD player, and hurls some pillows to the floor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS428
She throws down more pillows until only a few remain.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS429
She blows out another candle and climbs under the covers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS430
Lying on her back, SOMEONE closes her eyes then sneakily peeks one open. She watches as SOMEONE blows out more candles. He snuffs the last one with his hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS431
He pops a candy into his mouth and climbs into bed fully clothed. He scoots up against SOMEONE and folds his arms.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS432
SOMEONE eyes him as he chews. He glances over and she looks away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS433
He closes his eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS434
She climbs out of bed and grabs a blanket then swipes the pillow out from behind SOMEONE's head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS435
He bumps the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS436
As he winces, SOMEONE throws the pillow at his face. She settles onto a window bench.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS437
Closing his eyes, SOMEONE folds his hands behind his head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS438
From the bench, SOMEONE turns and glares at him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS439
Later, she wears her own clothes as she slams the suite's door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS440
SOMEONE stirs. He finds himself cuffed to the bed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS441
SOMEONE jingles the handcuff keys.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS442
She leaves.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS443
SOMEONE yanks on his cuff secured tightly to the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS444
As SOMEONE races out the door, SOMEONE frantically yanks on the headboard. He breaks off the top and falls back onto the bed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS445
Now, as he rushes outside, SOMEONE pulls his car out of the drive.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS446
Still attached to the headboard, he chases after her. The convertible speeds away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS447
He watches as it disappears around a corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS448
Meanwhile, at a gas station, SOMEONE opens his trunk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS449
He plucks a SOMEONE from the garbage bag full of cash and heads toward a convenient store.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS450
SOMEONE halts, gives Ray the finger, and steps into the store. Ray spots SOMEONE's car as it rides by.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS452
At cupid's cabin, as SOMEONE stands on the front stoop, SOMEONE shuts the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS453
SOMEONE watches as a black luxury sedan pulls up to the porch steps. A young couple climbs out and he approaches the driver.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS454
As the couple heads up the front steps, SOMEONE climbs into the car and peels out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS455
Meanwhile, SOMEONE drives SOMEONE's car. She spots a storefront with a Pink awning. Its psychedelic sign reads, Blue Ink Tattoos. Now, inside the tattoo parlor, SOMEONE strolls to the counter where a woman with a Mohawk and multiple piercings works.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS456
The woman glances at her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS457
SOMEONE frowns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS458
A bald tattoo artist eyes SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS459
She struts toward him, hand on her hip.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS460
She grabs her breasts.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS461
She frames her pelvis with her hands.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS462
She runs a hand down her thigh then pats it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS463
The tattoo artist eyes SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS464
SOMEONE turns to the tatted clerk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS465
Now, SOMEONE sits in a chair in a small room papered in tattoo designs.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS466
He draws a curtain.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS467
SOMEONE sits.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS468
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS469
Sitting beside her, SOMEONE leans back and smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS470
With a wave, SOMEONE hurries through the parlor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS471
Brushing her hair out of her face, she peers over her shoulder then casually heads to the bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS472
She opens the door, steps inside, and waits briefly. Glancing around, she creeps out of the bathroom and makes her way up some stairs. Now, she opens a door to a wood-paneled entry way. She cautiously checks over her shoulder then tiptoes inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS473
Seen through another doorway, an office chair sits at a desk with a giant mural of a snarling tiger behind it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS474
A red and black bowling shirt hangs on the back of the chair.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS475
SOMEONE scurries into the office.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS476
She sifts through a stack of paperwork then sits at the desk and rifles through files and drawers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS477
Swiveling in the chair, she spots a framed photo of a bowling team. In it, SOMEONE and SOMEONE pose with two teammates.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS478
A caption reads, Police Bowling League.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS479
SOMEONE looks around then sets the photo back on a trophy shelf.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS480
Scanning the office, she follows the sound around a corner and finds a louvered door locked by a deadbolt. She undoes the lock, opens the door, and finds SOMEONE inside. His mouth and wrists duct taped.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS481
Downstairs, SOMEONE enters.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS482
Upstairs, SOMEONE cuts tape binding SOMEONE's wrists.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS483
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE out a side door then rushes back in, grabs the bowling photo, and hurries out. SOMEONE enters through the front door, spots the open closet, and draws his gun. Looking inside, he finds it empty.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS485
They race down the street. Meanwhile, SOMEONE makes a call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS487
they get in SOMEONE's car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS488
SOMEONE's thugs sit in back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS489
They brandish their guns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS490
SOMEONE shrugs at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS491
As SOMEONE scrambles out, SOMEONE gawks. With a parting glance, SOMEONE sprints away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS492
SOMEONE frowns at Ray. SOMEONE lets his head lull back. Now, SOMEONE spies his car in a nearby parking lot. He pulls in. A mural of two widespread female legs flanks the hot-pink back door of a strip club named, Double D's. SOMEONE climbs out of the borrowed car, satchel in hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS493
He checks his phone and flips it open.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS494
SOMEONE approaches a purple and white muscle car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS495
Inside the strip club, SOMEONE eyes his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS496
Outside, SOMEONE shoots the lock of SOMEONE's trunk and opens it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS497
He finds the garbage bag of cash inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS498
He answers his phone and casually leans on the open trunk lid.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS499
He slings the garbage bag over his shoulder.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS500
SOMEONE enters the club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS501
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS502
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE with her captors and hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS503
SOMEONE watches as the two thugs escort his ex-wife through the strip club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS504
They stop at a neon restroom sign and she heads inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS505
In the bathroom, SOMEONE's shoulders sag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS506
Across the club, SOMEONE watches the thugs unnoticed. He answers his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS508
Outside the restroom, SOMEONE tosses cash at some patrons.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS509
SOMEONE hurls cash at the dancers onstage.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS510
As SOMEONE tosses bills to patrons and employees, the thugs try to grab the cash from their hands. SOMEONE empties the garbage bag on a pool table then runs onstage with more money.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS511
SOMEONE pushes people from the pool table.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS512
He punches a guy. SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in the restroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS513
A brawl breaks out in the club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS515
Back in the bathroom, SOMEONE stares wistfully.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS516
He leads her through the chaos. At the pool table a formidable pole dancer piggy-backs SOMEONE. As Ray shoves her off, she grabs a bottle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS517
The woman smashes it on SOMEONE's head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS518
He falls. Ray faces the dancer.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS519
She knocks him out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS520
Now, in the police department.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS521
In the ragtop, SOMEONE ends the call and glances at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS522
The convertible speeds down a street and through an intersection. Now, in the depository building, SOMEONE packs evidence baggies filled with white powder into a brown paper bag then rolls the top down.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS523
Outside, the Delta '88 sits parked across the street.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS524
A dark sedan drives around the corner of the depository and pulls into a parking spot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS525
SOMEONE's at the wheel.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS526
SOMEONE slumps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS527
They lock gazes then watch SOMEONE enter the depository.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS528
Inside, SOMEONE exits a freight elevator.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS529
SOMEONE shifts his confused stare.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS530
Downstairs, SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter through a main door. A clerk behind a cage-wire barrier addresses them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS532
SOMEONE sets the paper bag down.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS533
The men shoot at each other. SOMEONE grabs the clerk through a window.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS534
The clerk hits a button on his desk. SOMEONE opens a nearby gate.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS535
SOMEONE releases the clerk, who grabs a phone. Now, SOMEONE creeps up a stairwell, his gun drawn. SOMEONE follows. Later, they exit the stairwell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS536
SOMEONE fearfully trots up and hides behind SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS537
He glares toward her feet and she mouths, Sorry.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS538
As SOMEONE surveys their surroundings, SOMEONE takes cover behind a pillar.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS539
He irritably waves her over.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS540
A view through tall shelving units crammed with evidence shows the couple prowl forward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS541
As they sneak, SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's shoulder and he wheels around with his gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS542
Blood stains the freight elevator and they glimpse a fallen man's feet. As SOMEONE skulks off, SOMEONE and SOMEONE slink toward the elevator and find SOMEONE bleeding inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS543
They hurry over.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS544
SOMEONE swaps looks with SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS545
SOMEONE stalks off, gun raised. Back in the elevator, SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS546
SOMEONE glares at him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS547
Out among the industrial shelves, SOMEONE creeps past aisles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS548
SOMEONE hides at the end of one unit and watches SOMEONE creeping by.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS550
Back in the elevator, SOMEONE points at SOMEONE insistently then creeps out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS551
In the depository, SOMEONE prowls down an aisle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS552
He aims his gun around a corner and scans the vacant shadows.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS553
SOMEONE minces up to a shelving unit and peeks around it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS554
Elsewhere, SOMEONE ducks low then skulks forward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS555
SOMEONE sidles down an aisle, grabs SOMEONE's shoulder, and jabs his gun against the bounty hunter's neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS556
Hidden, SOMEONE spots them. SOMEONE drops his gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS557
SOMEONE mouths, Oh God and searches the shelves around her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS558
SOMEONE spots a pair of evidence boxes. One labeled, Gotti, K and the other Gotti, V. A long flat box beneath them reads handle with care. As SOMEONE kneels, SOMEONE finds an outline of a shotgun printed on top.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS559
SOMEONE takes aim.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS560
SOMEONE grins. SOMEONE fumes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS561
She blows a box to pieces.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS562
As SOMEONE turns to shoot, SOMEONE sweeps his legs. SOMEONE misses.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS563
Punched repeatedly, SOMEONE collapses. SOMEONE kicks his weapon away from him then glances at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS564
Daytime, outside. Dozens of police cruisers surround the depository.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS565
She kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS566
As she leaves she takes a call from SOMEONE, who limps between a warehouse and an empty lot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS567
SOMEONE drops.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS568
SOMEONE hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS569
Later, in SOMEONE's ragtop,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS570
a sly grin spreads across SOMEONE's lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS571
She and SOMEONE swap warm smiles. Sunlight bathes her face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS572
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE skids around a corner, pulls into a curbside spot, and brakes hard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS573
She notices the police station across the street.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS574
SOMEONE gets out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS576
In the station, SOMEONE wears handcuffs.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS577
A female officer leads SOMEONE away as she glares at SOMEONE. The bounty hunter signs a form and the cop at the desk shakes his head incredulously.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS578
Pursing his mouth regretfully, SOMEONE waves goodbye to the cop and ambles out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS579
Now, SOMEONE strolls outside passing an officer and handcuffed teen on their way in. As the bounty hunter descends the stoop, the arresting officer from the parade swaggers up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS580
SOMEONE eyes him with a half-smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS581
SOMEONE punches him. Inside, SOMEONE uses a phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS582
Gelman shoves a cuffed SOMEONE toward a holding cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS583
The officers place the couple in side-by-side cells. SOMEONE shrugs and faces his ex-wife through the bars. SOMEONE beams at him and shakes her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS584
They share a smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS585
They step up to the bars. SOMEONE reaches through them and wraps her arms around SOMEONE's neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS586
They kiss passionately.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS587
SOMEONE strokes her ex-husband's hair then cups the back of his head in both her hands.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS588
Separating, they gaze into each other's eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS589
Grinning, SOMEONE massages his neck then wraps her arms around him once again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS590
They embrace and share a deep kiss.
BURLESQUE_DVS26
Later as the blonde packs a suitcase, the sexy dancers pump their hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS27
The blonde regards a framed photo of a woman.
BURLESQUE_DVS28
She sings in the empty dive.
BURLESQUE_DVS29
She leaves the trailer park behind.
BURLESQUE_DVS32
At a bus station.
BURLESQUE_DVS33
Now she peers dreamily out the window of a cruising bus.
BURLESQUE_DVS34
As the sequined-clad dancers command their stage, the blonde sings to empty chairs in SOMEONE's bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS35
Now the Hollywood sign fills the screen. On the bus, the sleepy blonde opens her eyes just as the sign's reflection skates across her window.
BURLESQUE_DVS36
Later in a run-down room at the old redbrick Hotel Rosslyn, she opens her suitcase. Other views show the glitzy athletic dancers in unison, then the blonde rocking out in SOMEONE's empty bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS37
Now the blonde seals her stash of money inside a plastic bag.
BURLESQUE_DVS38
In the bathroom, she lifts the lid off the toilet tank and carefully sets the bag inside, leaving its top edge over the back rim.
BURLESQUE_DVS39
She replaces the porcelain lid.
BURLESQUE_DVS40
Now she unpacks her framed photo.
BURLESQUE_DVS41
The blonde gazes fondly at the photo, which shows the brunette woman cradling a young girl.
BURLESQUE_DVS42
Now the newcomer to LA sits at a desk with a postcard of the old hotel.
BURLESQUE_DVS43
She counts up several windows,
BURLESQUE_DVS44
She marks one specifically, and labels it.
BURLESQUE_DVS46
She flips the postcard. Her pen tip hovers.
BURLESQUE_DVS47
Then she rips the card to shreds.
BURLESQUE_DVS48
At her open window, she tosses the scraps and watches them flutter downward.
BURLESQUE_DVS49
Now she steps onto a busy sidewalk.
BURLESQUE_DVS50
She lifts her gaze from an issue of Back Stage Magazine in her hand and finds a sign for Hollywood Boulevard.
BURLESQUE_DVS51
Her finger trails down an ad in the magazine that seeks background singers for urban group.
BURLESQUE_DVS52
At a street corner, a set of signs marks Hollywood and Vine.
BURLESQUE_DVS53
Our view sweeps up the towering circular Capitol Records building.
BURLESQUE_DVS54
The blonde enters another building, then exits and crosses off the ad in her paper.
BURLESQUE_DVS55
Later still, she Xs out two more ads for singers and dancers as she continues down the boulevard.
BURLESQUE_DVS56
She gives someone a polite smile, which instantly fades as she moves on.
BURLESQUE_DVS57
Golden sunlight dwindles on the LA skyline.
BURLESQUE_DVS58
Fade to black.
BURLESQUE_DVS59
In the evening, the blonde strolls a busy street.
BURLESQUE_DVS60
Her eyes sweeping her surroundings,
BURLESQUE_DVS61
she stops at an eye-catching archway.
BURLESQUE_DVS62
Flashing light bulbs arc over a gleaming sign,
BURLESQUE_DVS63
Burlesque Lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS64
On the building's fire escape, she sees a woman in a sexy corset with a short feathery skirt.
BURLESQUE_DVS65
As the woman adjusts her striped thigh-highs, her gaze meets the blonde's. They share a smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS66
A bald man with a cigarette between his lips emerges from the building.
BURLESQUE_DVS67
The blonde heads toward the burlesque lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS68
Our view sweeps up a nearly completed high-rise behind her that advertises, Luxury Condos for Sale.
BURLESQUE_DVS69
The blonde checks out a poster outside the lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS70
It shows a pixie-faced blue-eyed brunette and reads, The Best View on the Sunset Strip.
BURLESQUE_DVS73
Entering the building, the blonde makes her way down a dim wood-paneled hall.
BURLESQUE_DVS74
As she heads down a staircase, she eyes the lounge's stage through a window.
BURLESQUE_DVS75
Onstage, cool-blue light bathes dancers in skimpy sailor-themed outfits as they strike provocative poses.
BURLESQUE_DVS76
A doorman holds out his hand.
BURLESQUE_DVS77
Onstage, six captivating dancers - three on a platform, three in front - scoop their hips and twirl their hands. They point skyward.
BURLESQUE_DVS78
The blonde opens her wallet and hesitates. She casts another glance at the show, then hands over a $20.
BURLESQUE_DVS79
Onstage, the reclined dancers snap then raise their arms in the air.
BURLESQUE_DVS81
Behind them, a woman with dark curly hair and high cheek bones faces us.
BURLESQUE_DVS82
She wears a low-cut black unitard with tails and fuchsia lapels.
BURLESQUE_DVS84
The dancers rise and strut around the singer.
BURLESQUE_DVS85
The dancers tap their heels, then nod to a neighboring stage where musicians play. One-by-one the dancers face the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS86
They pump their chests.
BURLESQUE_DVS87
The mesmerized blonde watches as varying dancers respond to their names.
BURLESQUE_DVS88
An auburn-haired dancer waves coyly. Now all of the dancers curl their fingers at us, beckoning mischievously.
BURLESQUE_DVS89
The dancers squat.
BURLESQUE_DVS90
The dancers strike alluring seductive poses and line up downstage. One lifts a leg higher than the singer's head.
BURLESQUE_DVS91
The posed dancers frame the smiling diva.
BURLESQUE_DVS92
Tears in her eyes, the blonde woman claps, transfixed.
BURLESQUE_DVS93
As the band plays, a spotlight shines on dancers in silver-sequined outfits. A handsome toned bartender in eyeliner and a bowler hat leans toward the blonde.
BURLESQUE_DVS94
They swap a smile. Then she returns her eyes to the stage where the dancers shake their hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS95
The bartender interrupts a pink-haired waitress who's busy flirting.
BURLESQUE_DVS96
The blonde turns back to the bartender.
BURLESQUE_DVS97
She points to the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS98
He hands her a business card.
BURLESQUE_DVS99
As she leaves, the bartender smiles. Now the blonde enters a bustling backstage area.
BURLESQUE_DVS100
A dancer bumps into her as she hurries past. The blonde sees another dancer pulling on a sparkling garter over black stockings.
BURLESQUE_DVS101
Two dancers wear light-satin corsets with black spirals at the breasts. The blonde visitor finds the bald stage manager conferring with the diva.
BURLESQUE_DVS102
The naysayer faces the singer.
BURLESQUE_DVS103
As SOMEONE does the dancer's hair, the blonde approaches.
BURLESQUE_DVS104
She finds SOMEONE applying makeup at a mirror and leans over her shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS105
The eager woman slouches sadly.
BURLESQUE_DVS106
On her way out, she collides with the brunette in large sunglasses.
BURLESQUE_DVS107
She shows her nails.
BURLESQUE_DVS108
As the pixie-faced dancer brushes on blush, the blonde tilts her head at her. SOMEONE glances over.
BURLESQUE_DVS109
As she leaves, Jesse reaches for SOMEONE's makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS110
Now, the young hopeful from Iowa sees the pink-haired waitress snubbing a customer. So she doffs her brown-leather jacket and grabs an empty tray from the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS111
She walks out among the tables. Collecting empty glasses, the ambitious girl starts taking drink orders.
BURLESQUE_DVS112
As she brings the tray back to the bar, SOMEONE notices her.
BURLESQUE_DVS113
The image revolves, framed in light bulbs like a dressing-room mirror. Now in black hot pants, the young hopeful collects a spent glass and draws a smile from SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS114
Onstage, SOMEONE slides down beaded strands forming a curtain. In a black bra and panties, she lands in a split.
BURLESQUE_DVS115
As the girl from Iowa serves drinks, SOMEONE notices her.
BURLESQUE_DVS116
She gestures for the young woman to come over.
BURLESQUE_DVS117
SOMEONE sits back down beside SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS118
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap smiles.
BURLESQUE_DVS119
SOMEONE windmills a leg, then seizes a bracelet off of Jesse.
BURLESQUE_DVS120
SOMEONE mimics a dance step, then resumes her work.
BURLESQUE_DVS121
SOMEONE leads four dancers downstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS122
Now a rugged man gets SOMEONE's attention.
BURLESQUE_DVS123
He slides her his AmEx.
BURLESQUE_DVS124
She looks back.
BURLESQUE_DVS126
SOMEONE smirks.
BURLESQUE_DVS127
SOMEONE pushes the beads aside. She sees SOMEONE performing, then SOMEONE waiting tables.
BURLESQUE_DVS128
She dons a white stole.
BURLESQUE_DVS129
The curtain parts and SOMEONE struts into the limelight.
BURLESQUE_DVS130
She passes her stole to SOMEONE, who pitches it and competitively joins SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS131
They swipe kitty paws at each other, then take turns upstaging each other.
BURLESQUE_DVS132
Entranced, SOMEONE flourishes a hand in front of a customer's face.
BURLESQUE_DVS133
Now the dancers drum their hips. SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's nose. Then they trade phrases.
BURLESQUE_DVS134
At the bar, SOMEONE imagines herself performing, showered by silver confetti.
BURLESQUE_DVS135
She flings away her serving tray.
BURLESQUE_DVS136
She twirls a string of diamonds overhead.
BURLESQUE_DVS137
Standing on a fringed pedestal surrounded by dancers, she coils the strand around her wrist. Snapping to, she gazes longingly at the performance. SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE offstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS138
She opens her arms to the crowd.
BURLESQUE_DVS139
SOMEONE taps her.
BURLESQUE_DVS140
While SOMEONE chats at Marcus' table, SOMEONE peers over his glasses. SOMEONE glances at the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS141
He slides her a tray of drinks. Now a stack of burlesque-related books lands on her hotel bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS142
SOMEONE lies on her stomach, flipping through photos of famed performers. At the lounge, she studies the dancers.
BURLESQUE_DVS143
Lying on her back, she rests another book on her chest.
BURLESQUE_DVS144
We glimpse the Burlesque Lounge sign. Then SOMEONE and SOMEONE at work.
BURLESQUE_DVS145
As she serves a drink, the bartender eyes her and rubs his unshaven cheek.
BURLESQUE_DVS146
Now a soundman preps a vocal CD.
BURLESQUE_DVS147
Sitting on the edge of the stage, SOMEONE crosses her legs.
BURLESQUE_DVS148
SOMEONE looks on with a tray of empty glasses.
BURLESQUE_DVS149
An overhead light shines down on three sexy nurses at an exam chair.
BURLESQUE_DVS150
In a lace bodysuit, SOMEONE stands and rocks her hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS151
Now in SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS152
SOMEONE looks on.
BURLESQUE_DVS153
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a document.
BURLESQUE_DVS154
He grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS155
SOMEONE paces to a framed photo of her burlesque troupe.
BURLESQUE_DVS156
The picture reflects her porcelain complexion.
BURLESQUE_DVS157
As SOMEONE waits, she regards him plainly.
BURLESQUE_DVS158
In the hall, SOMEONE overhears.
BURLESQUE_DVS159
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE turns on his way out.
BURLESQUE_DVS160
Onstage, the nurses roll SOMEONE along in the chair.
BURLESQUE_DVS161
She rises to her knees.
BURLESQUE_DVS162
A nurse eyes the crowd.
BURLESQUE_DVS163
SOMEONE watches her and SOMEONE looks up from pouring a drink. With a dramatic swoon, SOMEONE wipes her brow and lies back.
BURLESQUE_DVS164
Later a bartender pours two tequila shots. In the dressing room, the dancers fix their makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS165
SOMEONE sets down her tray.
BURLESQUE_DVS166
SOMEONE picks up the shot glasses.
BURLESQUE_DVS167
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch her down both shots.
BURLESQUE_DVS168
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE at a costume rack.
BURLESQUE_DVS170
SOMEONE glances back.
BURLESQUE_DVS171
SOMEONE peers through the rack.
BURLESQUE_DVS172
He wraps his legs around her.
BURLESQUE_DVS173
Now at the Hotel Rosslyn,
BURLESQUE_DVS174
SOMEONE finds her door broken in. She enters her ransacked studio apartment, then drops her purse and hurries into the bathroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS175
She finds the empty sandwich baggie on the floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS176
On the bed, SOMEONE finds her photograph under broken glass, halfway out of its now-bent frame.
BURLESQUE_DVS177
She holds the photo of the mother and child.
BURLESQUE_DVS178
SOMEONE glances around, then sits on the edge of the bed and covers her mouth.
BURLESQUE_DVS179
Now SOMEONE rides down a street on a motorcycle and parks.
BURLESQUE_DVS180
She sits on the stoop of a picturesque Spanish-style apartment building.
BURLESQUE_DVS181
Later he lets her in.
BURLESQUE_DVS182
He takes back his phone and they sip their drinks.
BURLESQUE_DVS183
Later, SOMEONE
BURLESQUE_DVS184
reclines on a daybed.
BURLESQUE_DVS185
SOMEONE sits at a synthesizer.
BURLESQUE_DVS186
She nestles in and pulls her blanket close.
BURLESQUE_DVS188
Rain pounds the street outside.
BURLESQUE_DVS189
SOMEONE wakes,
BURLESQUE_DVS190
then opens his bedroom's French doors and steps out in jeans and a white tank.
BURLESQUE_DVS191
SOMEONE ogles SOMEONE's short pajama top.
BURLESQUE_DVS192
As she hops into some jeans, she tips over.
BURLESQUE_DVS193
She collects her suitcase and bag.
BURLESQUE_DVS194
SOMEONE steps out of the apartment building and peers morosely at the rain-pelted street.
BURLESQUE_DVS195
She grabs a newspaper and holds it overhead.
BURLESQUE_DVS196
SOMEONE peers out of his window and watches her walk out to the curb.
BURLESQUE_DVS197
SOMEONE watches a car pass by. Then SOMEONE leaves the window.
BURLESQUE_DVS198
As SOMEONE waits in the downpour at a bus stop,
BURLESQUE_DVS199
SOMEONE steps out, barefoot.
BURLESQUE_DVS200
He picks her up.
BURLESQUE_DVS201
Now inside.
BURLESQUE_DVS202
He pushes the door shut.
BURLESQUE_DVS203
Now at the club, an employee polishes mirrored panels behind the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS204
The cashier puts down chairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS205
As the band practices, a bartender wipes down a bottle.
BURLESQUE_DVS206
SOMEONE enters a bathroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS207
She notes someone in a stall.
BURLESQUE_DVS208
The red-haired dancer steps out.
BURLESQUE_DVS209
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS210
The young woman leans on the sink.
BURLESQUE_DVS211
They hug.
BURLESQUE_DVS212
SOMEONE peers nervously skyward.
BURLESQUE_DVS213
Now beaming dancers in plain clothes leap through the air.
BURLESQUE_DVS214
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from a table on the empty floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS215
SOMEONE enters the club and observes the girls onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS216
As she doffs her jean jacket, she keeps watching.
BURLESQUE_DVS217
As the dancers leave, SOMEONE strides purposefully ahead.
BURLESQUE_DVS218
They notice SOMEONE onstage, swinging her hips and running her fingers down her blonde hair.
BURLESQUE_DVS219
SOMEONE peers back to the deejay booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS220
SOMEONE walks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS221
She wheels around.
BURLESQUE_DVS222
SOMEONE shoots a satisfied glance toward SOMEONE at the back of the house. SOMEONE returns to the table, where SOMEONE raises an eyebrow.
BURLESQUE_DVS223
SOMEONE and Coco enter and spot SOMEONE onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS224
Standing at a chair with her back turned, SOMEONE lets her hair down.
BURLESQUE_DVS225
SOMEONE joins the girls.
BURLESQUE_DVS226
Our view rises up SOMEONE's slender body
BURLESQUE_DVS227
As SOMEONE enters with a box of liquor, he notices her too.
BURLESQUE_DVS228
SOMEONE gyrates her backside, then looks over her shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS229
Holding the back of the chair, she seductively points her knees in and out.
BURLESQUE_DVS230
She whips her hair back and steps forward.
BURLESQUE_DVS231
SOMEONE and the others keep watching.
BURLESQUE_DVS232
SOMEONE holds her hands out like paws, then slaps her backside with her right, then with her left,
BURLESQUE_DVS233
then twice more before resuming the wild dance.
BURLESQUE_DVS234
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who eyes her knowingly.
BURLESQUE_DVS235
The club owner affords a slight nod.
BURLESQUE_DVS236
Now SOMEONE rubs her hands over her head and body, then points her knees in.
BURLESQUE_DVS237
SOMEONE softly shakes his head to himself. As SOMEONE leans forward and pouts her full lips, SOMEONE's cool gaze hardens even more. Onstage, SOMEONE prances, paws out, and grins adorably.
BURLESQUE_DVS238
SOMEONE remains watchful.
BURLESQUE_DVS239
A smiling SOMEONE points her knees and pops out her hands, then swings her arms, shakes her hips, and whips her hair back.
BURLESQUE_DVS240
SOMEONE smiles. SOMEONE glares. SOMEONE folds his hands.
BURLESQUE_DVS241
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE claps.
BURLESQUE_DVS242
SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave.
BURLESQUE_DVS243
SOMEONE joins the excited young woman onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS244
A delighted SOMEONE approaches, clapping.
BURLESQUE_DVS245
He nods.
BURLESQUE_DVS246
SOMEONE gives a silent scream.
BURLESQUE_DVS247
As she runs off, SOMEONE wears a muted smile. Now at the costume rack.
BURLESQUE_DVS249
A golden SOMEONE gun.
BURLESQUE_DVS250
It blasts him with gold confetti.
BURLESQUE_DVS251
He eyes her flatly and she forces a grin.
BURLESQUE_DVS252
Now SOMEONE struts confidently among pedestrians outside.
BURLESQUE_DVS253
At the club, she rehearses with the girls at the end of the line.
BURLESQUE_DVS254
Back with the pedestrians, she practices a move.
BURLESQUE_DVS255
In rehearsal, the dancers bounce, bop their heads, and gyrate their hips. On a sidewalk, SOMEONE practices the routine.
BURLESQUE_DVS256
The rehearsing dancers spin. Then SOMEONE spins on the street and resumes her walk.
BURLESQUE_DVS257
Onstage, a spotlight sweeps across the costumed girls.
BURLESQUE_DVS258
We cut from their routine to SOMEONE strolling down another street.
BURLESQUE_DVS259
She flourishes her wrist and gives a satisfied smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS260
In a performance, the dancers frolic downstage, SOMEONE among them. The newest dancer runs her hands through her hair and shakes her hips. The view veers to SOMEONE backstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS261
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE perform.
BURLESQUE_DVS262
The girls leave the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS263
Later in the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS264
As SOMEONE pulls on her sweater, the other dancers head out of the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS265
She slings her bag over her shoulder,
BURLESQUE_DVS266
then turns and sees the group disappearing down a staircase without her.
BURLESQUE_DVS267
With a heavy look,
BURLESQUE_DVS268
SOMEONE drops her bag back on the floor and plops into her chair at the dressing table.
BURLESQUE_DVS269
Resting her chin on her fist, she gazes at a black-and-white photo stuck to her mirror.
BURLESQUE_DVS270
It shows a glamorous burlesque dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS271
SOMEONE's eyes shift to her makeup,
BURLESQUE_DVS272
then return to the photo.
BURLESQUE_DVS273
She picks up a thin makeup brush.
BURLESQUE_DVS274
As SOMEONE nears the dressing room,
BURLESQUE_DVS275
she stops in the doorway and watches as SOMEONE tries to paint on eyeliner.
BURLESQUE_DVS276
The blonde pushes her eyelashes up with a brush
BURLESQUE_DVS277
and flinches.
BURLESQUE_DVS278
SOMEONE moves beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS279
returns her gaze to the mirror and lifts the brush to her lashes again.
BURLESQUE_DVS280
SOMEONE unzips a pouch and withdraws a brush.
BURLESQUE_DVS281
She holds it out to SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS282
As SOMEONE starts up again,
BURLESQUE_DVS283
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS284
She sits beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS285
She paints black lines along SOMEONE's eyelid.
BURLESQUE_DVS286
She applies color to SOMEONE's lids.
BURLESQUE_DVS287
SOMEONE grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS288
SOMEONE uses a large soft brush to apply rouge to SOMEONE's cheeks.
BURLESQUE_DVS289
She playfully taps SOMEONE's nose with the bristles.
BURLESQUE_DVS290
Holding SOMEONE' gaze, SOMEONE gives a mild shrug.
BURLESQUE_DVS291
With a faint smile, SOMEONE uses another brush to paint lipstick onto SOMEONE's parted lips.
BURLESQUE_DVS292
SOMEONE averts her eyes. As she stares off,
BURLESQUE_DVS293
SOMEONE skillfully finishes painting her lips.
BURLESQUE_DVS295
she gently tilts SOMEONE's face and examines her handiwork.
BURLESQUE_DVS296
SOMEONE turns to the mirror and sees her red lips and painted eyelids.
BURLESQUE_DVS297
Tilting her head back and forth, she touches her face.
BURLESQUE_DVS298
Now SOMEONE reaches out of the shower and finds bras and stockings hanging on a hook.
BURLESQUE_DVS299
He turns to a towel rack where more undergarments hang.
BURLESQUE_DVS300
He spots his towel on the floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS301
SOMEONE sleeps in the living room.
BURLESQUE_DVS302
He picks up a newspaper.
BURLESQUE_DVS303
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE grabs his phone off the bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS304
He swings the bedroom door shut.
BURLESQUE_DVS305
Later SOMEONE reads a housing ad in the newspaper.
BURLESQUE_DVS306
SOMEONE comes out.
BURLESQUE_DVS307
SOMEONE bites her thumb.
BURLESQUE_DVS308
pulls on his shirt.
BURLESQUE_DVS309
He takes the newspaper from her.
BURLESQUE_DVS310
She snatches the paper back.
BURLESQUE_DVS311
She backs into his bedroom and closes the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS313
At the lounge, a bartender carries crates of glasses and the band rehearses. SOMEONE storms out of SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS314
SOMEONE pauses from organizing costumes on a rack and watches SOMEONE stalk away.
BURLESQUE_DVS315
In her office, SOMEONE folds a piece of paper into an airplane.
BURLESQUE_DVS316
As she smooths the final crease, creating its wings,
BURLESQUE_DVS317
SOMEONE enters.
BURLESQUE_DVS318
SOMEONE tosses her paper plane at him.
BURLESQUE_DVS319
The backstage manager's gaze follows it as it lands on the floor at his feet.
BURLESQUE_DVS320
He picks it up and unfolds it.
BURLESQUE_DVS321
SOMEONE crumples the paper.
BURLESQUE_DVS322
Averting his gaze, SOMEONE shakes his head.
BURLESQUE_DVS323
SOMEONE lifts his chin.
BURLESQUE_DVS324
He bows his head.
BURLESQUE_DVS325
He locks his eyes with SOMEONE' desperate gaze, then moves forward to the couch where she sits.
BURLESQUE_DVS326
He sits beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS327
He wraps his arms around her and she rests her head on his shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS328
He pats her arm.
BURLESQUE_DVS329
Later in the crowded lounge, SOMEONE plays piano with the band.
BURLESQUE_DVS330
As the dancers get ready backstage, SOMEONE descends the staircase with a drink in her hand.
BURLESQUE_DVS331
Wearing a skimpy biker-themed costume, she heads toward the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS332
SOMEONE sniffs the drink.
BURLESQUE_DVS333
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS334
SOMEONE throws up her hands.
BURLESQUE_DVS335
SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE a costume. Meanwhile, SOMEONE enters the sound booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS336
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE leave, then moves to his soundboard. Onstage, a spotlight shines on Coco.
BURLESQUE_DVS337
The light shines on another dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS338
As the red spotlight fixes on SOMEONE for her turn to lip-sync, SOMEONE pulls a plug.
BURLESQUE_DVS339
SOMEONE stops dancing and gazes across the lounge toward the sound booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS340
SOMEONE gives a satisfied smile. Meanwhile, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE backstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS341
Onstage, SOMEONE sees the curtain descending. The doorman eyes departing patrons.
BURLESQUE_DVS342
SOMEONE tentatively steps to the front of the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS343
As the curtain continues to drop, she opens her mouth.
BURLESQUE_DVS344
SOMEONE, the doorman, and SOMEONE stare.
BURLESQUE_DVS345
The curtain freezes above SOMEONE's head.
BURLESQUE_DVS346
SOMEONE moves closer. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare, awestruck.
BURLESQUE_DVS347
The stagehand pulls a rope and the curtain rises back to the ceiling.
BURLESQUE_DVS348
A stagehand swivels a spotlight onto SOMEONE. As the band joins her, she struts toward the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS349
Dancing, she swings her hips from side to side. SOMEONE smiles and shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS350
Audience members bop their heads and shimmy their shoulders. SOMEONE grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS351
SOMEONE tips her biker cap.
BURLESQUE_DVS352
The crowd claps and the two dancers behind SOMEONE sing backup as they step from side to side. SOMEONE glares down at them. SOMEONE beckons the backup dancers and they join her downstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS353
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange a disbelieving look.
BURLESQUE_DVS354
SOMEONE grabs a musician out of the band and pulls him onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS355
Dancing around her, he plays the tambourine.
BURLESQUE_DVS356
SOMEONE strikes a pose with her arms in the air and the stage lights blink off.
BURLESQUE_DVS357
As Coco hugs SOMEONE, the crowd rises in a standing ovation.
BURLESQUE_DVS358
SOMEONE storms out of the sound booth with a sour expression.
BURLESQUE_DVS359
A spotlight fades up onstage and the bartenders, including SOMEONE, clap for the performers.
BURLESQUE_DVS360
SOMEONE's backup dancers push her forward.
BURLESQUE_DVS361
She curtsies, then bows with the others.
BURLESQUE_DVS362
The curtain falls.
BURLESQUE_DVS363
Backstage, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the other dancers crowd around.
BURLESQUE_DVS364
SOMEONE looks on.
BURLESQUE_DVS365
SOMEONE's jaw drops. SOMEONE gives her dancers a thumbs up, then turns to SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS366
SOMEONE glares at her.
BURLESQUE_DVS367
With a smile, SOMEONE strides away. SOMEONE juts out her chin.
BURLESQUE_DVS368
As the dancers disperse, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS369
He heads away, passing SOMEONE, who stares at SOMEONE, her arms crossed.
BURLESQUE_DVS370
She smiles.
BURLESQUE_DVS371
She turns away with a conniving smirk.
BURLESQUE_DVS372
Now SOMEONE exits the backstage area and finds SOMEONE waiting for her.
BURLESQUE_DVS373
Grinning, he claps.
BURLESQUE_DVS374
SOMEONE nods as she walks off.
BURLESQUE_DVS375
After hours, SOMEONE and the other dancers hang out at the bar with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS376
SOMEONE gets up. Coco looks at SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS377
SOMEONE shifts her gaze from Coco to another dancer, who nods.
BURLESQUE_DVS378
SOMEONE stares after her as she leaves with them.
BURLESQUE_DVS379
He pretends to think.
BURLESQUE_DVS380
As SOMEONE grabs her stuff, SOMEONE self-consciously looks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS381
With a smile, SOMEONE cocks his head.
BURLESQUE_DVS382
SOMEONE moves to his side.
BURLESQUE_DVS383
He points to a mirror.
BURLESQUE_DVS384
He sweeps her hair up.
BURLESQUE_DVS385
She gives the bald man a playful nudge. Now a light rises on SOMEONE in a platinum bobbed wig.
BURLESQUE_DVS386
She rises from the chaise lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS387
SOMEONE watches dreamily.
BURLESQUE_DVS388
She tugs on a gold rope.
BURLESQUE_DVS389
As the curtain rises, SOMEONE resumes his work.
BURLESQUE_DVS390
SOMEONE makes her way up some stairs, toward a platform. She tosses her head and shoulders back with each beat, then wiggles her hips at the crowd.
BURLESQUE_DVS391
Bending forward, she shakes her rear and the feathers on her short skirt flutter.
BURLESQUE_DVS392
She sits on a step and kicks her feet in the air.
BURLESQUE_DVS393
Facing the audience, she quickly spreads her knees, then crosses her legs. She dances up the rest of the stairs to the platform where another curtain opens, revealing more dancers.
BURLESQUE_DVS394
Now SOMEONE dances on the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS395
As a glass slides toward her, she kicks it out of the way. She struts to the wall of mirrored panels behind the bar and strikes a pose. As she pushes on one panel, it spins and she disappears behind it.
BURLESQUE_DVS396
A different panel spins and SOMEONE rotates into the room, then whirls away again.
BURLESQUE_DVS397
All of the panels turn with dancers in front of each.
BURLESQUE_DVS398
A bartender leans forward,
BURLESQUE_DVS399
bridging the wall and the bar with his back.
BURLESQUE_DVS400
Two others lead SOMEONE across.
BURLESQUE_DVS401
She swoons backwards off the bar. Two bartenders catch her and carry her to the chaise lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS402
She pretends to take a shot.
BURLESQUE_DVS403
The stage lights turn off.
BURLESQUE_DVS404
Later as SOMEONE works behind the bar, SOMEONE appears, still in her short sequined dress and platinum blonde wig.
BURLESQUE_DVS405
SOMEONE gives her a sidelong look.
BURLESQUE_DVS406
She spins on her stool.
BURLESQUE_DVS407
Her smile fades and she walks away. SOMEONE stares after her.
BURLESQUE_DVS409
SOMEONE struggles to uncap a spray bottle.
BURLESQUE_DVS410
SOMEONE easily removes the cap, then leans closer.
BURLESQUE_DVS411
SOMEONE gapes as SOMEONE strides away.
BURLESQUE_DVS412
In the lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS413
SOMEONE sets drinks on Marcus' table and sits across from him.
BURLESQUE_DVS415
at SOMEONE's place.
BURLESQUE_DVS416
Coming home, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE in the bedroom, wearing only pink panties and a matching bra.
BURLESQUE_DVS417
He steps further into the apartment,
BURLESQUE_DVS418
his mesmerized gaze fixed on her curves.
BURLESQUE_DVS419
His bag topples candles on the coffee table.
BURLESQUE_DVS420
He returns to the door.
BURLESQUE_DVS421
SOMEONE joins her at a mirror and zips up her dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS422
He notices SOMEONE's photo.
BURLESQUE_DVS424
SOMEONE glances up at him with a winsome pout.
BURLESQUE_DVS425
SOMEONE smiles warmly as she holds his gaze.
BURLESQUE_DVS426
Grinning boyishly, he steps away.
BURLESQUE_DVS427
SOMEONE's smile fades.
BURLESQUE_DVS428
Now feather fans lift away to reveal SOMEONE reclined on the lounge piano, in a skimpy two-piece outfit made of pearls.
BURLESQUE_DVS429
She pushes the pianist's head past her lap, then shimmies her pearls.
BURLESQUE_DVS430
At home, SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a comfortable laugh in the living room.
BURLESQUE_DVS431
At the lounge, SOMEONE pops a champagne bottle's cork and smirks.
BURLESQUE_DVS432
At a table, SOMEONE thoughtfully rubs his chin as he watches her.
BURLESQUE_DVS433
Now as she rides with SOMEONE on his motorcycle, her sheer scarf flies away.
BURLESQUE_DVS434
As SOMEONE puts her back to the audience, her top flies off.
BURLESQUE_DVS435
A dancer hands her a fan and she covers her chest. Turning away, she lowers the fan and shimmies.
BURLESQUE_DVS436
Quickly covering herself, she faces the crowd again.
BURLESQUE_DVS437
Her pearl briefs fly off. She snatches another fan from a dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS438
Now SOMEONE hurries into the dressing room with a giddy smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS439
She shows an engagement ring. The girls rush to hug her.
BURLESQUE_DVS440
Back onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS441
Peeking out from behind a fan, she comically blows feathers and hair out of her face.
BURLESQUE_DVS442
Now SOMEONE blows out birthday candles. Standing apart, SOMEONE snaps a photo, then smiles and winks at her.
BURLESQUE_DVS443
SOMEONE gazes tenderly at him.
BURLESQUE_DVS444
Onstage, she shimmies her fans.
BURLESQUE_DVS445
As she flings them away, her backup dancers raise two more in their place.
BURLESQUE_DVS446
They part the fans, revealing her naked form.
BURLESQUE_DVS447
A pair of bongos cover her breasts and a candle conceals her crotch.
BURLESQUE_DVS448
SOMEONE winks. Later she meets SOMEONE at the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS449
He stares, slack-jawed.
BURLESQUE_DVS450
SOMEONE carries a crate of glasses away.
BURLESQUE_DVS451
SOMEONE arrives at SOMEONE's side.
BURLESQUE_DVS452
He grabs her bag.
BURLESQUE_DVS453
Later SOMEONE rides in a vintage convertible speedster as SOMEONE drives.
BURLESQUE_DVS454
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS455
The speedster makes a turn.
BURLESQUE_DVS456
Later it pulls up outside a glamorous party.
BURLESQUE_DVS457
Primping, SOMEONE takes her hair down.
BURLESQUE_DVS458
As she and SOMEONE enter, several trendy upscale guests take notice.
BURLESQUE_DVS459
He takes her into a kitchen staffed with caterers and grabs one of the many bottles of wine.
BURLESQUE_DVS460
He takes two glasses and a tray of hors d'oeuvres.
BURLESQUE_DVS461
Leading her downstairs, he meets two guests.,
BURLESQUE_DVS462
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE onward.
BURLESQUE_DVS463
She halts in a doorway.
BURLESQUE_DVS464
A city view.
BURLESQUE_DVS465
SOMEONE gives her a smirk and sips his wine.
BURLESQUE_DVS466
Turning away, SOMEONE sips her wine with a cynical smirk.
BURLESQUE_DVS467
Now SOMEONE lies on the daybed with his eyes closed.
BURLESQUE_DVS468
His eyes open as SOMEONE arrives home.
BURLESQUE_DVS469
Now a gift box sits on a dressing-room stool.
BURLESQUE_DVS470
SOMEONE reads the card: To the best view in LA - SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS471
As the other girls look on, she opens the present and pulls out a pair of Louboutin shoes just like SOMEONE's.
BURLESQUE_DVS472
SOMEONE marches over and grabs the card.
BURLESQUE_DVS473
As she reads it, her smirk fades.
BURLESQUE_DVS474
SOMEONE leaves.
BURLESQUE_DVS475
Facing her mirror, SOMEONE dons a bowler hat.
BURLESQUE_DVS476
Now with the stage set to resemble the dressing room, SOMEONE and the dancers mime preparations for a show.
BURLESQUE_DVS477
The fake mirrors whisk upstage and three more dancers crawl out of them to simple wooden chairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS478
SOMEONE and the first two dancers pose erotically in their own chairs and snap their fingers.
BURLESQUE_DVS479
A dance begins.
BURLESQUE_DVS481
SOMEONE watches from his corner table.
BURLESQUE_DVS482
At home, SOMEONE adds notations to sheet music, then stares thoughtfully at it. SOMEONE arrives.
BURLESQUE_DVS483
As she removes her coat, he shakes his head and smiles.
BURLESQUE_DVS484
He notices her Louboutins.
BURLESQUE_DVS485
He watches from his keyboard as she walks into the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS487
her costume bears two handprints on her buttocks.
BURLESQUE_DVS488
SOMEONE works her hands up her body to her hair. Her backup dancers move upside-down on their chairs in acrobatic positions. At home, SOMEONE struts in her sparkly four-inch Louboutins as she puts on the new outfit.
BURLESQUE_DVS489
She leaves. Onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS492
At the entrance, a long line appears.
BURLESQUE_DVS493
Back inside the packed lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS494
Looking on, SOMEONE smiles proudly.
BURLESQUE_DVS495
SOMEONE lifts her knee in a sexy pose with one of her backup dancers. SOMEONE seethes as she watches.
BURLESQUE_DVS496
Mesmerized by the performance, SOMEONE interlaces his fingers.
BURLESQUE_DVS497
Now he drives SOMEONE in his vintage convertible.
BURLESQUE_DVS498
At his home, they share an intimate laugh as they sit on the couch by candlelight.
BURLESQUE_DVS499
Back in the lounge, the dancers advance downstage, reaching their hands toward the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS500
SOMEONE turns in profile and bumps her shoulders forward into an animalistic slouch.
BURLESQUE_DVS501
Spreading their legs, the dancers bend over and whip their hair.
BURLESQUE_DVS502
At home, SOMEONE finds a note taped to a mirror written on sheet music paper: Going out. See you tomorrow - SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS503
Back onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS504
SOMEONE and the others dance with precision and raw sensuality as the stage lights strobe.
BURLESQUE_DVS505
Now a makeup mirror reflects a newspaper photo of SOMEONE performing in the burlesque lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS506
SOMEONE smiles in her office as she reads the article on the front page of the LA Times Calendar section.
BURLESQUE_DVS507
The photo shows SOMEONE with Coco and another dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS508
SOMEONE sets down the paper and picks up a bank letter headed, Notice of Defaulted Payment. A red stamp reads, Final Notice.
BURLESQUE_DVS509
SOMEONE crumples it up.
BURLESQUE_DVS510
In the dressing room, the girls huddle around the newspaper feature.
BURLESQUE_DVS511
Coco faces SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS512
Meanwhile, two contortionists lie with their chins to the stage. Posed in deep backbends, they flick their toes over their heads. The doorman crouches between them.
BURLESQUE_DVS513
They scissor kick.
BURLESQUE_DVS514
One does a handstand and wraps her thighs around the doorman. The other sticks her leg straight up along his back.
BURLESQUE_DVS515
At Marcus' table.
BURLESQUE_DVS516
SOMEONE arrives.
BURLESQUE_DVS517
The doorman falls face-first into a contortionist's crotch.
BURLESQUE_DVS518
A patron spits out his drink with laughter.
BURLESQUE_DVS519
From the bar, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch SOMEONE with the two men.
BURLESQUE_DVS520
One of the contortionists passes the doorman a banana between her legs. He peels it, then gets distracted by her breasts, and lowers the phallic fruit to his crotch.
BURLESQUE_DVS521
The other contortionist deep-throats it.
BURLESQUE_DVS522
From a table overlooking the crowd, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE with SOMEONE and Harold.
BURLESQUE_DVS523
SOMEONE arrives at her side.
BURLESQUE_DVS524
One contortionist spreads her legs overhead and the doorman strikes a triangle between her thighs. Now in the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS525
She picks up her clutch purse.
BURLESQUE_DVS526
SOMEONE gives an affectionate smile as SOMEONE walks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS527
She bites her lip worriedly.
BURLESQUE_DVS528
SOMEONE brings costumes.
BURLESQUE_DVS529
SOMEONE glances after SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS530
He kisses SOMEONE' cheek.
BURLESQUE_DVS531
She watches him go with a grateful smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS532
Now she enters the stage area, her arms loaded with costumes.
BURLESQUE_DVS533
SOMEONE calls out from the deejay booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS534
She drops the costumes, then removes her
BURLESQUE_DVS535
coat, revealing a black sparkling top with a matching cardigan and pants.
BURLESQUE_DVS536
She climbs wearily onto the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS537
SOMEONE puts on a CD labeled, Instrumental Only, Last of Me.
BURLESQUE_DVS538
He cuts the stage lights.
BURLESQUE_DVS539
SOMEONE places a chair center stage and straddles it.
BURLESQUE_DVS540
SOMEONE focuses a blue-tinted spotlight on her.
BURLESQUE_DVS541
Silhouetted by an offstage light, she strolls away stoically.
BURLESQUE_DVS542
SOMEONE gazes after her with a small admiring nod, then switches off the spotlight.
BURLESQUE_DVS543
SOMEONE steps outside with
BURLESQUE_DVS544
costumes and heads down the entrance stairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS545
SOMEONE waits for her at the bottom.
BURLESQUE_DVS546
Wearing fingerless leather gloves, she takes a drag off a cigarette.
BURLESQUE_DVS548
SOMEONE gets in a convertible and wrestles her bag down beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS549
SOMEONE gives an incredulous stare. As SOMEONE backs out of her spot, her old mentor tosses her keys down onto her car's trunk.
BURLESQUE_DVS550
SOMEONE takes out a crowbar and smashes SOMEONE's passenger window as she drives past. The car stops abruptly.
BURLESQUE_DVS551
With an indignant gape, she peels off. SOMEONE flings the crowbar back into her trunk then turns and leans on the bumper.
BURLESQUE_DVS552
Now SOMEONE arrives home in a red clingy dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS553
Eyeing the daybed, she pauses briefly, then crosses to the French doors and opens them.
BURLESQUE_DVS554
She finds SOMEONE sleeping in the bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS555
SOMEONE rolls her eyes resentfully and pulls the doors shut.
BURLESQUE_DVS556
Now in their apartment, SOMEONE irritably grinds coffee. SOMEONE stirs awake in the red cocktail dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS557
He shuts the bedroom doors. She flings a pillow at a lamp.
BURLESQUE_DVS558
Now at a wedding.
BURLESQUE_DVS559
SOMEONE kisses Damon.
BURLESQUE_DVS560
Later at the reception, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE talk on his cell phone.
BURLESQUE_DVS561
With his eyes on SOMEONE, he lowers the phone. Now SOMEONE sits with Coco.
BURLESQUE_DVS562
As SOMEONE sips his drink, the deejay grins at him.
BURLESQUE_DVS563
At a bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS564
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance.
BURLESQUE_DVS565
He hugs her from behind.
BURLESQUE_DVS566
He kisses her cheek.
BURLESQUE_DVS567
Now leaning on the bar, SOMEONE sips the last of a cocktail. SOMEONE approaches and leans on the bar beside him.
BURLESQUE_DVS568
She ignores his toast.
BURLESQUE_DVS569
SOMEONE giggles, then downs her shot.
BURLESQUE_DVS570
SOMEONE nudges her with his elbow and leans in close.
BURLESQUE_DVS571
He points at the deejay, who points back. As SOMEONE leaves the bar, SOMEONE grabs her hand.
BURLESQUE_DVS572
They face each other on the dance floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS573
He grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS574
They dance.
BURLESQUE_DVS575
He spins her.
BURLESQUE_DVS577
As they enter the darkened apartment, SOMEONE knocks over a lamp.
BURLESQUE_DVS578
He bumps the lamp again.
BURLESQUE_DVS579
SOMEONE looks demurely up at him from the daybed. SOMEONE smiles genteelly.
BURLESQUE_DVS580
He hands SOMEONE her shoes.
BURLESQUE_DVS581
SOMEONE steps into the bedroom and shuts the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS582
A disappointed SOMEONE glances after him.
BURLESQUE_DVS583
He reopens the doors, wearing bright red pajamas.
BURLESQUE_DVS584
He flourishes his arms.
BURLESQUE_DVS585
She watches him cross back to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS586
He shuts the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS587
He reopens the doors, shirtless.
BURLESQUE_DVS588
As he enters the kitchen, she admires his toned back on the sly.
BURLESQUE_DVS589
As he returns to the bedroom, she checks him out again.
BURLESQUE_DVS590
SOMEONE spins around in the doorway and SOMEONE shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS591
SOMEONE removes her earrings, her back to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS592
SOMEONE reemerges naked.
BURLESQUE_DVS593
A chair, then a lamp conveniently hide his groin.
BURLESQUE_DVS594
SOMEONE still has her back to him.
BURLESQUE_DVS595
SOMEONE sees his bare tush.
BURLESQUE_DVS596
She covers her eyes, but peeks.
BURLESQUE_DVS597
He innocently holds a box of Famous Amos cookies over his privates.
BURLESQUE_DVS598
He returns to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS599
He shuts the French doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS600
As SOMEONE looks over her shoulder, the bedroom lights go out.
BURLESQUE_DVS601
She lowers her disappointed gaze and purses her lips, then gets up from the daybed.
BURLESQUE_DVS602
Reaching behind her back, she goes to unzip her dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS604
SOMEONE reopens the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS605
With a smoldering gaze, he steps out of the bedroom and approaches SOMEONE, then gently brushes her long blonde hair off her shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS606
He kisses her smooth neck and they share a peck on the lips.
BURLESQUE_DVS610
Facing each other, SOMEONE runs his fingers through her hair. They kiss again.
BURLESQUE_DVS611
They gaze into each other's eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS614
Daytime. In bed, SOMEONE rests her head on SOMEONE's chest.
BURLESQUE_DVS615
Pouring rain streaks their bedroom window.
BURLESQUE_DVS616
Onstage, SOMEONE sings in a satiny chartreuse gown.
BURLESQUE_DVS617
The image dissolves from SOMEONE onstage to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS618
SOMEONE lies in bed with a camera as SOMEONE pulls a black stocking over her knee.
BURLESQUE_DVS619
She pulls the stocking back down her leg, then bites her bottom lip.
BURLESQUE_DVS620
SOMEONE beckons.
BURLESQUE_DVS621
Onstage, SOMEONE sings to a full house.
BURLESQUE_DVS622
They lounge in bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS623
They embrace.
BURLESQUE_DVS624
Back onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS625
Silhouetted against a brilliant spotlight, SOMEONE closes her hands and gently lowers her arms.
BURLESQUE_DVS626
Now a young woman enters the apartment.
BURLESQUE_DVS627
She sets down a suitcase and tosses aside her keys. Scanning the living room, she finds an article of clothing.
BURLESQUE_DVS628
She barges into the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS629
She shoves past him.
BURLESQUE_DVS630
Now SOMEONE's wedding deejay opens a front door.
BURLESQUE_DVS631
In SOMEONE's bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS632
SOMEONE looks up from his bed and they smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS633
Wearing only a blanket, SOMEONE covers up.
BURLESQUE_DVS634
In the kitchen, SOMEONE makes coffee.
BURLESQUE_DVS635
SOMEONE sighs and lowers a spoon.
BURLESQUE_DVS636
Now at Jacks apartment. SOMEONE leaves with her luggage.
BURLESQUE_DVS637
Later at SOMEONE's second floor apartment, SOMEONE steps outside.
BURLESQUE_DVS638
SOMEONE pulls into the driveway on his motorcycle.
BURLESQUE_DVS639
SOMEONE passes the deejay on his way upstairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS640
He heads off.
BURLESQUE_DVS641
SOMEONE looks pointedly after SOMEONE walking to his car.
BURLESQUE_DVS642
SOMEONE turns.
BURLESQUE_DVS643
Now in SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS645
SOMEONE heads for the door.
BURLESQUE_DVS646
Now at Marcus' contemporary three-story mansion, SOMEONE walks up a staircase to the top floor and its breathtaking view of the city.
BURLESQUE_DVS647
She looks out a window and spots SOMEONE pacing outside on his phone.
BURLESQUE_DVS648
She leaves the window and regards an architectural model of a city block set up on a table.
BURLESQUE_DVS649
SOMEONE notes an address on the model:
BURLESQUE_DVS650
8080 Sunset Boulevard.
BURLESQUE_DVS651
SOMEONE joins her and hands her a coffee mug.
BURLESQUE_DVS652
She grabs her jacket.
BURLESQUE_DVS653
She walks out and leaves SOMEONE standing alone.
BURLESQUE_DVS654
Now we descend to the lit-up sign for the Burlesque Lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS655
Inside SOMEONE crosses a dim hallway adorned with memorabilia.
BURLESQUE_DVS656
She stops and takes a second long look at a red neon sign which reads, The Best View on the Sunset Strip.
BURLESQUE_DVS657
SOMEONE hurries on.
BURLESQUE_DVS658
Onstage, dancers move in unison while the seated band performs.
BURLESQUE_DVS659
In the dressing room, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS660
She holds up a bottle of tequila.
BURLESQUE_DVS661
SOMEONE enters SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS662
SOMEONE lowers her gaze, then looks up and gives an amused roll of the eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS663
Onstage, the dancers finish their number to the delight of a packed house.
BURLESQUE_DVS664
Now SOMEONE chats with SOMEONE as they exit the lounge, passing under its unlit archway.
BURLESQUE_DVS665
They head across the street to the high-rise of luxury condos. Inside, a white-haired man sits at a desk, talking on the phone.
BURLESQUE_DVS666
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter his office.
BURLESQUE_DVS667
As he hangs up, the women sit.
BURLESQUE_DVS668
He gives SOMEONE a brochure.
BURLESQUE_DVS669
The white-haired businessman gives a confused look.
BURLESQUE_DVS671
The lights on the lounge's archway glow onto the sidewalk.
BURLESQUE_DVS672
Inside the club, SOMEONE strolls up to SOMEONE, who sits at a table looking through a stack of paperwork.
BURLESQUE_DVS673
She takes a seat across from him.
BURLESQUE_DVS674
Smiling, she drops an envelope in front of him.
BURLESQUE_DVS675
He opens it and finds a check for $500,000.
BURLESQUE_DVS676
He stares at her with wide eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS677
She glances skyward.
BURLESQUE_DVS678
He shakes his head at the check.
BURLESQUE_DVS679
He gives her a nod and she presses her lips to his.
BURLESQUE_DVS680
Pulling away, she eyes him.
BURLESQUE_DVS681
As she leaves, SOMEONE's lips curl into a smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS682
Meanwhile, SOMEONE chats with a bartender.
BURLESQUE_DVS683
SOMEONE strolls up to the bar and leans her back against it.
BURLESQUE_DVS684
SOMEONE swivels her stool to face the same direction.
BURLESQUE_DVS685
They share a grin and SOMEONE good-naturedly smacks SOMEONE's leg.
BURLESQUE_DVS686
Entering the lounge, SOMEONE spots them.
BURLESQUE_DVS687
The women's smiles fade as they notice her.
BURLESQUE_DVS688
As she approaches SOMEONE, SOMEONE turns back to the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS689
SOMEONE hangs her head, then lifts her tearful gaze.
BURLESQUE_DVS690
She gives SOMEONE an earnest look.
BURLESQUE_DVS691
The club owner replies with a gentle smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS692
SOMEONE beams.
BURLESQUE_DVS693
With a nod, SOMEONE hurries off.
BURLESQUE_DVS694
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS695
She puts her head on SOMEONE' shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS696
She hops off her stool and walks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS697
SOMEONE stares after her.
BURLESQUE_DVS698
With a serene look, she turns away and sips from a glass of dessert wine.
BURLESQUE_DVS699
SOMEONE approaches and leans beside her on the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS700
He heads away, leaving SOMEONE at the bar with a faint smile on her lips and a faraway look.
BURLESQUE_DVS701
Meanwhile, SOMEONE climbs the stairs to the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS702
She sets down her bag, removes her jacket, and sits at her vanity table.
BURLESQUE_DVS703
Behind her, SOMEONE combs her hair, her eyes fixed on the blonde.
BURLESQUE_DVS704
SOMEONE lifts a brush to her eyes then spots her rival in the reflection of her mirror.
BURLESQUE_DVS705
She gives SOMEONE a cordial nod.
BURLESQUE_DVS706
With her lips pursed in a haughty expression, the diva looks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS707
The corner of SOMEONE's mouth twitches in a thoughtful smirk as she continues to watch SOMEONE in the mirror,
BURLESQUE_DVS708
then returns to her makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS709
then lowers her gaze, her lips curling into a genial smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS710
The brunette shoots her another look,
BURLESQUE_DVS711
As she stares off dreamily, another dancer reaches for her makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS712
SOMEONE slaps her hands away, her jaw dropping in exasperation.
BURLESQUE_DVS713
SOMEONE smiles as she watches in her mirror, then touches up her mascara.
BURLESQUE_DVS714
SOMEONE appears in a doorway.
BURLESQUE_DVS715
SOMEONE lowers her mascara brush as she sees him.
BURLESQUE_DVS716
SOMEONE moves closer.
BURLESQUE_DVS717
He gives a pleading look.
BURLESQUE_DVS718
SOMEONE avoids his gaze.
BURLESQUE_DVS719
He gently lifts her chin.
BURLESQUE_DVS720
He stares into her pale-blue eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS721
With her head tilted, SOMEONE shifts her gaze over his face.
BURLESQUE_DVS723
he opens his mouth to speak,
BURLESQUE_DVS724
then closes it again.
BURLESQUE_DVS725
His face scrunches up as he gives a charming grin.
BURLESQUE_DVS726
Glancing away, SOMEONE bites her lip.
BURLESQUE_DVS727
He leans in and they kiss. SOMEONE presses her hands to his toned chest, then wraps her arms around his neck.
BURLESQUE_DVS728
He clutches her shoulders, returning the embrace.
BURLESQUE_DVS729
They part and SOMEONE slides her hands back down his chest as he presses his lips to her
BURLESQUE_DVS731
He moves in to kiss her again, then pulls back with a smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS732
He steps away.
BURLESQUE_DVS733
He grins widely.
BURLESQUE_DVS734
Heading for the door, he pauses.
BURLESQUE_DVS735
He walks back to her and hands her some sheet music.
BURLESQUE_DVS736
The title reads, Show Me How You Burlesque, by SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS737
Now on a dark stage, a spotlight shines down on SOMEONE, who wears a sparkling outfit and her platinum wig.
BURLESQUE_DVS738
Strobe lights flash and giant block letters spelling Burlesque light up onstage. As the other dancers grind against the letters, SOMEONE sits atop the E at the center.
BURLESQUE_DVS739
More girls dance on tables in the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS741
The dancers on the tables swing their arms and flip their hair. The stage performers mirror them. With a smile, the doorman bobs his head. SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch proudly from the balcony. Onstage, the dancers pump their chests.
BURLESQUE_DVS742
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sing backup from atop the bar. More dancers strut out from the revolving mirrored panels behind them. Another girl tickles the doorman's lips and he smiles. An outline of red neon flashes around the letters onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS743
The dancers on the bar fall back into the arms of the bartenders, who carry them to the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS744
All of the girls cluster together, with SOMEONE at the center.
BURLESQUE_DVS745
They each strike a pose, coolly snapping their fingers.
BURLESQUE_DVS746
Several bartenders run onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS747
They surround SOMEONE and grind their hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS748
The women sit on some steps in front of her.
BURLESQUE_DVS749
The male and female dancers now stand staggered on the staircase, moving in unison.
BURLESQUE_DVS750
As they shake their butts at the audience, SOMEONE imitates them and SOMEONE grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS751
The dancers hop from foot to foot, their hands beckoning the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS752
The stage lights flash and the dancers disappear, leaving only the glowing letters. Remaining opening titles: Dianna Agron,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS25
The bare-chested soldier watches the students halt at the end of the SOMEONE. A live young woman with wavy, corn silk hair, sets her purse on the railing.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS26
A boyish guy sits on the railings, sending her purse plunging into the water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS27
As SOMEONE jogs up the SOMEONE toward the beach, the soldier jumps off the railing and plummets 15 feet into the water. The blonde's jaw drops. Underwater, the soldier swims down along the SOMEONE's barnacled supports. The purse stirs in the current, on the SOMEONE strewn ocean floor. The soldier seizes it, then kicks off the bottom and shoots back to the surface.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS28
The soldier swims toward the beach.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS29
On the sand, SOMEONE kicks off his flip-flops, and trots into the water, meeting the soldier in the surf.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS30
The soldier delivers it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS31
The smiling woman shakes her drenched bag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS32
SOMEONE ambles off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS33
SOMEONE halts and walks back toward them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS34
He grabs his surfboard.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS35
As SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, he accidentally bangs his board on the SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS36
They head off side by side.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS37
The setting sun casts long shadows over the sand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS38
Dear SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS39
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE Porter, and SOMEONE Jenkins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS40
Now a date appears. Spring 2001.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS41
Guests mill about a SOMEONE beach house's natural un-landscaped yard. SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in an unlit fire pit.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS42
SOMEONE notices a bulky ring on SOMEONE's finger.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS43
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a beer.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS44
SOMEONE mimes throwing punches.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS45
SOMEONE eyes him, coolly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS46
SOMEONE salutes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS47
He leaves.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS48
SOMEONE hangs his head with a subdued smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS49
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE candidly. Then allows a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS50
He looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS51
A tow-headed boy hugs her from behind.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS52
The young boy beams.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS53
SOMEONE peers downward.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS54
A bearded man joins them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS55
SOMEONE plays with some driftwood.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS56
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS57
SOMEONE climbs over a log bench, and heads off with his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS58
He looks over his shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS59
SOMEONE gapes, and SOMEONE gives a stunned smirk. SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit back down.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS60
SOMEONE drops his gaze, and SOMEONE studies him with a warm smile. They lock eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS62
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ramble toward the water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS63
They halt among tufted beach grass, and gaze up at the moon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS64
As he demonstrates, she copies him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS65
She covers the moon with her thumb.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS66
SOMEONE watches enviously from the fire pit.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS67
Later, SOMEONE whacks a striker bar against a magnesium strip key-chain, instantly igniting a small campfire.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS69
Holding a hotdog on a stick, SOMEONE grins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS70
SOMEONE bashfully glances at the fire and turns away. Then faces SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS71
She nods, beaming.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS72
He missteps, almost tripping into the fire. Then affects a cool recovery.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS73
Later, SOMEONE hobbles down a deserted road in his flip-flops, carrying his surfboard under one arm.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS74
A pickup slows beside him. It's SOMEONE. SOMEONE ride shotgun.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS75
He stumbles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS76
SOMEONE loads his board into the bed of the truck. Later they drive.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS77
SOMEONE points at SOMEONE with a nod.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS78
SOMEONE sways capriciously and tickles the men's necks. Now the truck stops before a modest home with a bushy tree in the front yard. SOMEONE climbs out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS79
SOMEONE heads off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS80
He carries his board toward the house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS81
Now, SOMEONE opens the front door and enters a room veiled in shadow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS82
In a study, a balding man wearing a single white glove examines a coin under a magnifying glass. SOMEONE lifts the edge of a window shade covering the room's French door, and peeks inside at his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS83
The oblivious man's gaze remains locked on his coin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS84
SOMEONE lets go of the shade and walks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS85
His father glances over his shoulder, then stares off glumly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS86
SOMEONE heads into his room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS88
Outside, laundry whips on a line in the wind.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS89
In the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS90
SOMEONE's father purses his lips into a thoughtful frown, and digs in his pocket. He pulls out a set of keys and hands them to SOMEONE, who ambles toward the door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS91
Later, a sign on a shabby seaside building reads, Bowens Island Restaurant.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS92
Loitering men spot SOMEONE and swap looks. A goateed guy speaks up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS93
SOMEONE inches over to him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS94
SOMEONE joins a puzzled SOMEONE a few steps ahead of him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS95
Later in the restaurant.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS96
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE blankly, and offers a fleeting grin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS97
She smiles back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS98
At twilight, two men fish on the dock outside the restaurant. Back inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS99
She smiles quizzically.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS100
He munches some food. Eyes the rosy-cheeked young woman, then shyly bows his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS101
SOMEONE locks her in his sudden sobered gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS102
Later, they stroll toward his front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS103
They head inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS104
SOMEONE's father looks up from his desk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS105
He stands to greet them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS106
She extends a hand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS107
He bashfully shakes it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS108
She notices a coin collection.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS109
He takes a coin from her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS110
He rubs it vigorously on his shirt. Then peers at her through his glasses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS111
He gives her a white cotton glove.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS112
He covers a wheel printed on the coin with a silver dollar.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS113
He brings out more.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS114
Now the SOMEONE family car pulls up in front of SOMEONE's house. Riding with SOMEONE, she beams.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS115
SOMEONE chews his pursed lips. Leaning over, SOMEONE gives him a kiss on the cheek. Then gets out of the car.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS116
SOMEONE grins at him and shuts the door. He happily gazes after her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS118
At the beach, SOMEONE paddles his surfboard out over the breaking waves. He crests one, then swims farther out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS119
Later, he paddles with a flow of a swelling wave, as its foaming crest reaches his board, he gets to his feet and surfs it until it breaks. Later, he sits straddling his board, gazing at the houses along the shore.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS120
Later still, he paddles out past a stone jetty.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS121
At her house, SOMEONE steps out on her screened-in porch, and gazes toward the beach.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS122
Now she walks with SOMEONE, as he carries his board from the water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS123
They stroll toward her home.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS124
Now they approach a partially constructed house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS126
Later, she leads him through the house's framework.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS127
It starts to rain.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS128
She leads him under a cluster of boards supported by a beam.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS129
They stand close together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS130
She strokes his eyebrow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS131
Looking away, SOMEONE works his mouth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS132
SOMEONE shrugs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS133
SOMEONE rests his cheek against the side of the beam.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS134
SOMEONE gazes tenderly at SOMEONE. He leans his face closer to her, and she smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS135
She lifts her chin and her nose brushes against his.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS136
Opening her mouth, she kisses him hungrily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS137
SOMEONE drapes her arms around his neck, as they passionately make out. He lifts her up, and she wraps her legs around him. As SOMEONE lowers himself to the floor, she straddles his lap.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS138
Now, as they walk down a sidewalk, SOMEONE clasps SOMEONE's hand to his chest. At the sun dappled construction site, SOMEONE arrives to find him working at the top of a ladder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS139
She stops, watching him appreciatively.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS140
He spots her, and they share a warm smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS141
Now, SOMEONE holds his surfboard, tucked under his arm as they trod into the ocean. Later a wet-suit clad SOMEONE, crouches low on the board as she awkwardly rides a wave.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS142
Tumbling into the shallow water, she grins. From the shore, her female friend pouts beside SOMEONE, who sullenly watches the couple. Trying another wave, SOMEONE manages to stand briefly as SOMEONE cheers her on.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS143
Now, she hugs his arm as they walk hand in hand past a cafe. At the SOMEONE house, the young couple enjoys a meal with SOMEONE's father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS144
Later, silhouetted by a dusky sky, SOMEONE frolics on the beach, playfully evading SOMEONE's grasp.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS145
He finally catches her in his arms. Lifts her and spins. At the construction site, the couple adds a plywood board to a wall. She swats her hand in front of him, as he hammers it in place.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS146
In a living room, SOMEONE sings and plays guitar for SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS147
In a hallway, SOMEONE sneaks up on her as she shuts a door. He turns her to face him, and they share a tender kiss.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS148
SOMEONE peeks around a corner.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS149
As his father paces in the living room, SOMEONE carries his girlfriend upstairs. Now they tumble unto his bed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS151
Mr. SOMEONE slows, blinking.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS152
He gives a startled turn, then stares off. His brow knitted.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS153
Upstairs SOMEONE rolls off the bed, then scrambles to a closet and shuts herself in.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS154
She pulls at the door knobs, but he yanks the doors open.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS155
Pouncing at her side, he tickles her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS156
As our view drifts upward, his armed uniform obscures them from view.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS157
Back in the living room, SOMEONE smiles as she plays the guitar.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS158
Reclining beside her, SOMEONE beams appreciatively.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS159
Now, tall reeds wave in a breeze as the young man hikes into view, and gazes ahead. On the beach, a small group plays volleyball amidst a boisterous party. Near a grill, SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS160
Another group sits around two young men playing acoustic guitars.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS161
SOMEONE hangs back, pensively taking in the cheerful scene.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS162
Turning, he spots a solitary figure sitting alone at the base of a grassy dune.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS163
At the volleyball net, SOMEONE pauses. He watches his rival cross to the dune, then turns back to his game.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS164
SOMEONE hikes along a grassy ridge towards SOMEONE, and sneaks down behind her. He playfully grabs her side, startling the live young beauty.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS165
She smiles contentedly in his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS166
SOMEONE lowers her troubled gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS167
Pulling her closer, SOMEONE kisses her brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS168
He rocks her in his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS169
Her lips creep into a faint smile, and he kisses her brow again.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS170
Turning, SOMEONE wraps her arms around him and lays him back against the dune.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS171
Later, they stroll toward the party.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS172
SOMEONE trots ahead a few paces and bends to pick up a seashell. As she straightens and pockets it, SOMEONE drapes a loving arm around her shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS173
He stops and faces her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS174
SOMEONE lowers her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS175
SOMEONE starts to speak, then turns away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS176
He sulks off, leaving his girlfriend behind.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS177
Reaching the party, he heads up a boardwalk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS178
SOMEONE tosses him a can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS179
SOMEONE chucks it aside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS180
SOMEONE pulls him aside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS181
He touches SOMEONE's chest. The soldier flings him to the ground. His buddy runs over, and SOMEONE punches him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS182
SOMEONE rushes up behind the soldier. SOMEONE elbows him in the face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS183
Glaring lividly, SOMEONE smacks his arm. SOMEONE faces her briefly, then leaves. SOMEONE cups a hand over his nose.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS184
SOMEONE crouches to him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS185
At dusk, SOMEONE hikes along a dirt road. His feature obscured by shadow. An SUV rounds a turn, pulls up beside him, and continues on.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS186
Silhouetted against the gray sky, SOMEONE bows his head. His stride unbroken.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS188
Daytime, SOMEONE stands on SOMEONE's porch, knocking on the screen door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS189
In the next yard, SOMEONE takes out the trash, sporting a black eye and a swollen nose.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS190
SOMEONE approaches him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS191
SOMEONE shrugs his hand and steps forward.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS192
Getting a look at his face, SOMEONE slows.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS193
SOMEONE fishes a scrap of paper from the trash bin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS194
SOMEONE meets the kind man who hands him the paper with a pen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS195
SOMEONE nods, and steps away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS196
Now an oven door opens, revealing two pans of lasagna.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS197
A pair of hands and oven mitts take them out and sets them on a stove. SOMEONE wanders into the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS198
SOMEONE shuffles into the dining room. His father closes the oven door, crosses to an island counter and watches him. The young man clears one of three place settings from the dining room table. Taking it into the kitchen, he sets the plate, place mat and glass on the island. His father looks on as he starts to put the silverware away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS199
SOMEONE puts the silverware back down.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS200
As he steps away, Mr. SOMEONE methodically sets the silverware aside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS201
He picks up the plate in both hands. Sets it at a precise angle in a wooden case, and slides a glass door close in front of it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS202
Later, we watch through a doorway, as father and son eat at the dining room table. SOMEONE gazes off as he chews, then looks down at his plate.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS203
His father picks at his food.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS204
SOMEONE watches him with a concerned expression.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS205
With a melancholy stare, Mr. SOMEONE scoops a large fork full of lasagna into his mouth and chews.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS206
He turns, facing a window. SOMEONE follows his gaze to find SOMEONE's car pulling up outside. Standing, he leaves the table.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS207
He goes outside and jogs down off the porch. Getting out of her car, SOMEONE faces him with an affectionate smirk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS208
They embrace.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS209
He caresses her corn silk hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS210
He kisses her smooth forehead.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS211
She warps her arms around him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS212
She gives him an envelope and he starts to open it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS213
He drapes an arm around her shoulder and she hugs his waist as they head inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS214
Now they eat dinner with SOMEONE's father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS215
Later as SOMEONE sits in her car, SOMEONE leans through the window and playfully grapples with her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS216
She turns her face toward his and kisses him. In the house, Mr. SOMEONE looks up from his coins. A window shows SOMEONE's car pulling away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS217
SOMEONE gazes after her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS218
His image recedes as she drives away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS219
With glistening eyes, SOMEONE watches him through her rear-view mirror.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS220
She tearfully looks away, and watches the road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS221
Now at a bus station.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS222
He takes two bags from his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS223
The young man boards a waiting bus.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS224
Its long side window shows Mr. SOMEONE lingering on the spot, staring off as he stuffs his hands into his pockets. The bus pulls away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS225
On the bus, SOMEONE reads SOMEONE's letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS226
Now amongst sleeping soldiers, SOMEONE reads by flashlight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS227
Daytime at an airfield.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS228
The soldiers file off a plane in their camouflaged uniforms. Each carrying a duffel.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS229
SOMEONE exits the aircraft, squinting in the sun and proceeds across the tarmac.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS231
He eyes one of his peers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS232
The dark-haired soldier stares defeatedly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS233
Their mustached superior leaves. SOMEONE lowers his gaze. At dusk, the platoon crosses the airfield and climbs the boarding steps of a cargo plane. On board, SOMEONE writes a letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS234
Now a helicopter descends. SOMEONE rides on board among the others.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS235
He gazes at passing trees.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS236
The soldiers hop out of the landed chopper, one by one. Now they enter a crude village where a calf drinks from ruts of sitting water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS237
He hands a letter to a pilot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS238
SOMEONE watches the helicopter take off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS239
Now multiple letters travel along four conveyor belts. One of them addressed to SOMEONE Curtis. Letters flip vertically through a machine. A bin of bundled letters slides down a track, and a postal worker sorts the letters into cubbies. On a college campus, a mailman takes a few letters from his satchel and places them into one of many PO boxes. From inside the PO box, we see SOMEONE take out her mail.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS240
On finding SOMEONE's letter, she smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS241
She reads on her way to class. SOMEONE instructs African troops.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS242
In a lecture, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE reading.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS243
SOMEONE's dark-haired buddy goes through the newly receive mail.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS244
SOMEONE reads.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS245
Now, African women play drums and dance. Soldiers walk among merchants set up along a dirt road. A soldier in sunglasses chats with two local men. Another soldier exits a house and pats SOMEONE, who sits on a porch reading.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS246
SOMEONE leaves a horse and runs across the front yard to greet SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS247
She picks him up and twirls.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS248
Now they ride horses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS252
She grins at the boy.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS253
Leaning on a fence, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch SOMEONE feed a horse.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS254
SOMEONE writes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS255
SOMEONE reads attentively. Nighttime in a tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS256
SOMEONE grabs the letter from him. Now SOMEONE receives another.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS257
She gazes at the moon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS258
She covers the moon with her thumb.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS259
Her cheeks flushed. She holds her gaze steady.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS260
Now at Mr. SOMEONE's house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS261
He hesitates at the door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS262
He retrieves a small case from a lower drawer.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS263
Then takes out a coin, which he holds under a magnifying glass.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS264
Flipping the nickel over, he reveals the back of a penny.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS265
He glances around the desk, and finds another coin. SOMEONE smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS266
Riding in the bed of a transport truck, SOMEONE reads "What's the story?".
DEAR_JOHN_DVS268
He stares off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS269
In a flashback, a boy receives a handful of change from an ice-cream vendor.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS270
Leaving the van, the boy studies his change.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS271
Young SOMEONE licks his ice-cream cone.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS272
Later his dad's fingers rinse the peculiar coin under the faucet.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS273
In the kitchen, a younger Mr. SOMEONE studies the coin and shakes his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS274
He glances at the boy.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS275
Now at a pawn shop.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS276
SOMEONE brightens, his grin missing a couple baby teeth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS277
Mr. SOMEONE collects the coin and tugs his son away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS278
Mr. SOMEONE hurries down a sidewalk and briefly stops for SOMEONE to catch up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS279
In another store.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS280
The clerk sets the coin on a square napkin. Bends down and digs under his counter to retrieve a pamphlet titled, The Four Thousand Dollar Mule.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS281
Mr. SOMEONE looks at his son.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS282
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS283
The clerk grins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS284
Now at another coin shop.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS285
They view coins on display.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS286
We tour a collection.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS287
Now older SOMEONE takes milk out of the fridge.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS288
He drinks from the carton.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS289
He tosses the carton back inside and shuts the door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS290
His father opens the door and stands the carton upright.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS291
Now Mr. SOMEONE studies a coin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS292
SOMEONE goes to a stereo in the living room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS293
His father looks up from a coin. Seen distantly through the doorway, SOMEONE leaves the stereo and walks out of sight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS294
His dad glances over his shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS295
On campus, a passing student bumps into SOMEONE as she reads. At the bottom of a staircase, she reaches a walkway where frantic peers gather and talk on cellphones. A confused SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's letter with both hands as she observes the anxious activity.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS296
As SOMEONE remains frozen, our view is sent to take in a bird's eye view of the chaos. Now wearing plain clothes, SOMEONE walks alone on a busy street in an eastern European town. A horse-drawn cart, a woman on a bicycle, and a man on a scooter crosses path. SOMEONE approaches a cafe, where pedestrians gather outside. Reaching the entrance, SOMEONE joins his dark-haired buddy to watch television news coverage. Black smoke billows from one of New York City's Twin Towers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS297
SOMEONE breathes heavily as he watches SOMEONE falling off the building.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS298
Fade to black.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS299
Now in a hanger, the soldier’s superior approaches.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS300
SOMEONE packs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS301
SOMEONE's friend rises.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS302
SOMEONE, the only one left seated, lowers his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS303
Later in a conference room, he shakes hands with two soldiers then grabs his bag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS304
He eyes his dark-haired friend.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS305
Now a gray cargo plane lands on an airstrip.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS306
Inside a crowded airport, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE on the other side of a security gate.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS307
She ducks under a dividing rope, and hurries around to the other side. SOMEONE notices her and beams. She runs to him and leaps into his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS308
As he spins her around, they kiss.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS309
A heavy-set traveler eyes them as he takes off his belt.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS310
Another man eyes them, holding out his arms for a guard.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS311
Later while SOMEONE drives, SOMEONE raises her free hand to his lips. He rubs her hand with his chin, then she strokes the back of his head, fondle his ear, and caresses his cheek.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS312
SOMEONE brushes her long blonde hair behind her shoulder. As he gazes at her, thumbing her hair around her ear, she meets his gaze and smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS313
Now, outside his father's house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS314
They approach the front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS315
Inside, Mr. SOMEONE sits on a chair and buttons a suit jacket.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS316
Behind him, the front door opens, and the couple enters.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS317
SOMEONE walks off, then returns to the sitting room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS319
They follow him into the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS320
He takes out the pan.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS321
Now Mr. SOMEONE sits in the back seat of SOMEONE's blue Volkswagen, as they drive away. On a country road, he nervously stares at the foiled wrapped meatloaf nestled in a cardboard box on his lap.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS323
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE. Mr. SOMEONE squeezes his brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS324
Grimacing, he grabs at the door. SOMEONE reaches back. The car stops and Mr. SOMEONE gets out. A disheartened SOMEONE remains in the passenger seat, and rests his elbow on the window sill.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS325
Mr. SOMEONE slouches at the side of the road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS326
She touches his back, and he walks off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS327
He walks a few paces away, then halts and hunches forward, catching his breath.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS328
Now at the SOMEONE house, they get out of the car.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS329
Mr. SOMEONE goes to the front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS330
His father pauses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS331
He enters the house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS332
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, rolls his eyes, then returns to the car.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS333
Later on the road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS334
SOMEONE meets her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS335
They both stare ahead somberly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS336
Now SOMEONE's car pulls onto a private road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS337
A stylish brunette woman in a white dress, crosses the front porch of a colonial plantation home, and greets arriving guests as she passes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS338
She hugs SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS339
Well over a dozen cars sit parked on the front lawn. Inside, guests mingle over drinks and hor d'oeuvres.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS340
SOMEONE offers his hand. SOMEONE ignores him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS341
SOMEONE returns and offers SOMEONE a drink.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS342
SOMEONE takes the drink and averts his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS343
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS344
A cigar-smoking man approaches SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS345
As her father leaves, SOMEONE joins them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS346
A blonde woman joins them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS347
The woman and SOMEONE leave.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS348
The boy collects hor d'oeuvres on a plate.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS349
SOMEONE looks around self-consciously.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS350
SOMEONE sips his bourbon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS351
SOMEONE nods and glances off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS352
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS353
SOMEONE eyes him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS354
SOMEONE deflates.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS355
Now on the porch, SOMEONE paces behind SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS356
She leans on the railing, gazing out over the lawn as departing guests find their cars. He stands behind her, and she lowers her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS357
She flinches and shifts away from him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS358
SOMEONE bows his head and faces her from the side.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS359
She looks at him ascant, then faces him fully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS360
She grimaces, agonizing and SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS361
She storms past him and disappears down the front steps, leaving him alone on the porch. SOMEONE watches her go, then swallows hard and hangs his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS362
Now as guests stroll around the Curtis' expansive grounds, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE siting alone on a bench overlooking a marsh. His pace slows as he draws closer.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS363
He gazes out at the wetlands as he waits a few feet away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS364
SOMEONE clasps SOMEONE's head in her hands, then wraps her arms around his neck and pulls him into a tight embrace. She rests her chin on his shoulder as he holds her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS365
She meets his gaze, then draws his face closer and kisses his forehead.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS366
Leading him by the hand, SOMEONE takes SOMEONE to her family's stables. Inside, she leans back against a wall as she unbuttons his dress shirt.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS367
He caresses her hair, then lovingly kisses her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS368
Dim blue light outlines SOMEONE's corn silk hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS369
SOMEONE nuzzles the top of her head, as he sweeps her long blonde locks behind her back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS370
She parts his shirt, and slips it off his shoulders. Then wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him hungrily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS371
As SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's neck, she lowers her dress and presses her body against his.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS372
Now, SOMEONE's toned upper body hovers above SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS373
Propped up by his arms, as she pulls his undershirt over his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS374
She then removes her bra.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS375
He lowers himself on top of her, and meets her lips with a passionate kiss.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS376
The muscles in his shoulders ripple as he and SOMEONE make love.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS377
He kisses her shoulder, then trails his lips from the tip of her chin, down her neck, and gently caresses her hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS379
He lies beside her, his arm reaching across her body, to stroke her corn silk tresses with his fingertips.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS380
They kiss sweetly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS381
She stares distantly. Her hand clasping SOMEONE's smooth freckled shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS383
With a wistful look, she closes her eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS384
A tear slides out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS385
Glistening in the light.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS386
And rests at the corner of her eye.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS387
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands as they stroll outside the stable into the daylight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS388
SOMEONE carries her heels, and she wears his jacket over her dress.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS389
A wider view shows warm sunlight glinting through Spanish moss on a tree, as the couple embraces in front of the stables.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS390
Now wearing his fatigues, SOMEONE enters the airport with SOMEONE by his side.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS391
He spots his father waiting at a security checkpoint.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS392
As the couple draws closer, a grin crosses SOMEONE's face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS393
Mr. SOMEONE smiles briefly, but avoids his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS394
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who grins at Mr. SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS395
SOMEONE shares a quick look with SOMEONE, who turns away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS396
He faces his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS397
They exchange smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS398
Mr. SOMEONE shifts his gaze uneasily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS399
SOMEONE extends his hand. With his eyes averted, Mr. SOMEONE shakes it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS400
The soldier awkwardly watches his father, then turns to SOMEONE, who waits a few steps away. As she faces SOMEONE, Mr. SOMEONE walks past them and exits the airport. SOMEONE bends down and wraps his arms around SOMEONE's waist.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS401
They embrace tightly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS402
SOMEONE straightens.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS403
Clasping his neck, SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE, then rests her forehead against his.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS404
He lifts his lips and kisses the top of her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS405
She looks up at him, tearfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS406
Tears shine in her red rimmed eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS407
The corner of SOMEONE's mouth twitches into a tiny smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS408
He and SOMEONE kiss desperately.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS409
She cups SOMEONE's face in her hands as she kisses him one last time, then turns away and strides out of the airport.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS410
SOMEONE clenches his jaw as he watches her leave.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS411
Outside, she glances over her shoulder and smiles at him, then continues away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS412
Now in a military plane, SOMEONE lies on some cargo netting as it takes off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS413
Later in the hanger on base.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS414
The captain observes his men.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS415
Sitting on a crate, SOMEONE furrows his brow thoughtfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS416
He rises and stands at attention, joining the rest of his team.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS417
The captain nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS418
As the captain heads off, our bird's eye view of his men swings down to watch them collect their belongings.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS419
Now, an image of SOMEONE's address handwritten on an envelope, drifts into view.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS420
In Afghanistan, SOMEONE patrols a bustling street.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS421
He pauses to talk to a young boy.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS422
In a close-up of SOMEONE's letter, we glimpse fragments of sentences.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS424
Just not the same without you. Rises and sets for both of us, is what helps me survive day to day. Love SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS426
In a college classroom SOMEONE writes thoughtfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS427
A close-up shows her pen gracefully filling a page with elegant cursive.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS428
Back in Afghanistan, a pallet drops from a plane, and a parachute opens above it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS429
Later, two soldiers approach the fallen crate. SOMEONE heads over and receives a mailbag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS430
At the army camp, he distributes letters to soldiers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS431
With a letter in his hand, SOMEONE sits on a cot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS432
Now, a close-up shows a smooth cursive signature. Always SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS434
SOMEONE drops some letters on top of others in a metal box. Then closes the lid. He kicks it under his cot as he begins to write a reply on a pad of paper. In Charleston, SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride horses together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS435
Back in Afghanistan, SOMEONE trains another soldier.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS437
The soldier fires at a target.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS438
SOMEONE pats him on the back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS439
Close-ups of a pen show him writing the dates on more letters to SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS440
June, September, December.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS441
In Charleston, moonlight shines across SOMEONE's face as she lies awake in bed. Our view of the moon morphs into the blazing sun.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS442
In Afghanistan, SOMEONE riffles through a pile of letters. With a disappointed look, he turns away from the mailbag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS443
Now he cleans a gun.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS444
Glancing up, he notices a soldier reclined on a cot, and reading a letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS445
In Charleston, SOMEONE sits alone on the beach. She closes her eyes regretfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS446
In Afghanistan, SOMEONE's dark-haired buddy, passes him with a mailbag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS447
SOMEONE hangs his head as the soldier walks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS448
Now, SOMEONE cautiously glances around as he steps into a tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS449
He finds a cellphone on a desk, and reaches for it. Sitting down, he dials, then lifts the phone to his ear.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS450
Now dust billows as a bundled pallet parachutes to the ground. Later, a soldier opens a mailbag and searches its contents.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS451
Now, SOMEONE's dark-haired buddy carries a letter in one hand, and the mailbag in the other, as he enters the fenced-in base camp.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS452
Passing a group of soldiers playing football, he approaches other lounging on picnic tables outside a tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS453
He heads into the tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS454
SOMEONE sits at a weight machine.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS455
He hands SOMEONE the thin envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS456
SOMEONE thoughtfully runs his thumb over it. Gauging its weight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS457
Later, he sits outside and reads the letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS458
SOMEONE trudges into his tent with the letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS459
He sits on his cot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS460
SOMEONE glances at the other soldiers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS461
He lowers his miserable gaze to the handwritten pages.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS462
SOMEONE lifts his head into the sunlight, and bites his lip resolutely.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS463
Reaching under his cot,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS464
he extracts the metal box and carries it outside. As he pries off its cover, he fumbles it, and it falls to the ground.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS465
As SOMEONE retrieves his spilled letters, a soldier passes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS466
Now, flames dance inside a trash can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS467
SOMEONE tosses a stack of letters onto the fire. As he adds more from his box, his dark-haired buddy walks up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS468
Clenching his jaw, SOMEONE shakes his head, as he continues to toss letters into the flames. His friend eyes him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS470
SOMEONE dumps the remainder of the box into the trash can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS471
He heads off, leaving SOMEONE staring at the fire.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS472
Later, a convoy of military vehicles trundles down a dirt road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS473
Dust churns from their wheels. A Humvee passes a man leading a camel and maneuvers unto a busier road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS474
SOMEONE rides inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS475
A man runs in front of their Humvee with his arms raised over his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS476
The Humvee stops, and the soldiers climb out with their guns drawn.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS477
SOMEONE heads away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS478
SOMEONE's dark-haired friend joins him. With their guns at the ready, they creep around the parameter of a decrepit factory.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS479
The captain gestures to the rest of the team. Meanwhile, SOMEONE and Noodles round the corner of a deteriorating cement wall. Noodles glances at SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS480
A man on a balcony shoots Noodles. SOMEONE fires back, then talks into his radio.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS481
He grabs Noodles by the vest and drags him out of harm’s way. Then inspects the soldier's chest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS482
SOMEONE extracts a bullet from Noodles' tactical vest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS483
As SOMEONE helps Noodles stand, four bullets rip through him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS484
SOMEONE falls back in slow motion.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS485
Soldiers fire at his shooter, who collapses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS486
Kneeling beside SOMEONE, Noodles props him against a wall.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS487
SOMEONE's vision blurs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS488
SOMEONE glances drowsily at Noodles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS489
He gently slaps SOMEONE's cheek.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS490
Our view of the soldiers tilts upside down, then drifts to the ground.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS492
Now pale light shines through Venetian blinds, as SOMEONE lies in a bed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS493
A hand adjusts the slats on the blinds and bright sunlight pours into the room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS494
SOMEONE's head shifts, and his hazy vision finds a nurse at his bedside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS495
She smiles down at the groggy soldier.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS496
As helooks at the nurse's kind expression, SOMEONE's vision gets blurrier, and he closes his eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS497
Fade to black.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS498
Now, SOMEONE sits on the side of his bed, with his arm in a sling. Struggling, he manages to lift the strap over his head. He drops the sling on the floor.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS499
Eyeing his reflection in a mirror, he unsnaps the top of his hospital gown, to reveal his bandaged shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS500
He winces as he tears the tape and gauze from his skin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS502
As SOMEONE slips one arm into a t-shirt, sunlight gleams on the scarred flesh of two bullet wounds on his back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS503
Later, he straightens the collar of his army fatigues. Standing in front of the mirror in his uniform, he pulls his belt tight around his waist.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS504
Now, he enters a military building, and turns down a hallway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS505
He finds the captain writing at a desk in his office.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS506
The captain looks up, as SOMEONE walks in.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS507
SOMEONE doesn't budge.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS508
He sullenly lowers himself into a chair, across from the captain.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS509
The captain grins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS510
SOMEONE holds the captain's gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS511
Now, a helicopter sweeps over a desert.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS512
Inside, SOMEONE shifts his gaze away from the open side door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS513
Now, a smoke grenade billows on an Afghan street, as soldier’s race across it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS514
SOMEONE searches an abandon building, his gun drawn.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS515
Outside of a village, three explosions burst from the ground.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS516
SOMEONE leads a group of soldiers down a rocky hill.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS517
He directs his team as they race away from a hut.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS518
It explodes and flames shoot into the sky.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS519
Now, words appear. Special forces base, Qatar.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS521
SOMEONE strolls into his room, and reclines on his bed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS522
A soldier stops in the doorway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS523
SOMEONE sits up with an alarmed look.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS524
He lowers his gaze from the soldier.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS525
Now, he stares out an airplane window. His eyes narrowing as sunlight rises across his face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS526
Later in a hospital hallway, SOMEONE watches his father through a window.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS527
Tubes trail from Mr. SOMEONE's mouth to a nearby ventilator.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS528
A doctor stops beside SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS529
SOMEONE bows his head slightly and nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS531
Wearing his army uniform, and carrying two bags, SOMEONE mounts the steps to his dad's house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS532
He sets one bag down, opens the screen door and heads inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS533
Dim light bathes his face as he steps into the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS534
Dirty dishes, bottles, and jars clutter the counter top and stove.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS535
SOMEONE's haunted stare holds steady on the mess.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS537
He treads down a hall to his father's shadowy study, and lingers in the doorway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS538
Now, he pulls open a drawer and finds a jumble of dozens of coins in small boxes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS539
He takes out a blue velvet box and opens it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS540
With a sober stare, he turns over the Jefferson Mule in his fingers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS541
Seated at his father's desk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS542
He lifts his head and gazes out a window.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS543
SOMEONE sets the coin aside, and takes out a blank sheet of paper.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS544
He lays it on the desk, then takes a pen from a holder and writes the word, Dear in the upper left hand corner.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS545
Now in the hospital, SOMEONE strides up to his father's room. But finds his bed empty.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS546
He glances around, uneasily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS547
Doctors and nurses bustle past.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS548
His brow furrowed, SOMEONE spots a cot in the corridor, and strides toward it to find his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS549
The ailing man wears an oxygen mask. An IV bag hangs above his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS550
A doctor reading a file, continues on her way.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS551
Mr. SOMEONE gives a weary blink.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS552
SOMEONE stares at him uncomfortably.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS553
He takes an envelope from his back pocket.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS555
Glides his finger along its edge, then reluctantly hands it to his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS556
Mr. SOMEONE lifts the flap.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS559
With palsied hands, Mr. SOMEONE closes the envelope’s flap, and tucks the letter against the side of his body.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS560
SOMEONE sways awkwardly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS561
He scoots a wheeled stool over, and takes a seat.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS562
As doctors and nurses stride past, he slides the letter out of the envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS563
His father watches through heavy lidded eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS564
His ailing father offers a series of slow nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS565
Mr. SOMEONE gazes at his son tenderly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS566
His right hand trembles against his chest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS567
SOMEONE's smoothly shaven jaw quivers as his eyes remain locked on his letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS568
He resolutely shakes his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS569
His father limply raises one hand and rests it against SOMEONE's shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS570
As it slides off, SOMEONE catches it, and lovingly touches his chin to his father's frail fingers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS571
Mr. SOMEONE pulls his hand away and places his palm against SOMEONE's cheek.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS572
SOMEONE holds it in place with his own hand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS573
Sliding his father's hand to cup the back of his neck.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS574
SOMEONE hunches down and hides his face in the crook of the man's frail arm.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS575
Mr. SOMEONE raises his other hand to his son.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS576
The soldier lifts his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS577
And his father strokes his short hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS578
SOMEONE gently collapses unto the man's chest. And the coin collector cradles him as best he can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS579
Now, as misty rain pours down on an otherwise empty beach.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS580
SOMEONE sits beside his surfboard with his knees pulled up, and his head bowed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS582
Later, lying belly down on his surfboard, he paddles out in the steel gray sea.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS583
Cloudy rain sheets down, as the waves buck and toss beneath him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS584
He swings his legs into the water, and drops his unhooked ankle leash onto his board.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS585
Releasing his grip on the board.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS586
He lets himself drift away from it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS587
As he floats on his back,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS588
a foamy wave breaks nearby.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS589
Water laps at his face, and flows over his mouth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS590
His head sinks beneath the surface and he vanishes. His board gently bobs on the waves.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS591
A few feet under water, SOMEONE hovers vertically. His arms raised limply over his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS592
Bubbles stream out of his mouth, as he tips his head back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS593
Later, still submerged, the grieving son buries his face in his hands. Then runs his fingers back into his hair, and covers his eyes with his palms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS595
SOMEONE sits alone in a vacant church. A coffin stands in front of the alter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS596
A pastor creeps in.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS597
The pastor nods, sympathetically.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS598
Then glances at the coffin and paces out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS599
Wearing his dress uniform, SOMEONE stares off beneath his knitted brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS600
His gaze shifts and he blinks sadly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS601
The pastor disappears through a doorway, leaving SOMEONE alone once again.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS602
Now, the soldier drives his car with a stoic frown.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS603
The images of passing trees reflect faintly on his windshield.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS604
The car pulls through the gate of SOMEONE's family home. And follows the winding drive around a knarled tree.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS605
Slowing, the car pulls up alongside the corral beside the modest stables.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS606
Inside, SOMEONE's slender long-legged silhouette stands, petting a horse.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS607
SOMEONE stops the car and takes out his keys.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS608
Her features lost in shadows, SOMEONE looks toward him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS609
SOMEONE gets out and faces the stables. Nervously pursing his lips.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS610
SOMEONE quickly locks the horse into its stall.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS611
Her form still silhouetted against the stables rear open doorway. SOMEONE treads towards SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS612
He moves across the corral.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS613
His mouth twitches uneasily above his neatly pressed uniform shirt.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS614
The shadows hiding SOMEONE's face fade, as she steps outside into the gentle sunlight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS615
It bathes her doe-like eyes and rosy cheeks.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS616
SOMEONE moves faster.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS617
A pain smile fades from his former lover's rosebud lips. She halts.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS618
SOMEONE continues toward her, then stops a few yards away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS619
SOMEONE's corn silk hair lies captured in a tight braid, and she wears slim-fitting breaches and riding boots. She allows a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS620
A brief grin flickers over the corner of his mouth, as he stares at SOMEONE intensely.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS621
Gazing back at him, she summons a deep breath.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS622
SOMEONE uncomfortably shoves a hand into his pocket. His lips parting sadly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS623
SOMEONE swallows, dropping his gaze, then shakes his head and locks eyes with SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS624
Her jaw drops.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS625
She clutches both hands to her mouth and arches her brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS626
She studies SOMEONE sympathetically.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS627
He bows his head and shifts awkwardly from foot to foot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS628
He reads a sign above the barn door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS629
She forces a smile and gives a high shrug.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS630
SOMEONE lowers his stare and swallows. Swaying on his feet. Then looks back up at her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS631
She tearfully meets his gaze before glancing away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS632
SOMEONE offers a faint nod.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS633
Later in SOMEONE's dining room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS634
SOMEONE nods, then sorrowfully shakes her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS635
SOMEONE stares down at the table.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS636
Smiling, SOMEONE drops his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS637
SOMEONE offers a candid grin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS638
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS639
She hurries away, and he idly looks around.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS640
The soldier gets up and ambles towards a mantle.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS641
Where several framed photographs stand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS642
SOMEONE glances at him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS643
She presses her lips together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS644
One photograph shows SOMEONE in a wedding dress.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS645
She poses with SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS646
SOMEONE stares at the wedding photo. His brow knit.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS647
SOMEONE summons a breath and eyes him uneasily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS648
SOMEONE swallows hard.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS649
In the photo, SOMEONE beams beside her bearded groom.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS650
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll through a sunny park.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS651
Later in a hospital, they head into an atrium.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS652
They find a beardless SOMEONE sitting in a wheelchair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS653
He musters a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS654
A teenage SOMEONE jogs up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS655
SOMEONE faces her husband.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS656
She kisses him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS657
SOMEONE skips off after SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS658
SOMEONE stands awkwardly in front of the cancer patient. Clasping his hands.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS659
SOMEONE takes a seat and the ailing father studies him wryly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS660
Nodding, the two men lock gazes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS661
SOMEONE earnestly lifts his brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS662
SOMEONE drops his eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS663
SOMEONE gives a long weary blink.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS664
The soldier's gaze drifts thoughtfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS665
SOMEONE stares off. His eyes bleary.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS666
SOMEONE tucks his lips into his mouth and bites them gently.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS667
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE as she stands with SOMEONE at a snack kiosk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS668
SOMEONE bows his head, avoiding SOMEONE's gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS669
The patient's lips twitch into a wincing smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS670
SOMEONE's eyes remain downcast.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS671
He lifts his head and glances at SOMEONE, blinking pensively.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS672
Later, SOMEONE's SUV parks in front of her plantation style home.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS673
SOMEONE gets out and races away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS674
SOMEONE and SOMEONE linger in the vehicle. Their seat-belts fastened.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS675
SOMEONE unbuckles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS676
SOMEONE shakes her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS677
Staring off despondently.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS678
SOMEONE tightens her rosebud lips, then locks eyes with her former lover.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS679
SOMEONE manages a smile and looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS681
In a dining room, SOMEONE pours herself a glass of wine.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS682
SOMEONE glowers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS683
She uncomfortably shifts her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS684
As SOMEONE studies her inscrutably out of the corner of his eye, she rubs her lips together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS685
Her wounded smile fades, and she looks to the ceiling.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS686
SOMEONE taps his fork against his plate and sets it down.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS687
SOMEONE stares with doe-like eyes, then lowers her dark lashes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS688
SOMEONE glares, shifting his jaw.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS689
His mouth opens as if to speak.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS690
But he shuts it and looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS691
He shakes his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS692
His intense gaze grows tearful.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS693
SOMEONE hangs her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS694
Bobbing it equivocatingly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS695
She stares at the table.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS696
She looks up imploringly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS697
SOMEONE gapes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS698
SOMEONE rises and starts out of the room, then whirls around.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS699
SOMEONE pulls her into his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS700
She buries her face against his chest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS701
Cupping SOMEONE's head in his hand, he gently rocks her back and forth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS702
Later in the sitting room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS703
She removes a rubber band from a stack of SOMEONE's letters.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS704
He takes an envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS705
SOMEONE slides out the letter inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS706
It reads, I love you, SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS707
As she reaches for the stack of letters, she knocks over a glass of wine.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS708
Liquid drips from SOMEONE's sleeve.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS709
SOMEONE unbuttons his wet sleeve as he heads into a bathroom.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS710
Behind him, SOMEONE stands just inside a bedroom with a door half open.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS711
She removes her blouse.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS712
As SOMEONE scrubs his sleeve, he glimpses a reflection of her bare back in the bathroom mirror.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS713
He eyes her longingly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS714
SOMEONE brushes her hair back and turns, catching SOMEONE's gaze in the mirror.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS715
The former lovers lock eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS716
SOMEONE turns away pulls a flannel shirt over her shoulders. SOMEONE bows his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS717
Now they head downstairs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS718
She heads into the kitchen, but SOMEONE strides past the doorway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS719
She glances back at him, then leans heavily on a counter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS720
In the hall, SOMEONE shifts his weight uneasily, then treads toward the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS721
As SOMEONE turns to face him, he halts in the doorway and stares at her resolutely. One hand shoved in his pocket.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS722
She tearfully locks eyes with him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS723
Clenching his jaw.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS724
He holds SOMEONE's gaze. Then turns from the doorway and strides off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS725
He walks into the dining room, and retrieves his jacket from the back of his chair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS726
SOMEONE joins him, her dark-lashed eyes blinking forlornly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS727
She looks to SOMEONE, then shyly shifts her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS728
He grinds his jaw as he watches her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS729
She beams at him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS730
SOMEONE looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS731
His gaze downcast, he backs away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS732
Then heads to the front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS733
He halts.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS734
SOMEONE stares at the floor.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS735
She takes a few steps toward him and raises her tearful eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS736
As SOMEONE turns, she lifts her brow expectantly and offers a faint smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS737
He meets her pleading stare, then bows his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS739
He opens the screen door and steps outside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS740
SOMEONE swallows, cringing as tears well in her eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS741
She shakes her head disbelievingly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS742
Outside, SOMEONE trudges to his car. His jacket slung over his shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS743
Inside, tears stream down SOMEONE's face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS745
SOMEONE's car trundles down the driveway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS746
Inside, SOMEONE rests his head against his hand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS747
Tears shine on his face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS748
His face seizes. His chin trembling.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS749
He rubs his brow, then pounds his hand on the steering wheel.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS751
He accidentally turns on his wipers and they glide across the windshield.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS752
He flips them off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS753
Later at his house, he stands in his father's study with his hands in his pockets.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS754
He thoughtfully eyes the boxes of coins stored under a glass counter. Then pulls them out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS755
Now at the Honest Coin dealer shop.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS756
Outside, SOMEONE opens his trunk to reveal the collection.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS757
Now in a desert, SOMEONE holds out his Jefferson Mule.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS758
SOMEONE flips the coin into the sand. The soldier inspects it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS759
As SOMEONE leads the group, a soldier approaches him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS760
He hands over an envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS761
SOMEONE studies the envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS762
Later, soldiers load cargo into vehicles as SOMEONE reads his letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS763
In a flashback, guests greet SOMEONE at a casual party.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS764
He laughs with SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS765
In another flashback, SOMEONE writes the letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS766
Nighttime, SOMEONE stands on her porch and gazes into the sky.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS767
Tears glisten in her eyes as she stares at the moon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS768
Now, SOMEONE wheels a bike down a busy street.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS769
He wears a button down shirt and a neatly trimmed goatee.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS770
A view through a cafe window shows SOMEONE seated at a table by herself.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS771
SOMEONE's reflection appears on an adjoining window, as he bends to lock his bike to a parking meter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS772
Inside, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS773
Noticing her, he does a double take,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS774
and they share a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS775
SOMEONE rises and heads outside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS776
Grinning, she wraps her arms around SOMEONE's neck.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS777
And blissfully closes her eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS778
SOMEONE holds her tightly. His face buried against her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS13
The teacher catches a boy with a joint.
EASY_A_DVS14
He offers a bong.
EASY_A_DVS15
She reaches for it, letting her breasts hang out.
EASY_A_DVS16
Friday afternoon, SOMEONE opens a greeting card that reads, "To my granddaughter, you're my pocket full of sunshine." She finds a $5 SOMEONE inside.
EASY_A_DVS17
Saturday morning, SOMEONE opens the card again.
EASY_A_DVS18
Painting her toenails, she sings to a dog on her bed, then paints the dog's nails.
EASY_A_DVS19
Saturday afternoon.
EASY_A_DVS20
Saturday night, SOMEONE kneels before her dog, shaking her hips. Sunday morning, SOMEONE repeatedly opens and shuts the card.
EASY_A_DVS21
Sunday afternoon, in the shower.
EASY_A_DVS23
She glances about, then shuts the card and joins the dog on her bed.
EASY_A_DVS24
In the ladies room.
EASY_A_DVS25
Another girl steps out of a stall and glares at SOMEONE, while washing her hands.
EASY_A_DVS26
She flicks water at SOMEONE, and leaves.
EASY_A_DVS27
SOMEONE passes out flyers.
EASY_A_DVS28
Last year.
EASY_A_DVS29
A guy in a devil costume tears through a banner, his face and bare chest painted blue. Launching off a trampoline, he flips and dunks a basketball then hangs from the hoop. He throws his toy pitchfork into the crowd.
EASY_A_DVS31
This year.
EASY_A_DVS32
A plush Woodchuck mascot rips through a banner with a wheelbarrow of logs. He pretends to gnaw on one.
EASY_A_DVS33
He launches off the trampoline for a dunk, but falls on his face.
EASY_A_DVS34
He shows a title.
EASY_A_DVS35
Our view dashes across the school grounds to a guy on a cellphone. We zip into a classroom where a few students read a text message. In a theater class, a guy checks his phone while lying on stage mid rehearsal.
EASY_A_DVS36
We zoom out the window, then zip around the building into another class. Where a girl turns to show a text to a friend at a desk behind her.
EASY_A_DVS37
The friend turns to a guy behind her, then we shoot outside past a row of lockers to find SOMEONE. The red-haired teen stands alone. Listening to the chatter.
EASY_A_DVS38
Turning to go, she runs into SOMEONE with a snooty friend.
EASY_A_DVS39
They pat their hearts and raise their hands to the sky.
EASY_A_DVS40
She rejoins SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS41
Now at home.
EASY_A_DVS42
A black boy sits beside her.
EASY_A_DVS43
At school her peers stare.
EASY_A_DVS44
SOMEONE's hand shoots up.
EASY_A_DVS45
She faces SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS46
Now SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE, from behind an administrative counter, while aggressively stapling a document.
EASY_A_DVS47
SOMEONE pounds on the stapler.
EASY_A_DVS48
An athletic team steps into view, followed by a smaller guy holding a rag to his bloody nose.
EASY_A_DVS49
Now in the principal's office.
EASY_A_DVS50
He scribbles on a slip.
EASY_A_DVS51
He points at the door.
EASY_A_DVS52
Outside Woodchuck SOMEONE carries the head of his costume as he falls into step with SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS53
He high fives a guy.
EASY_A_DVS54
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS55
SOMEONE mimics a boxer.
EASY_A_DVS56
She musses her friend's hair and saunters off. Now at home, SOMEONE's mother serves her peas.
EASY_A_DVS57
SOMEONE eyes her younger brother.
EASY_A_DVS59
Her brother eyes her plate.
EASY_A_DVS60
She kisses her mom.
EASY_A_DVS61
Her husband sits with their son.
EASY_A_DVS62
Now SOMEONE mops the gym.
EASY_A_DVS63
She grins at him. Now they clean a tennis court.
EASY_A_DVS64
Later, SOMEONE wipes graffiti from a bathroom stall.
EASY_A_DVS65
SOMEONE adds graffiti.
EASY_A_DVS66
Now on a ridge overlooking the town.
EASY_A_DVS67
Lounging on the hood of an old VW bug, SOMEONE reaches through the window and takes out her cellphone.
EASY_A_DVS68
SOMEONE nods.
EASY_A_DVS69
We peer through an arched hedge.
EASY_A_DVS70
SOMEONE rides into view on a scooter, lurches to a halt and dismounts awkwardly. He arrives at the Penderghast front door and knocks. SOMEONE's mother answers with a warm delighted smile.
EASY_A_DVS71
She pulls him inside.
EASY_A_DVS72
She faces a stairway.
EASY_A_DVS73
She leads SOMEONE upstairs.
EASY_A_DVS74
Under her puzzled stare, SOMEONE screws up his mouth and nods coolly.
EASY_A_DVS75
His eyes well with tears.
EASY_A_DVS76
SOMEONE shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS77
SOMEONE stares imploringly at her.
EASY_A_DVS78
At the party, two teens water slide into a pool.
EASY_A_DVS79
She leans close to Melody.
EASY_A_DVS80
She pretends to munch on his ear.
EASY_A_DVS81
She shuts the door.
EASY_A_DVS82
She slips off a pair of red SOMEONE panties from under her skirt.
EASY_A_DVS83
She hangs them on the doorknob, blocking the keyhole.
EASY_A_DVS84
The bully tries to peer through, as a crowd gathers. SOMEONE eyes the drapes.
EASY_A_DVS85
He goes to the bed.
EASY_A_DVS86
The eavesdropping team swap looks.
EASY_A_DVS87
She slaps him, then cups a hand over his mouth.
EASY_A_DVS88
She spanks him with a book.
EASY_A_DVS89
He yanks him to his feet.
EASY_A_DVS90
SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump on the bed and smack the wall.
EASY_A_DVS91
He slaps her rear end and she smacks him.
EASY_A_DVS92
She punches him in the gut.
EASY_A_DVS93
SOMEONE hops down off the bed as SOMEONE recovers.
EASY_A_DVS94
As he stands, she musses his hair and rumbles his shirt.
EASY_A_DVS95
Pausing, SOMEONE grabs her arm.
EASY_A_DVS96
Olives meets his earnest gaze.
EASY_A_DVS97
As she smiles and nods, he leans his forehead against hers.
EASY_A_DVS98
SOMEONE beams kindly, and gives another nod. Facing the door, SOMEONE halts.
EASY_A_DVS99
He hands her the panties. SOMEONE salutes him, then stuffs them in his pocket.
EASY_A_DVS100
The eavesdroppers scatter as SOMEONE opens the door.
EASY_A_DVS101
He heads into the hallway.
EASY_A_DVS102
His bully accosts him.
EASY_A_DVS103
The bully gives him a friendly shove into a crowd of congratulatory males. As SOMEONE makes her way through the hallway, other teens clear a path and stare at her. She nearly bumps into SOMEONE at a doorway.
EASY_A_DVS104
Behind her back, several guys crudely thrust their pelvises.
EASY_A_DVS105
As she turns around, they sheepishly stop.
EASY_A_DVS106
Now SOMEONE plays an acoustic guitar in her room.
EASY_A_DVS107
Her mother enters, bearing a green box wrapped with a blue ribbon.
EASY_A_DVS108
Her mother bumps and grinds her hips on her way out.
EASY_A_DVS109
SOMEONE bonds unto her bed and opens the box. Inside she finds a greeting card with a gift card.
EASY_A_DVS110
She pulls out a phallic object wrapped in tissue.
EASY_A_DVS111
SOMEONE sets it back in the box, and answers her cell.
EASY_A_DVS112
The box vibrates.
EASY_A_DVS113
She ends the call.
EASY_A_DVS114
She flings all the clothes out of her closet and storms out.
EASY_A_DVS115
Later, she returns toting a half dozen shopping bags. Now SOMEONE tears red fabric into scraps then meticulously cuts them up with scissors as her dog looks on.
EASY_A_DVS116
Pulling bustiers from the shopping bags, she sits to work with a needle and thread.
EASY_A_DVS117
She pricks herself.
EASY_A_DVS118
She sucks her thumb, but keeps working, cutting the thread with her teeth.
EASY_A_DVS119
Her father steps in.
EASY_A_DVS121
They share a grin, and he heads out. Later SOMEONE sews with a smile. She bites off the thread then studies her handiwork.
EASY_A_DVS123
In an outdoor breezeway, SOMEONE struts into a crowd of students wearing a black bustier with a red letter A sewn to the bust. A double strand of pearls rings her neck, and her auburn hair falls in soft curls around her face. Dark sunglasses hide her eyes above her coy smile. As she sashays onward, the students stare at her.
EASY_A_DVS124
She makes a kissy face.
EASY_A_DVS125
A girl and guy watched slack-jawed. SOMEONE smirks to herself.
EASY_A_DVS126
With a bustier showing off her narrow waist, she halts facing SOMEONE and SOMEONE. The blonde eyes her friend scandalous outfit, and shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS127
SOMEONE frowns.
EASY_A_DVS128
SOMEONE smacks SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS129
Now at the lunch counter, SOMEONE serves herself mashed potatoes. Two guys ogle her. She eats some of her potatoes, and sucks the spoon.
EASY_A_DVS130
One guy drops his tray. As they scramble away, SOMEONE finds herself facing SOMEONE, who snares and heads off.
EASY_A_DVS131
Seeing Mr. SOMEONE behind her, SOMEONE yanks the spoon from her mouth.
EASY_A_DVS132
Now in a gazebo.
EASY_A_DVS133
She points at everyone.
EASY_A_DVS134
A hunky guy with a cross necklace accompanies a boy on guitar.
EASY_A_DVS135
SOMEONE climbs out of a lap pool.
EASY_A_DVS136
He gives her a playful shove. A chubby guy drives off behind her.
EASY_A_DVS137
She stutters and stalks off.
EASY_A_DVS138
She gives him an angry gape. SOMEONE blinks shamefully.
EASY_A_DVS139
He gestures at his chunky build.
EASY_A_DVS140
He plods away.
EASY_A_DVS141
SOMEONE lingers, brushing her hair back.
EASY_A_DVS142
She watches as SOMEONE plops down on a bench.
EASY_A_DVS143
He glumly eats a snack. SOMEONE bombs her head equivocatingly.
EASY_A_DVS144
His hopeful expression fades as she saunters off.
EASY_A_DVS145
Our view zooms from guys texting at the pool, to more guys huddle around a cellphone on the soccer field.
EASY_A_DVS146
Nearby, a girl talks to a football player. She heads to the track, where four other girls race, then stop and huddle around a phone.
EASY_A_DVS147
Our view whizzes to the bleachers, where another girl chats with a couple.
EASY_A_DVS148
We zoom through tennis courts, through a locker room, and into the gym. A dance team reads a text, as they rehearse a can-can. We whiz back through the locker room, to the lap pool, where SOMEONE stands uncomfortably. A guy points at her.
EASY_A_DVS149
A Christian boy play guitar.
EASY_A_DVS150
Paris Bueller sings.
EASY_A_DVS151
SOMEONE shows another page to her webcam.
EASY_A_DVS152
Now she knocks on Mr. SOMEONE's open door.
EASY_A_DVS153
She takes a seat facing his desk.
EASY_A_DVS154
He nods, then waggles a finger at a scarlet A on her pink bustier.
EASY_A_DVS155
A tall blonde enters.
EASY_A_DVS156
SOMEONE leaves.
EASY_A_DVS157
As they kiss, he gropes her rear.
EASY_A_DVS158
He pinches her butt.
EASY_A_DVS159
He stares longingly after his wife, then frowns and shifts his gaze. Now in the administrative office, SOMEONE sharpens pencils and blows off the shavings.
EASY_A_DVS160
SOMEONE scowls at SOMEONE, who winks back at her.
EASY_A_DVS162
She shows a plaque.
EASY_A_DVS163
SOMEONE nods blankly.
EASY_A_DVS164
She offers a handful of condoms.
EASY_A_DVS165
Mrs. SOMEONE nods and smiles as SOMEONE collects her things.
EASY_A_DVS166
In the main office, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE comforting Micah.
EASY_A_DVS167
SOMEONE squeezes his arm and murmurs. He tearfully heads toward the counselor's office.
EASY_A_DVS168
She kisses her fingers, pats her hand over her heart, then raises it skyward. Micah does the same.
EASY_A_DVS169
SOMEONE takes a seat beside SOMEONE, and awkwardly pats the sobbing girl's head.
EASY_A_DVS170
SOMEONE grabs her.
EASY_A_DVS171
She yanks her into a hug.
EASY_A_DVS172
SOMEONE seizes her in another hug.
EASY_A_DVS173
SOMEONE shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS174
As they hug again, SOMEONE sniffs her hair.
EASY_A_DVS175
The next day they hug again.
EASY_A_DVS176
SOMEONE points at her phone. SOMEONE reads her text. "Hey girlie, hang after SKL today, xoxox. WWJD."
EASY_A_DVS177
SOMEONE points at her ceramics partner and mimes gagging. SOMEONE gives a sarcastic thumbs up.
EASY_A_DVS178
As they hug, SOMEONE rests her hand near a spinning table saw.
EASY_A_DVS179
SOMEONE uses a wooden cross to edge it away. Now in a hospital room.
EASY_A_DVS180
His mother swats him.
EASY_A_DVS181
She smacks him again. Later she uses her cellphone.
EASY_A_DVS182
Now in the school office, SOMEONE holds a phone to her ear.
EASY_A_DVS183
Mrs. SOMEONE steps in and overhears.
EASY_A_DVS184
Now SOMEONE storms into the locker room.
EASY_A_DVS185
She slaps SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS186
SOMEONE smirks. Now Micah uses his cell.
EASY_A_DVS187
Mrs. SOMEONE hangs up.
EASY_A_DVS188
She paces in her office, a hand cupped over her mouth.
EASY_A_DVS189
SOMEONE walks in.
EASY_A_DVS190
She throws a photo of herself with her husband into a box, breaking the frame.
EASY_A_DVS191
SOMEONE stares sympathetically at the tearful guidance counselor.
EASY_A_DVS192
Mrs. SOMEONE looks up at her.
EASY_A_DVS193
She nods emphatically. SOMEONE lays a hand on her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS194
SOMEONE winces, then lowers her hand.
EASY_A_DVS195
Mrs. SOMEONE pulls her into a hug. Her hair pokes into SOMEONE's mouth.
EASY_A_DVS196
Later SOMEONE steps outside, to find the fundamentalists holding signs reading variations of, "Olive is a slut."
EASY_A_DVS197
SOMEONE pickets.
EASY_A_DVS198
She rejoins the group. As SOMEONE starts to leave, she bumps into SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS199
He glimpses at the protesters.
EASY_A_DVS200
SOMEONE turns away.
EASY_A_DVS201
With her back to SOMEONE and the protesters, she wears a wounded stare as she walks away.
EASY_A_DVS202
At a bookstore.
EASY_A_DVS203
Later she flips through a Bible.
EASY_A_DVS204
Now at a church.
EASY_A_DVS205
SOMEONE steps into a confessional booth.
EASY_A_DVS206
SOMEONE's large green eyes glisten.
EASY_A_DVS207
The young outcast gives a slow nod, then shrugs tearfully.
EASY_A_DVS208
Light from the confessional's grated screen cast an ornate shadow pattern against her cheek.
EASY_A_DVS209
Looking in, she finds the priest's booth empty.
EASY_A_DVS210
She leaves the confessional and rushes past a pew, knocking a Bible from the seat. She puts it back and hurries out.
EASY_A_DVS211
Now in the pastor's office.
EASY_A_DVS212
His placid smile briefly vanishes.
EASY_A_DVS213
She knocks over a family photo. Righting it, she finds SOMEONE in the picture.
EASY_A_DVS214
She topples another photo of him and SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS215
Now at home, SOMEONE sits on a sectional with her mom and brother.
EASY_A_DVS216
In the cafeteria.
EASY_A_DVS217
SOMEONE smiles as he stands.
EASY_A_DVS218
She beams softly to herself.
EASY_A_DVS219
Nighttime at the Lobster Shack, SOMEONE shares a booth with SOMEONE who wears a demure black dress.
EASY_A_DVS220
He smiles boyishly.
EASY_A_DVS221
Under SOMEONE's unwavering gaze, SOMEONE gives a nervous nod, then looks down at the table.
EASY_A_DVS222
Wearing a plush lobster on his head, SOMEONE leads fellow servers to a table.
EASY_A_DVS223
Watching fondly, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE on the other side of a fish tank.
EASY_A_DVS224
SOMEONE spots them.
EASY_A_DVS225
Sneaking out, SOMEONE glances over and finds her staring.
EASY_A_DVS226
SOMEONE turns away.
EASY_A_DVS227
Later, SOMEONE walks her to a car.
EASY_A_DVS228
She starts to open the passenger door, but he shuts it.
EASY_A_DVS229
He presents a gift card.
EASY_A_DVS230
Staring at it, SOMEONE tears up and bites her lip.
EASY_A_DVS231
SOMEONE looks up at him with a wounded glare.
EASY_A_DVS232
He kisses her. She pulls back.
EASY_A_DVS233
He tries again. She pushes him away.
EASY_A_DVS234
He grabs her.
EASY_A_DVS235
She shoves him.
EASY_A_DVS236
He leans in again.
EASY_A_DVS237
SOMEONE wrestles him off her. Then marches toward the restaurant.
EASY_A_DVS238
She chucks the gift card at him.
EASY_A_DVS239
She turns her back to him and cries.
EASY_A_DVS240
She bites her lip hard. SOMEONE gets in his car.
EASY_A_DVS241
SOMEONE picks at the stitching of her A.
EASY_A_DVS242
SOMEONE comes out from the back of the building.
EASY_A_DVS243
SOMEONE's car peals through the parking lot as the off-duty waiter approaches the tearful girl.
EASY_A_DVS244
She gives a grateful nod.
EASY_A_DVS245
Now SOMEONE drives, as SOMEONE cries in the passenger seat.
EASY_A_DVS246
She shakes her head, wincing tearfully.
EASY_A_DVS247
They smile and lock eyes. SOMEONE bashfully drops her gaze.
EASY_A_DVS248
Knitting her brow, she shakes her head. SOMEONE blinks.
EASY_A_DVS249
She unbuckles her seat belt and they share a tight embrace.
EASY_A_DVS250
SOMEONE buries his face in her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS251
As she pulls away, he holds on to her hand.
EASY_A_DVS252
She pulls it away, and opens the door. Then swings her long slender legs outside.
EASY_A_DVS253
She stands and shuts the door behind her, strolling off.
EASY_A_DVS254
Facing the car once again, she leans down to peak at SOMEONE through the window.
EASY_A_DVS255
He rolls it down. And turns off the ignition.
EASY_A_DVS256
She cringes, rolling her eyes, then heads off.
EASY_A_DVS257
She grins at him over her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS258
The gossipy girl dashes off.
EASY_A_DVS259
She crumbles ice-cream cones at the chubby server.
EASY_A_DVS260
Micah scratches himself as he reads a Bible.
EASY_A_DVS262
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed. Mrs. SOMEONE smiles, and shifts in her seat.
EASY_A_DVS263
SOMEONE hurries out and runs across the quad into Mr. SOMEONE's classroom.
EASY_A_DVS264
SOMEONE's jaw drops and she shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS265
She shifts her horrified gaze.
EASY_A_DVS266
Now at her webcam.
EASY_A_DVS267
Mr. SOMEONE trudges though campus.
EASY_A_DVS268
Nighttime on the ridge.
EASY_A_DVS269
SOMEONE shows her scarf.
EASY_A_DVS270
The mother kisses her daughter's head.
EASY_A_DVS271
She cradles SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS272
SOMEONE shows a glittery sign to her webcam.
EASY_A_DVS273
Now in a packed gym, SOMEONE rolls out the wheelbarrow. SOMEONE climbs out of the wood in a feather boa.
EASY_A_DVS274
She rips off SOMEONE's Woodchuck costume, revealing his blue devil costume.
EASY_A_DVS275
They share a grin.
EASY_A_DVS276
In the stands, the fundamentalists stare as other students smile and clap.
EASY_A_DVS277
SOMEONE pumps his fist.
EASY_A_DVS278
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's cheek and gives her the feather boa.
EASY_A_DVS279
In a black corset with red stripes, SOMEONE bumps her hip at a gawking basketball player. Then smacks a dancer's rear.
EASY_A_DVS280
SOMEONE's jaw drops. SOMEONE pulls the slide of a band member's trombone, and poses with SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS281
SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
EASY_A_DVS283
Principal Gibbons storms over.
EASY_A_DVS284
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap disgusted looks.
EASY_A_DVS285
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's arm and scampers out with him.
EASY_A_DVS286
Later she faces her webcam as her classmates, teachers, and family watch her webcast.
EASY_A_DVS287
SOMEONE peeks outside, and finds SOMEONE standing on a lawnmower holding a pair of speakers.
EASY_A_DVS288
She faces her webcam once again.
EASY_A_DVS289
Her brother stares, listening in.
EASY_A_DVS290
The webcast shows her grin and trod out the door.
EASY_A_DVS291
The pastor frowns at his laptop.
EASY_A_DVS292
SOMEONE watches on a cellphone and a truck almost hits him.
EASY_A_DVS293
He hurls ice cream at it.
EASY_A_DVS294
Now, Mr. SOMEONE stares steadily at his laptop.
EASY_A_DVS295
His wife smiles at him, but he ignores her.
EASY_A_DVS296
She sheepishly sucks her lips and heads off.
EASY_A_DVS297
Mr., SOMEONE watches her go.
EASY_A_DVS298
In the gazebo, SOMEONE soberly touches her cross necklace.
EASY_A_DVS299
SOMEONE sits at a fountain, staring at a text that reads, "Ri, sorry I lied to you."
EASY_A_DVS300
The busty blonde gazes off tearfully.
EASY_A_DVS301
Now in a hotel room, SOMEONE lies in bed.
EASY_A_DVS302
His beefy mocha skin boyfriend snuggles up behind him and they watch Huckleberry Finn on a laptop.
EASY_A_DVS303
SOMEONE smiles. Now outside, SOMEONE leaps into SOMEONE's arms.
EASY_A_DVS304
He whirls her around, then sets her down. They share a sweet passionate kiss.
EASY_A_DVS305
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand, then leads her to the lawnmower.
EASY_A_DVS306
She climbs onto the rear grass-bagger as SOMEONE takes a seat at the wheel.
EASY_A_DVS307
She wraps her arm around his chest and they ride off.
EASY_A_DVS308
They wheel slowly across the lawn.
EASY_A_DVS309
SOMEONE raises an arm victoriously, and so does SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS310
Their image freezes.
EASY_A_DVS311
They drive onward, keeping their fists in the air.
EASY_A_DVS312
The mower carries them up a tree-lined road on a hill.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS13
The frowning beauty arrives beside SOMEONE and accidentally drops her purse.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS14
As he sets it on the bar, she spies his wedding ring.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS15
The pair leaves.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS17
She puts his hand on her breast.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS18
He keeps his hand on her chest. Beverly Hills 2011.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS19
He leaves a note on a young woman's pillow, Cindy I had a great night.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS20
P.S, thanks for not beating me like my wife does.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS21
Now at a medical practice, a woman takes a stiff dark liquid filled sack from a box.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS22
A deliveryman eyes the product.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS23
She grabs her own breast. The man reaches for it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS24
With a woman who has one eyebrow much higher than the other.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS25
SOMEONE’s botched eyebrow rises even higher.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS26
SOMEONE dryly lowers her chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS27
Her eyebrow remains cocked.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS28
She nods.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS29
Her brow shoots to her hairline.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS30
As he hugs her, she waggles her brows.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS31
SOMEONE's cousin arrives.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS32
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS33
Now stylish guests attend a hip party at a mansion overlooking the ocean.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS34
SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach a man with an unnaturally stiff, smooth face.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS35
As they down drinks, wine spills down his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS36
Now in a bathroom.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS37
SOMEONE pockets his ring.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS38
He gives Ariel a shot, then smacks him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS39
Later, they leave the bathroom.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS40
Clad in a filmy cerulean dress, a young statuesque beauty with sun-kissed skin and long blonde hair approaches SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS41
The longtime bachelor stops in his tracks and stares.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS42
As the pair steps outside, Adon struggles to close his lips around his straw.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS43
A taut-faced woman.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS44
Later on the beach.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS45
SOMEONE leans in and kisses him. Their arms twine around each other and they sway on their feet.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS47
In a nock encased by tall rock formations, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie between two blankets.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS48
Digging through his pockets, SOMEONE finds the wedding ring. Her smile vanishes as she holds it up.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS49
She chucks the ring at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS50
She marches down the beach. Now at SOMEONE's medical practice.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS51
SOMEONE tosses her hair and smiles vapidly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS52
Two kids enter with a stout SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS53
The SOMEONE plays a hand-held video game.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS54
SOMEONE faces him with a wide-eyed smirk.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS55
Now at a private school, SOMEONE leads a student through a crowded hallway. SOMEONE enters with flowers. Seeing him, the young teacher turns away.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS56
She dumps the extravagant bouquet in a trash bin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS57
SOMEONE takes him to a classroom.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS59
SOMEONE faces a window. From the other side, Silas glares and points menacingly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS60
On Rodeo Drive.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS61
Now in a high-end store, she wobbles in a pair of four-inch heels.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS62
SOMEONE gives her a gentle shove, and she falls over.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS63
Now SOMEONE eyes a vast display of designer handbags.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS64
Later, SOMEONE carries a few shopping bags in each hand, as he follows her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS65
In a store, SOMEONE tries on one stylish curve-hugging dress after another.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS66
SOMEONE gives her a playful shove, and she swats at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS67
She shakes her hips, and they laugh.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS68
Later, SOMEONE follows her out of Tiffany's, loaded down with shopping bags. Now a hairdresser eyes SOMEONE appraisingly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS69
She frowns as he coldly approaches.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS70
Bending down, he takes up handfuls of her long honey-brown hair and peers closely at it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS71
Now at an upscale sunlit lounge.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS72
From a stairway, SOMEONE ascends into view in a white sheet dress that shows off her long tan legs and graceful curves.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS73
Her hair tousled in sexy waves, she smirks through glamorous sunglasses. A distinguished man in a suit trails her dutifully.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS74
SOMEONE turns and her jaw drops at the site of the other woman.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS75
Moving in slow motion, SOMEONE blows a kiss to a stranger.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS76
She slaps the waiter's rear.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS77
SOMEONE nearly chokes on her red wine.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS78
SOMEONE jolts.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS79
She kicks SOMEONE hard in the shin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS80
Later, they leave.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS81
Facing SOMEONE, she finds him staring pointedly at her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS82
She abruptly gets in the limo.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS83
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE, who stares agog at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS84
At Pizza Hut.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS85
The SOMEONE salsa dances around a janitor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS86
They shake hands on it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS87
SOMEONE faces her younger brother.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS88
SOMEONE pours soda into his glass, then takes a sip through a straw. All the while, keeping a cold glare fixed on SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS89
SOMEONE sucks on his straw as if it's a cigarette.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS90
The girl picks up her slice and winces at it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS92
A woman with mismatched breasts.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS93
They go to the exam room.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS94
SOMEONE meets his gaze, sheepishly. SOMEONE grins.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS95
He wags his finger in his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS96
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS97
He reaches for her phone. She swats him away, then answers.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS98
She ends the call. Returning to Mrs. Harrington, she finds SOMEONE staring at her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS99
A lopsided bra.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS100
He wiggles his finger from his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS101
Outside, JD McFunnigans.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS102
SOMEONE steps out of her car in a tight dress.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS103
In slow motion, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and the kids try to cross the parking lot.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS104
A boy holding a soda cup runs out in front of them. He stops and turns. As his pregnant mother catches up, he chucks the full cup at her and runs off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS105
Soaked with soda, the pregnant woman raises her hands overhand and yells after him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS106
Everyone still moving in slow motion, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the kids watch the furious woman chase after her
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS108
Inside, children run wildly through an elaborate play structure with tunnels, slides, and climbing ropes. SOMEONE enters with SOMEONE and the kids.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS109
A chubby boy trips and head-butts SOMEONE in the crotch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS110
SOMEONE approaches.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS111
SOMEONE stares at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS112
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a look.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS113
She runs away.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS114
SOMEONE leaves and SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS115
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE through the play structure.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS116
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look up from the floor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS117
A little boy sneezes on SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS119
SOMEONE eyes him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS120
She beams and takes a bite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS121
SOMEONE mouths, Thank you.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS122
SOMEONE returns.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS123
SOMEONE grins at him, then hangs his head and cries.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS124
Now at LAX, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE and the kids in a busy airport terminal.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS125
A bespectacled SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE on the lips until she pushes him off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS126
He wags his tongue, and SOMEONE catches it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS127
She drags him aside and wipes her hand on his vest.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS128
He points to his round glasses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS129
SOMEONE backhands him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS130
Now a Hawaiian airliner soars over turquoise water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS131
On the island, a luxurious beachside resort boasts several swimming pools on its manicured grounds.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS132
Beyond a large reflecting pool in the lobby, the family arrives. SOMEONE approaches the registration desk.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS133
SOMEONE takes out his credit card then returns to the others.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS134
SOMEONE and SOMEONE raise their hands. Now on a palm tree lined beach, SOMEONE steps out of the water in a yellow string bikini. SOMEONE and SOMEONE check her out as they cross the sand. The voluptuous young woman brushes back her long blonde hair. Ogling her, SOMEONE lifts his round glasses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS135
SOMEONE walks his fingers up SOMEONE's arm. Later outside a jewelry store.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS136
Nighttime at a luau, fire dancers perform while the group eats dinner.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS137
SOMEONE takes a pitcher from the waiter.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS138
The kids swap a look.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS139
The petite redhead flounces over.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS140
He kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS141
SOMEONE squints at them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS142
The guys pound fists.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS143
Dawn in the lobby.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS144
Now in a lush tropical forest, the group hikes a trail.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS145
The black-haired pig charges them and they run. SOMEONE knocks SOMEONE down, and the pig steps on his back.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS146
Later, the group hikes a narrow trail beside a canyon.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS147
SOMEONE scales a steep hill, while the others lag behind. Hiking through bamboo stalks, she leads the group up another incline.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS148
On a river, they paddle two-person canoes. Sitting behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE gawks at the exposed crack of her rear.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS149
SOMEONE whacks him with her paddle.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS150
Now as all six of them cross a rope bridge, a family of four spots them from below.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS151
SOMEONE stands at the tail end.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS152
A board breaks, and he lands on a crossbeam, crotch first.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS154
SOMEONE chucks SOMEONE into a mud puddle.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS155
She lifts her face from the sticky muck.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS156
Now at a lagoon with a waterfall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS157
SOMEONE strips down to a skimpy string bikini.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS158
She goes to the water's edge.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS159
SOMEONE dives gracefully into the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS161
SOMEONE approaches the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS162
SOMEONE shyly whispers to his mother.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS163
On the far side of the lagoon, SOMEONE emerges from the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS164
She picks her way over some jagged rocks, and stands beneath the waterfall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS165
He tries to high five SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS166
SOMEONE strips down to a pink string bikini, revealing her tan slender body.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS167
In slow motion, she saunters to the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS168
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare slack-jawed at SOMEONE's well-toned figure.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS169
SOMEONE steps away. SOMEONE picks her way out to a rocky point.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS170
SOMEONE dives into the water. Cladding briefs with frogs printed on them, SOMEONE climbs rocks by the waterfall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS171
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lounge near-by.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS172
He drops to the water, landing on his back.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS173
Now back at the hotel, the group disembarks from a shuttle.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS174
Evening in SOMEONE's suite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS175
He wags his finger from his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS176
As she leaves, SOMEONE approaches her in the hallway.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS177
SOMEONE punches him in the gut and keeps walking.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS178
Later in SOMEONE's suite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS179
SOMEONE draws a card and reads.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS180
SOMEONE draws a card.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS181
SOMEONE shrugs.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS182
As he cries, SOMEONE goes to comfort him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS183
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS184
SOMEONE storms off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS185
SOMEONE holds her crying brother in her arms. Turning, SOMEONE smacks his shoulder.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS186
Now he tucks them in.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS187
SOMEONE looks in on them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS188
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE shoves the kids back down on the bed.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS189
Now on a putting green overlooking the ocean.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS190
He gives her the putting flag.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS191
The flag juts up from his butt cheeks. Now by the hotel pool, he wears water wings.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS192
SOMEONE tosses him into the pool. SOMEONE surfaces and scoops him up in his arms.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS193
Later, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS194
SOMEONE puppets a dolphin shaped cookie.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS195
SOMEONE flails his arms and kicks his legs. Slowly making his way towards the pool's edge. As he arrives, SOMEONE feeds him the cookie and tousles his wet hair.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS196
At a spa.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS197
The women get massages.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS198
SOMEONE's brow furrows. At the pool.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS199
SOMEONE takes off his water wings.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS200
SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE from his arms, and the little boy flails and kicks his way across the pool. SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS201
SOMEONE's head dips below the water, and he lifts it back out.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS202
SOMEONE reaches the pool's edge, high fives his mother and grins broadly. SOMEONE happily picks up SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS203
SOMEONE removes her sunglasses, and smiles lovingly at SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS204
Beside her, SOMEONE takes off her shades and regards him with a fond gaze.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS205
SOMEONE drops SOMEONE in the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS206
SOMEONE urges SOMEONE to intervene.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS207
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE into the pool.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS208
He jumps in the water, dunks her and holds her under.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS209
He lets SOMEONE up, and she splashes him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS210
In SOMEONE's suite, he talks on the phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS211
SOMEONE emerges from the bathroom, wrapped in a towel. Reclining on a sofa, SOMEONE struggles to sit up.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS212
SOMEONE drops her towel. SOMEONE tosses an apple between his hands.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS213
He resumes his call.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS214
SOMEONE enters the bathroom. In the shower, SOMEONE dances and lip-syncs.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS215
He switches off the music.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS216
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE, eating a mango she thrusts the phone at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS217
She smacks him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS218
He ends the call.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS219
She gestures to the bathroom, where a pillow and a blanket sit in the tub.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS220
Now at an upscale restaurant, a woman gracefully hula dances to music by a live band. At a table, SOMEONE scrutinizes a wine list.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS221
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pout and rub noses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS222
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE staring at his lap. She receives a text from him reading, I think they took one of your yellow bombers.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS223
Glancing at the couple, she suppresses a grin. SOMEONE receives her reply. I just hope their noses are clean.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS224
Now a hybrid car pulls up to a dilapidated outdoor barbecue restaurant.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS225
At dinner, SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS226
The waitress pours wine.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS227
SOMEONE gapes.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS228
He faces SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS229
They rub their noses together.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS230
SOMEONE leaves.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS231
With SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS232
The local girl leads them around back.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS233
A crowd gathers. SOMEONE nervously approaches the white sheep, which lies on its side. He pokes it a few times.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS234
With SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS235
SOMEONE mockingly mimes an overbite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS236
Gazing into his eyes, SOMEONE softly nods.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS237
SOMEONE meets her gaze, and nods as well.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS238
SOMEONE and SOMEONE shift in their seats. Meanwhile, SOMEONE waves the limp sheep's legs.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS239
He shoves hay in its mouth and grabs her udder.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS240
He does CPR.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS241
He drops his elbow into its belly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS242
He tries the Heimlich maneuver.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS243
A plastic fish pops out, and the sheep walks away.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS244
The girl hugs SOMEONE, then he gives her the Heimlich maneuver.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS245
SOMEONE downs a shot.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS246
She downs another.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS248
SOMEONE leads a group of ladies in bra tops and grass skirts.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS249
SOMEONE re-positions herself center-stage in front of her rival. The ladies start to dance.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS250
He holds his hand over an elderly woman.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS251
As he guides her off stage, SOMEONE gives her a hug.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS252
Tanner highlights SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS253
He moves on to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS254
A heavy-set woman shimmies in a coconut top.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS255
She storms off. Only SOMEONE and SOMEONE remain.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS256
SOMEONE raises her arms overhead and shakes her hips.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS257
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, then matches her hip action. SOMEONE glares.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS258
The tall redhead shakes her head and circles her bent arms, then points to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS259
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE, who gestures forward to show off her own moves. She shrugs her shoulders, then does a break dancing arm wave, and stops facing SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS260
SOMEONE opens his arms. SOMEONE glances at her opponent, then breaks into a lively Charleston, kicking up her heels. She twirls like a ballerina, then points back to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS261
SOMEONE lowers her center of gravity, then mimes as though she were juggling. She juggles pretend balls behind her back, catches them in her bosom and throws one to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS262
SOMEONE watches her rival. With her back to the crowd, SOMEONE gyrates her rear. Slow at first, then faster, and faster.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS263
SOMEONE does the same, until SOMEONE does an aerial cartwheel, twirls and drops into a split.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS264
She raises her arm in a final pose.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS265
SOMEONE hulas in front of SOMEONE, then shakes her hips while raising her arms overhead.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS266
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE out of the way and poses again. She gets up and blows SOMEONE kisses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS268
SOMEONE flashes her rear, and all of the men stand up.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS269
SOMEONE grabs the mic.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS270
Later, each couple holds a coconut between them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS271
Both couples struggle to raise their coconuts above their bellies.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS272
SOMEONE kneels, resting the coconut at SOMEONE's waist on her cleavage.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS273
SOMEONE's chin holds the coconut at SOMEONE's crotch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS274
SOMEONE and SOMEONE bring their coconut up to their chests.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS275
SOMEONE and SOMEONE drop their coconut on the floor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS276
SOMEONE lowers his butt over the coconut.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS277
He lifts the coconut off of the floor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS278
He waddles around, then lifts his backside to SOMEONE's waist.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS279
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold their coconut between their necks.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS280
With their mouth under their coconut, SOMEONE pushes it up to SOMEONE's lips.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS281
SOMEONE drops hers. With their eyes locked, SOMEONE and SOMEONE let their coconut fall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS282
SOMEONE storms off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS283
SOMEONE follows.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS285
At SOMEONE's door.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS286
He wags his finger at his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS287
SOMEONE jolts, then hugs her kids.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS288
An obese woman sleeps on a couch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS289
They shake hands.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS290
As SOMEONE walks away, SOMEONE slowly shuts the door to her suite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS291
Now SOMEONE steps off of an elevator and crosses a hallway, with his hand shoved in his pockets.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS292
At the end of another hall, he reaches the door to his own suite and stops.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS293
Rounding a corner, he breaks into a run. SOMEONE jogs back to the elevators and presses the call button.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS294
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS295
SOMEONE points to his ring finger.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS296
The elevator opens and SOMEONE freezes.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS297
She shares a gaze with SOMEONE as the elevator doors close.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS298
Later, we drift over a bed, to find SOMEONE lying alone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS299
Staring thoughtfully, he fondles his wedding ring between his fingertips.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS300
In the next room, SOMEONE tries on short white dresses while chatting on the phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS301
Elsewhere, SOMEONE lies awake in bed. She restlessly wipes her nose, and flips on her other side.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS302
In the bathroom, SOMEONE sleeps in the cramped tub.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS303
As he turns on his side, his left hand lands in the toilet.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS304
Later, SOMEONE lies sound asleep, resting her head on SOMEONE's shoulder.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS305
He remains awake, staring blankly across the room.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS306
SOMEONE lies awake in bed. SOMEONE rests beside her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS307
The brown-haired girl takes her mother's hand and rests her head on SOMEONE's pillow.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS308
Half asleep, SOMEONE ambles into the bathroom, where SOMEONE still sleeps with his hand in the toilet.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS309
The bed-headed boy drops his shorts, then sits on the bowl hunched forward with his arms dangling between his knees.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS310
SOMEONE wakes, noticing his hand, and yanks it out of the bowl.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS311
He grabs a towel and wraps his arm.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS312
He storms out past the boy.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS313
Later, SOMEONE steps outside. Surrounded by tropical plants and lit candles, he makes a call on a portable phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS314
SOMEONE answers a bedside phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS315
SOMEONE shakes his head.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS316
SOMEONE pensively rubs his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS317
Perched on the edge of a hot tub, SOMEONE stares ahead and lowers the phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS318
Now silhouetted against the moonlit ocean, a pod of dolphins leap from the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS320
In the lobby, SOMEONE faces the concierge.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS321
SOMEONE arrives nearby.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS322
The blonde approaches wearing a white dress and a magnolia in her hair.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS323
As SOMEONE hugs her, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE helping her kids pick out clothes in a gift shop.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS324
She watches him with wistful lovelorn gaze.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS325
Now in an outdoor beachfront bar, SOMEONE finishes off a tropical cocktail, as the bartender brings her another.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS326
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS327
SOMEONE sips a cocktail.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS328
SOMEONE regards her with a sober frown.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS329
SOMEONE shrugs her hand.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS330
SOMEONE checks up sailors.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS331
Across the bar, SOMEONE clownishly hula dances for the sailors.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS332
The two women hug.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS333
SOMEONE sits next to them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS334
SOMEONE doubles over laughing with the sailors.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS335
He cocks his head patiently.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS336
SOMEONE tilts his head and grins. Beaming, SOMEONE shakes her head fondly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS337
Her old friend gives a small nod. Leaning in, she gives him a passionate kiss.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS338
The sailors and SOMEONE watch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS339
Now in a life-vest, SOMEONE faces a dolphin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS340
Two push him through the water with their noses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS341
On an airplane.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS342
Now at a wedding reception.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS343
SOMEONE sits alone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS344
SOMEONE leads him to the dance floor. Nearby, SOMEONE clownishly poses for photos with a gaggle of attractive young women.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS345
Slow dancing with his wife, SOMEONE eyes the stage.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS346
SOMEONE sports a long soul patch. SOMEONE wags his finger from his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS347
SOMEONE grimaces as he plays. His inches long pillar of facial hair waving in a breeze. He makes the gesture again.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS348
Grinning, SOMEONE pulls him close. The couple sways happily in unison as their friends and loved ones celebrate around them.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS5
At the guys house
KNOCKED_UP_DVS6
SOMEONE stares blankly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS7
Executive's office.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS8
He cups his flexed hands toward his chest.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS9
SOMEONE points to his head.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS10
Later they walk past a nightclub.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS11
Smile at each other.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS13
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE wearily.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS14
Daytime. The pool sparkles outside the guesthouse.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS15
Now a pale chubby butt lies naked under tangled sheets.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS16
SOMEONE, standing and dressed, wrinkles her brow at SOMEONE's butt. She bounces the mattress with her foot.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS17
She bounces it harder.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS18
She extends her foot and touches SOMEONE's side. He jerks up and glances around.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS19
Stares at his bare behind.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS21
SOMEONE cocks her head.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS22
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out of the guesthouse.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS23
SOMEONE in a well-cut suit. In front of the house they walk across the lawn as SOMEONE carries the baby toward them.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS24
They shake hands.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS25
SOMEONE faces the baby.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS26
Now in a dinner, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE in a booth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS27
SOMEONE shakes his head gazing off.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS28
SOMEONE frowns.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS29
SOMEONE sits back down.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS30
Eight weeks later.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS31
SOMEONE and an editor watch James on a computer monitor.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS32
She swallows hard.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS33
SOMEONE touches her throat and heaves forward. She claps a hand over her mouth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS34
Raising his hands overhead.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS35
SOMEONE slowly sits back up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS36
She wipes her mouth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS37
She takes another swipe at her mouth, then freezes
KNOCKED_UP_DVS38
She leans back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS39
They sit by the pool.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS40
SOMEONE gazes off.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS41
A web page reads, Coming Soon.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS42
The screen shows the guys email address.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS43
An email pops up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS44
SOMEONE wrinkles her nose. Now in their backyard the guys smoke.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS45
Now SOMEONE paces as she dials the phone. Back with the guys.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS46
SOMEONE raises both arms.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS47
SOMEONE forces a smile.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS48
He leans back in his chair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS49
Now in an exam room, a smiling doctor enters.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS50
SOMEONE's eyes shift.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS51
Puts her feet in the stir-ups and the doctor
KNOCKED_UP_DVS52
covers her legs with a blanket. SOMEONE glances around uncomfortably.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS53
The blanket.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS54
SOMEONE gazes at the ceiling. The doctor squeezes gel onto the end of a wand.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS55
Smiles indulgently as the doctor forces a smile and inserts the wand. SOMEONE shifts. An image appears on a monitor.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS56
She is sobbing face.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS57
Pats SOMEONE's back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS58
Now at SOMEONE's place.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS59
SOMEONE leans forward.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS60
SOMEONE gets up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS61
Now at home and wearing pajamas SOMEONE makes a phone call.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS62
Her eyes glisten tearfully.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS63
Now SOMEONE pulls into the driveway of the rental house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS64
SOMEONE gestures to his chubby friend.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS65
His amiable smile fades as he eyes her body.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS66
They gaze at her through blurry eyes.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS67
As SOMEONE leaves the room SOMEONE sits. SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE, all stare at the TV.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS68
SOMEONE follows their gaze to a clip from Wild Things. Neve Campbell kisses a topless Denise Richards in a swimming pool. SOMEONE shrugs.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS69
On screen, SOMEONE removes SOMEONE's shirt.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS70
Little hat and holds a tiny outfit.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS71
SOMEONE walk outside they tentatively hold hands. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand in their bathroom facing opposite directions. Brushing his teeth he turns to face her.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS72
She dabs under her eyes with her fingertips.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS73
Shifts his stunned gaze.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS74
Now in the guesthouse SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a tender passionate kiss. He gazes into her eyes.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS75
SOMEONE pulls away.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS76
SOMEONE sits on the bed and pulls SOMEONE down beside her.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS77
SOMEONE gives a slow thoughtful nod.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS78
Face each other sharing a warm smile. They lean close and enjoy a tender kiss. Pulling away slightly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS79
Takes a long sip of coffee. The toddler beams at SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS80
He lifts his brow and smiles.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS81
Now in the backyard, SOMEONE plays with the girls.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS83
Her sister forces a smile.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS85
Now outside the rental house, SOMEONE and SOMEONE play Ping-Pong while the others watch.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS87
Now under an ultrasound video words appear. Sixteen weeks.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS88
A wardrobe lady fits SOMEONE with a belt.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS89
A female executive passes by.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS90
SOMEONE gives a defensive shrug
KNOCKED_UP_DVS91
A Baby Bjorn Baby Sling box shows a couple beaming at each other. SOMEONE winces at the picture then shows it to SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS92
They join SOMEONE at a crib. He eyes the price tag.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS93
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit the store.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS94
Now at Record Surplus record store.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS95
He grins broadly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS96
Now a website shows a grinning cartoon logo.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS97
He remains behind and sits facing SOMEONE who thoughtfully tokes on a joint.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS98
Now in the guesthouse.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS99
SOMEONE's eyes glisten.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS100
SOMEONE's bed.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS101
In SOMEONE's car.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS102
Now under an ultrasound video.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS103
SOMEONE drains his glass and pounds the table.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS104
Now in his bedroom SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS105
Now she lies sideways with her back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS106
Later SOMEONE sits in the living room.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS107
A woman covers her bare breast.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS108
SOMEONE shakes his hand exposing...
KNOCKED_UP_DVS109
SOMEONE shrugs at the passing cruiser.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS110
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit by the open cabinet among piles of stuff. She touches an overturned marijuana plant and a large branch breaks off in her hand. Dropping it, she finds a bank statement with SOMEONE's name on it.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS111
It reads $117.13.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS113
SOMEONE notices a shopping bag protruding from the cabinet.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS115
She finds Three baby books. SOMEONE eyes the covers one by one.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS117
With her mouth agape she drops the books
KNOCKED_UP_DVS118
into the bag, then stares off with a pensive expression.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS119
Beneath an ultrasound showing a fetus.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS120
SOMEONE answers the phone.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS121
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS122
To a large suburban house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS123
Gently shuts the door.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS125
Comes downstairs.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS126
SOMEONE creeps toward the back of the house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS127
With a furrowed brow, SOMEONE turns and walks out.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS128
She wipes a tear and heads off.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS129
SOMEONE and SOMEONE wait by the car.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS130
SOMEONE squints at her then unbuckles his seat belt.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS132
SOMEONE's teeth clench.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS133
Leaves with his middle finger raised.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS134
SOMEONE strains to regain her composure.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS135
Now at Del's Saloon.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS136
SOMEONE shakes his head.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS137
The guesthouse, SOMEONE reclines and watches a program.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS138
Opens the front door and stares through red-rimmed eyes.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS139
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS140
SOMEONE shuts the door on him. Nighttime.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS141
SOMEONE watches nervously.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS143
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on the curb.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS144
Now a hotel TV.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS145
SOMEONE sits on a bed.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS146
Moves to a shorter chair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS147
He curls up in a cushioned chair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS148
SOMEONE jams his fist in his mouth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS150
Sadie answers in a princess outfit.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS151
She nods to herself then cracks up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS152
SOMEONE a gift.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS153
Now standing away from the party SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS154
She glances over her shoulder.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS155
SOMEONE holds a large castle cake with ice cream cone turrets.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS156
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE stares after him with a wounded gaze. Then walks out to the backyard.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS157
SOMEONE clenches his jaw.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS158
Sadie runs downstairs.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS159
Denise Richards grabs Neve Campbell's arm. On the couch SOMEONE shakes her head at the screen.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS160
She pauses thoughtfully and puts a hand on her belly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS161
SOMEONE reads What to Expect When You're Expecting.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS162
He picks up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS163
In her bedroom SOMEONE struggles to pack a suitcase without bending over.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS165
He enters the main house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS166
He heads upstairs and strides down the hall.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS167
SOMEONE's bed stands empty. He steps toward the bathroom. SOMEONE lounges in the tub covered in bubbles.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS168
She lets her hands drift downward.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS169
He paces in the hall.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS170
SOMEONE pokes his head into the bathroom.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS171
Hangs up and gazes off. Now he returns to the bathroom and sits on the edge of the tub.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS172
SOMEONE smiles.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS173
SOMEONE stares.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS174
The tense doctor enters.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS175
In the waiting room SOMEONE fidgets.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS176
Meanwhile, SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS177
Samuel strides in.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS178
Between her legs and another on her belly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS179
In the hall, SOMEONE clutches his hand while talking.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS181
SOMEONE lifts her head off the pillow as Dr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE return to her beside.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS182
As Dr. SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS183
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in.. wheelchair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS184
He lowers his head to one side and taps his fingers on the armrest.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS185
A passing doctor shakes his head at them.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS186
In the hall SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS187
As SOMEONE walks away, SOMEONE stares after him. Her mouth agape.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS188
Now she mopes over to the waiting room and plops down beside SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS189
Watching his wife, SOMEONE smirks.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS190
In the delivery room.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS191
He returns to the others.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS192
Shakes his head and sits down.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS193
SOMEONE winks.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS194
SOMEONE's eye Shift between his wife and SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS195
In a wheelchair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS196
On car seat, mother watches her baby. SOMEONE drives.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS10
He unfastens his brace.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS11
In apparel with a trainee.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS12
It shows all team of executives.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS13
He points to a crown on his mug.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS14
SOMEONE glances from his white-mustached boss to a trio of younger executives.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS15
The senior executive meets his gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS16
Man shows a ring.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS17
Unfazed executive grins.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS18
SOMEONE stares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS19
The beefy executive callously picks pizza out of his teeth.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS20
Larry’s eyes glisten in a helpless stare.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS21
The brown-faced executive spreads his hands. SOMEONE takes a breath
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS22
to speak then swallows and looks away. Now traffic lines up behind SOMEONE as he drives his SUV with a stunned gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS23
A view with the left break light shows the SUV gliding into the driveway of a modest home with a well-manicured front lawn. Nighttime. A doorway on the opposite end of the cluttered room frames SOMEONE as he sits on the edge of his bed. Later he lies awake on his stomach, with one-half of his face against a pillow. Now on his back, he presses his hands to his face.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS24
An open doorway shows a glimpse of SOMEONE shoveling through the house. In an adjacent room a globe lamp glows softly. Standing in a closet of mostly empty hangers, SOMEONE hangs up his red U-Mart polo shirt. He stares at it for a moment, then slides the closet door shut.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS25
Daytime. A series of phone calls.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS26
SOMEONE flips his cellphone shut and rests this chin in his hand. Now at a bathroom sink he turns on the cold-water tap and bends over to splash his face. Later, he gazes worriedly into the mirror, as he blots his skin with a towel. Now he holds a pair of slacks on an ironing board.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS27
Now he sits across from a banker with blond, feathered hair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS28
SOMEONE's chest heaves.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS29
Now at home, SOMEONE hauls lawn chairs and a bag of golf clubs out to his front lawn.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS30
SOMEONE puffs a pipe.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS31
SOMEONE follows his neighbor into a garage filled with secondhand goods.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS32
He hands SOMEONE a booklet.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS33
Back in the present.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS34
Entrance reads East Valley Community.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS35
He looks at map and checks it, then.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS37
Now at a registration desk he looks over a course book.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS38
A silver haired man with a bowtie and a toothy smile approaches him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS39
He points at the course book.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS40
He gives a suggestive wink.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS41
Camera bulb flashes and a student ID appears, featuring a photo of a puzzled-looking SOMEONE. Now at a gas station SOMEONE inspects the ID.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS42
Gas tank pocketing his wallet, he eyes the pump’s display. As his gas cost ticks up past $60
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS43
He fills his small tank.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS44
SOMEONE’s total passes $70.00.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS45
The scooter’s total is less than four.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS46
The scooter’s meek.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS47
He wrenches the gas nozzle from his tank.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS48
SOMEONE approaches a scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS49
SOMEONE smiles.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS50
Now SOMEONE carries over a flat screen TV. Later he straddles the scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS51
He falters, half astride the scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS52
Mill around outside East Valley Community College.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS53
She pulls into a space in the parking lot.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS54
Driver side door opens and a woman’s hand sets a pair of high heels on the ground.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS55
Shapely foot slides into each high heels.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS56
Owner an alluring woman with wavy auburn hair emerges. Wearing
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS57
she trudges down a hall.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS58
She enters her in her cluttered office reading the document.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS59
She sits at her desk,
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS60
she brushes her hair out of her face.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS61
Then opens a drawer and takes out a pill.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS63
She takes a weary breath. A full-figured raven-haired woman holding a to-go cup appears in her doorway.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS64
Her colleague enters an office across the hall.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS65
Still sitting, she sips her drink.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS66
The young woman grins.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS67
Removing her helmet, she shakes out her curly hair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS68
SOMEONE eyes his belted khakis.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS69
Now the auburn haired professor peeks in through a window in a classroom door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS70
She enters and looks around.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS71
She counts the meager number of students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS72
She checks again.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS73
The students stare at her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS74
SOMEONE bursts in through another door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS75
The students follow his gaze to their professor, whose shoulders sag disappointedly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS76
Strides to the front of the class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS77
He watches from a front desk off to one side, as Professor SOMEONE sets down her back. The instructor gazes out at their expectant faces, then gives an indifferent shrug. She writes on a chalkboard in front of them.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS78
Breaks, she waves dismissively.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS79
She gives a bright firm nod.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS80
She eyes the students who shoot each other uneasy glances, then return their attention to their professor.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS81
A young man with dark curly hair raises his hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS82
With a wry look she cocks her head.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS83
Her eyes narrow.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS84
SOMEONE blinks apprehensively.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS85
He smiles and nods. The other students shift their uneasy gazes to Miss SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS86
SOMEONE half-smiles in SOMEONE’s direction but breaks off an urge to comment to him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS87
He answers his cell.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS88
Miss SOMEONE's jaw drops.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS89
With a resolute nod she strides up to SOMEONE's desk and raps on it.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS90
He hangs up. As the professor leaves SOMEONE's desk, SOMEONE watches her alertly. Later, he hurries.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS91
Seated at the end of one. He stops.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS92
He sits beside her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS93
SOMEONE gives a puzzled frown, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE. Tilting her head she considers him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS94
SOMEONE's brow crinkles.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS95
She snags his cell.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS96
She tosses its casing to.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS98
He adjusts a mic.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS99
He smiles. The students stare. His smile widens,
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS100
he grins more broadly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS101
He lifts his brow at the unresponsive students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS102
Another classroom Miss SOMEONE writes care on a blackboard then faces two males and two females.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS103
She gives a disappointed nod.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS104
With her eyes averted, she grabs her bag off the table and strides to the back of the classroom. The students watch as the professor exits. Now in a computer
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS105
saw an image of a woman in her underwear.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS109
She grabs two bottles from a liquor cabinet. Her high heels off, she dumps ice into a blender.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS110
Scans his office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS111
He grabs a book and enters the kitchen.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS112
His wife indifferently sips her drink.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS113
She lowers the cocktail.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS114
She sits in an armchair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS115
Guilty frown.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS116
He rolls his eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS117
As he sits across from SOMEONE, she looks up from her magazine.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS118
She takes two long swigs.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS119
Closing her eyes, she leans forward.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS120
She holds her brow. She winces.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS122
SOMEONE meets his gaze. She opens her mouth to speak, then strides off.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS123
Escaping to a balcony, SOMEONE closes the sliding door and sits. Her husband wraps on the glass, his gaze intolerant.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS124
He cups his hands around his mouth.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS125
Now in speech class a blond student hyperactively swivels a Lacrosse stick in her two-handed grip.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS126
SOMEONE shyly raises a hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS127
SOMEONE squares a stack of notecards on his desk then rises from his seat. As he moves behind the lectern the dean smiles excitedly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS128
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS129
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS130
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE checks his phone
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS131
and picks lint of his shirt. He blinks nervously.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS132
He checks his notes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS133
As the dean gapes, SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS134
As SOMEONE sits back down the dean grins.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS135
SOMEONE heads to the podium.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS136
SOMEONE stares disbelievingly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS137
Into the mic.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS138
Grinning he glances around at his classmates.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS139
Lying on the floor with his toe and the other two back away.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS140
He snaps as he steps from side to side repeatedly putting his feet apart then together.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS141
Legs bent, he swivels his knees in and out.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS143
Hovers on the movie screen, asking, Scoot?
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS144
takes the phone out again. Another
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS145
and look to your left. Furrowing his brow
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS146
He turns over his shoulder and sees SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS147
riding a scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS148
Professor SOMEONE glares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS149
He stands in front of SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS150
SOMEONE closes his cell and places it in the professor's hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS151
As he walks off, SOMEONE
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS152
to SOMEONE, who winces. Later.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS153
SOMEONE reverts his gaze as she
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS154
his polo.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS155
SOMEONE locks his menacing.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS156
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS157
Hurries over.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS158
SOMEONE heads home. A scruffy friend studies a
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS159
while he searches a rack of clothes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS160
Her pair of shorts.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS161
In SOMEONE's house, the middle-aged student highlights almost every line on a textbook's pages. Seated at his kitchen island he looks to the front door and doffs his glasses.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS162
SOMEONE enters with a blonde friend.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS163
SOMEONE gets up.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS164
Later Sal cuts SOMEONE's hair in the bathroom.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS165
His friends redecorate.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS166
SOMEONE shrugs. Later SOMEONE drapes a silk scarf over a lamp. In the now smartly arranged living room,
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS167
SOMEONE and a friend read.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS168
Sal introduces SOMEONE. He sports a hip close-cropped haircut.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS169
SOMEONE eyes the made over room.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS170
SOMEONE complies.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS171
SOMEONE gives him a kiss.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS172
She follows the others out.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS173
He peeks through his window blinds, then turns. SOMEONE faces him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS174
SOMEONE nods.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS175
SOMEONE makes eye contact.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS176
Nodding, SOMEONE swallows.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS177
They stack their left hands on top.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS178
SOMEONE's look goes from smiley to severe in a split second. He leaves. SOMEONE smoothes his new do, rubbing the sides forward and padding down the back. He views his handsome living room.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS179
Lamar bites down on his pipe.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS180
SOMEONE sees SOMEONE watching.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS181
She raises her window. Later in class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS182
SOMEONE doffs his glasses and beams. He sees the female Lacrosse player watching his googly eyed response.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS183
SOMEONE eyes his professor.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS184
He winks at her. SOMEONE eyes him flatly, then looks to her right.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS185
Talk about dance steps sleeps.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS186
An eraser hits him and he jolts awake.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS187
She regards SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS188
His smile wilts and he nervously glances aside. SOMEONE looks to the center.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS189
SOMEONE points.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS190
SOMEONE frowns studiously.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS191
At Talia's photo, teacher's pet.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS192
I read the course pad.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS193
The professor's hand reaches out. SOMEONE flips his cellphone shut and hands it over. Standing over him, SOMEONE angrily shakes the phone. Now at a storage facility.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS194
SOMEONE bends over, his cotton-clad rear inadvertently mooning SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS195
Takes off his shades and glares at SOMEONE. She shrugs then drapes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS196
SOMEONE waggles his bottoms into the pants.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS197
Puts his shades back on.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS198
Now SOMEONE's scooter sits parked outside of SOMEONE's Restaurant. Inside, he pours coffee for group of older men.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS199
men playing cards. He sets down the pot and sits by SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS200
SOMEONE eyes him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS201
He doffs his glasses.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS202
Carlos resumes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS203
Raul nods grimly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS204
Now SOMEONE cracks an egg.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS205
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand. Now in class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS206
The students look over their shoulders. SOMEONE wears vampire fangs.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS207
SOMEONE hangs his head, SOMEONE wipes her brow.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS208
His chest. Now our view follow SOMEONE as he weaves through traffic o0n his blue scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS209
SOMEONE smiles.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS210
SOMEONE hands over his cell. Later he talks with to the professor outside.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS211
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS212
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch her go. SOMEONE low
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS213
parked outside donut prince.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS214
SOMEONE sits in the car with a pen and a slip of paper. Rain trickles down.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS215
The square of paper aside and grabs another.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS216
An SUV parks in front of her car.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS217
SOMEONE drinks from her travel cup.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS218
Peering ahead, she notices something and sets the cup back down. She gawks as SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave the SUV for the donut shop.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS219
Windshield wipers swish before her view of the duo closing their umbrellas and entering.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS220
She feeds SOMEONE a bite.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS221
They return to SOMEONE's SUV.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS222
Later, SOMEONE enters the classroom wearing a tasseled scarf.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS223
SOMEONE enters.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS224
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS225
As SOMEONE enters, SOMEONE adjusts the podium.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS226
She puts down a box then crosses to her desk at the back of the room. SOMEONE draws a paper slip from the box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS227
SOMEONE heads for the podium. SOMEONE seated at the desk and checks her watch.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS228
SOMEONE looks up at a clock, which reads two minutes to eight. He scans his fellow students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS229
He fidgets with the paper slip.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS230
SOMEONE glares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS232
She gives him a trendy dark rimmed pair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS233
She wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him on the cheek.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS234
SOMEONE takes a seat opposite them. SOMEONE regards him uneasily.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS235
SOMEONE glares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS236
Later, SOMEONE rides glumly as her husband drives. A dessert box sits on the dashboard.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS237
SOMEONE rolls her eyes at him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS238
SOMEONE stares ahead, her jaw hanging open.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS239
She picks up a fistful of pebbles from a tree planter, hurls them after the departing car, then staggers off. Now she sits cross-legged on a bus stop bench in front of a row of dark
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS240
with the flow of traffic the street
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS241
SOMEONE sneers at her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS243
She puts on her high heeled pumps.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS244
She stands. SOMEONE frowns.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS245
She looks at him with a withering gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS246
He Drags his lips in an affable
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS247
Now riding behind him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS249
To the landing outside her apartment. Turning she finds SOMEONE behind her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS250
She looks around.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS251
SOMEONE searches a potted plant.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS252
She examines her door locks.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS253
In between SOMEONE and the door SOMEONE unlocks it.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS254
SOMEONE returns the key tin to its pot, then keeps his back to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS255
SOMEONE's brow furrows as he listens.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS256
He rolls his eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS257
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS258
Facing her, SOMEONE takes in her drunken grin.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS259
She shows her ring.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS260
She smiles through half closed eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS261
SOMEONE frowns.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS262
SOMEONE gives him a playful grin and SOMEONE stares at her with concerned eyes. She sways slightly, her hands joint beneath her chin and her gaze softens. As she grabs him, SOMEONE wraps his arms around her waist. They kiss.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS263
Her off her feet and she slaps.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS266
He digs in the plants pot, finds the key.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS267
Pressing her hands to the door the teacher peers through a peep hole and sees SOMEONE as he joyfully move around.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS268
passenger door arrives at SOMEONE's apartment building.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS269
SOMEONE's husband climbs out.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS270
He raps against the trunk, the cab pulls away.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS271
Cheesecake drips from the takeout box in his hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS272
He lumbers on to the sidewalk and approaches the apartment building.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS273
On the landing, he finds the contents of his home office. Multiple copies of the same book sit in stacks around his computer, which displays a porn site.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS274
Box and it splatters against the door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS275
In class SOMEONE wears sunglasses.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS276
Grabbing a skateboard, SOMEONE smirks at SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS277
The middle-aged student gathers his things and makes his way towards SOMEONE's table at the back of the room. She sits stiffly, her large dark sunglasses masking most of her expression.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS278
SOMEONE offers a tender smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS279
SOMEONE's hopeful smile fades.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS280
SOMEONE's brow knits in a wounded look.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS281
She gazes off.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS282
She gives a brisk headshake then returns her attention to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS283
With his lips pressed in a solemn line SOMEONE gives a respectful nod. SOMEONE's chin twitches as she firmly returns the gesture.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS284
As he turns away, SOMEONE's shoulders sag.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS285
Chain swings from SOMEONE's pocket as he pulls his bag over his shoulder. Sitting motionless, the teacher gazes after him, then bows her head as he exits. Now at home, SOMEONE packs papers into a large accordion file. He places a checkmark on the last line of a list. Picking up a key, he eyes a handwritten tag tied to it with string, then throws it in the file.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS286
He rides his scooter down a street.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS287
He gives her the accordion files.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS288
With a triumphant smirk he turns on his heel and strides out of the bank. Now at the yard sale, he smokes a pipe with Lamar.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS289
SOMEONE gives him a thoughtful look.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS290
A mother and daughter arrive with a measuring tape.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS291
While lying in bed, SOMEONE wipes a tear from the corner of her eye.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS292
Still in her pajamas, she opens a windows blinds. As she peers outside, falling
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS293
rain reflects against the glass. Lingering by the window
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS294
from a mug. Now in class she walks among her students with a box of folded slips of paper. Each student draws one.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS295
SOMEONE draws a topic and reads it.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS296
SOMEONE draws his.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS297
SOMEONE the Lacrosse player reads her topic.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS298
SOMEONE strolls up to the podium and sets the cardboard box on top. Her students gather there.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS299
Picking up a notebook, she heads to the back of the classroom.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS300
SOMEONE removes his reading glasses, then gazes after her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS301
He follows the other students out. Now SOMEONE walks down the hall to her office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS302
SOMEONE gapes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS303
SOMEONE looks over.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS304
With her gaze fixed on SOMEONE's SOMEONE twitches a faint, crooked smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS305
SOMEONE enters her office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS306
Now in Economics.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS307
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS308
SOMEONE stands his class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS309
He regards his sober students with wide eyes. SOMEONE taps his pen.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS310
SOMEONE's smile fades.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS311
She shows her lower back.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS312
SOMEONE touches it. Watching them, SOMEONE knocks on the window.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS313
He throws up his hand and turns away.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS314
He gets on his scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS315
Now in the kitchen at SOMEONE's, SOMEONE transfers a grilled sandwich on to a plate, garnishes the meal and sets the order on a pickup or a paperback.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS316
He highlights a passage near the end. Now a view through
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS317
booth consulting notes and typing on a laptop.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS318
Scooter through his neighborhood.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS319
He passes the neighbor walking a dog, then
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS320
His scooter's headlights briefly illuminates red-striped diagonally across the sign.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS322
The aging man removes his helmet.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS323
It's warmly lit window show a family milling about inside. SOMEONE stands and
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS324
He sweeps his gaze over the surrounding neighborhood.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS325
The idyllic tranquil moment, then turns away and grimly heads inside.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS327
He looks at the now empty house, then exits, shutting the door beside him. Outside Lamar sits on SOMEONE's sofa, which rests on the front lawn among his other belongings. SOMEONE brings SOMEONE his box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS328
SOMEONE works on a car.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS329
An approaching BMW sports a pizza joint sign on its.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS330
The beefy U Mart exec.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS331
SOMEONE stares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS332
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a twenty.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS333
SOMEONE averts his gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS334
He reaches into his pocket.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS335
Lamar gives him three lottery tickets.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS336
Two kids ride past them.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS337
SOMEONE disappear as SOMEONE follow.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS341
Delivery boy hands her a pizza box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS342
SOMEONE smirks.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS343
In a pizza box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS344
Driver side door opens SOMEONE places her heels on the ground
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS345
She slides her feet into them. Now SOMEONE strolls the campus.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS347
He scoops the litter up. He drops the can in a recycle bin and throws out the paper.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS348
Joins SOMEONE on the walkway.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS349
Outside the classroom.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS350
He reaches for the door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS351
It opens. She mouths.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS352
SOMEONE grips off his palm.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS353
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE intently.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS354
SOMEONE beams.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS355
He meets SOMEONE's gaze, she grins broadly in reply.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS356
Later in economics, Professor SOMEONE watches his students from his desk. He caps a thermos then sets it near a collection of cellphones and sips from the thermos cup. Sitting at the long tables, the econ students diligently work on their exams. SOMEONE stands. He collects his bag and papers and makes his way to the professor's desk.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS357
He returns SOMEONE's smart phone.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS358
As SOMEONE heads out of the lecture hall the professor lifts his thermos.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS360
Taking a sip, she stares to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS361
SOMEONE comma SOMEONE, a cursor blinks beside an A.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS362
SOMEONE considers, then adds a plus.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS363
She briefly touches her flushed cheeks.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS364
SOMEONE enters following her raven haired
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS365
SOMEONE notices her. SOMEONE glances at him with a smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS366
Who shares a booth with SOMEONE spots SOMEONE too.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS367
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE's booth.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS368
SOMEONE smiles at her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS369
She smiles sincerely.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS370
As SOMEONE heads away, SOMEONE turns back to her friend.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS371
SOMEONE glances out the window.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS372
He sits among the greatly diminished headcount.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS373
Bored elsewhere, SOMEONE finishes writing the word care next to her course title. English 40, Shakespeare the Politician. She faces a handful of students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS374
Door in the back opens.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS375
She smiles as SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the Lacrosse player hurry in.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS376
SOMEONE subdues a delighted smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS377
SOMEONE slaps his forehead. SOMEONE glances at his friends then slumps in his seat, as SOMEONE distributes a handout.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS378
Later the auburn haired professor walks down the narrow corridor toward her office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS382
Horton number seven. A doodled black crown marks the bottom as his signature. Closing her eyes, SOMEONE gives a wide
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS383
She slips the note off the bin.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS384
Displays an arrow moving along the map as she drives.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS13
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a bemused frown.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS14
Muffled click.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS15
In the ward, a male nurse tends to a burly patient on his side.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS16
SOMEONE's gloved hand twist the tube.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS17
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS18
Where SOMEONE and SOMEONE sanitize their hands.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS19
They bump fists.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS20
Now at the SOMEONE' two-story colonial, a red family crest hangs in SOMEONE's basement layer. It reads, Certavi et Vici Byrnes. A framed photo shows SOMEONE with a Bedouin, dressed as a Bedouin. In another, he shoulder-to-shoulder with President SOMEONE W. Bush. Sepia-toned photo shows dates, men, and officers resembling SOMEONE. A shelf holds books on genealogy. On a bulletin board, headshots form a smartly right-angled family tree. SOMEONE frowns at photos of Deborah Banks and Dr. Robert Banks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS21
He takes down Robert's photo. Now in their bedroom, SOMEONE packs a suitcase.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS22
Holds his chest but quickly smiles.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS23
Now as SOMEONE drives, his cell reads incoming call. Mom Focker.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS24
On a studio. The Bohemian mother talks on the phone.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS25
SOMEONE tosses earpiece aside. In his layer, SOMEONE honkers at his desk.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS26
Using an X-ACTO knife, he neatly cuts a wedding picture of Dr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE down the middle. He folds Dr. SOMEONE's half, tears it in two, and shoves it in a wastebasket. Eyeing SOMEONE's photo, the ex-CIA agent rubs his chest.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS27
He places two fingers alongside his carotid.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS28
As his Siamese cat eyes him from a footstool, SOMEONE dials his cellphone.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS29
SOMEONE turns on his polygraph machine then tears open his button down.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS31
The cat observes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS32
SOMEONE Skypes them from a yacht.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS33
Bikini clog beauty approaches SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS34
Nuzzling and kissing him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS35
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE give the departing hottie a playful smack on the rear.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS36
SOMEONE's lasagna.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS37
SOMEONE glances at his family.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS38
He enters a bedroom.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS39
SOMEONE swivels in his chair.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS40
SOMEONE lifts his brow.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS41
He points to a photo of SOMEONE on the family tree.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS42
SOMEONE shifts his thoughtful gaze.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS43
We view him through window blinds.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS44
He stares unflinchingly.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS45
Gazing out the window, SOMEONE lowers his phone. With a strange smile, he strolls back into the kitchen where SOMEONE looks over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS46
He lifts her brow.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS47
SOMEONE eyes his daughter.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS48
Chewing her food, she turns away. SOMEONE shifts his gaze to his son, SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS49
He looks up.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS50
With a calm look, SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE, his hands folded.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS51
SOMEONE holds up quieting fingers.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS52
SOMEONE closes her mouth.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS53
He eyes him firmly.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS54
SOMEONE takes a small bite.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS55
As SOMEONE gives a satisfied look, SOMEONE vomits.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS56
Daytime, puffy clouds.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS59
Its window, he opens it then jogs across the street to the SOMEONE' car.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS60
With one hand on SOMEONE's waist and the other on his neck, SOMEONE kisses both of the older man's cheeks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS61
He slaps his hands to SOMEONE's face and kisses him again.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS62
Later at the dinner table.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS63
SOMEONE picks up his glass.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS64
He winks at SOMEONE then leaves.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS65
He takes it out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS66
SOMEONE's smile disappears.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS67
As he carves, SOMEONE peeks over the table.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS68
SOMEONE winces as SOMEONE mangles the bird.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS70
SOMEONE takes his hand. SOMEONE places his other one over it.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS71
SOMEONE gazes at her.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS72
SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn to SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS73
He squeezes the back of SOMEONE's neck and the boy goes limp, his eyes closed.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS74
He sets him on the couch.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS75
SOMEONE sets a hand on SOMEONE's other shoulder.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS76
They both pat his face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS77
Morning, SOMEONE feels SOMEONE's flushed brow as she lies in bed.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS78
He and SOMEONE drive into the city.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS79
SOMEONE rumples his lips into a frown.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS80
SOMEONE's face hardens.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS81
Now, a handful of children play in the courtyard of a glass-paneled building. Inside an auditorium, a blonde woman grins at the audience as she strolls on stage.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS82
A slide show starts.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS83
A photo shows surgeons.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS84
Children sketch a shirtless model.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS85
In the courtyard, young children in cheerleading uniforms do backflip.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS86
They give confused looks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS87
Their smiles fade.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS88
Later, they pull up to the new house where some construction workers take a break in the yard. A dump truck of sand sits in the driveway.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS89
An orange sports car zooms past
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS90
Then swings into a U-turn and parks behind SOMEONE's car. SOMEONE climbs out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS91
He hops at the bottom of the drive.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS92
He hits door, sand cascades onto SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS93
SOMEONE race over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS94
He supports SOMEONE's head.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS95
SOMEONE glares.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS96
Later, SOMEONE swabs his ears.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS97
SOMEONE touches his cheek.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS98
SOMEONE returns to the phone.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS99
SOMEONE listens from under the bed.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS100
Later, SOMEONE sits with her as she pretends to shoot green toy soldiers with tan ones.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS101
SOMEONE nods.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS102
SOMEONE's eyes shift.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS103
Later, SOMEONE arrives at home.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS104
Sees SOMEONE stow a bag in a closet.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS105
As SOMEONE hurries down the hall, SOMEONE glares after him. On a table, SOMEONE's phone vibrates. Turning to it, SOMEONE reads a text from SOMEONE, Can't wait to see you at the hotel tonight. Later SOMEONE walks outside, his briefcase clutched in one hand. SOMEONE sneaks after him, disguised in a windbreaker and bucket hat. As SOMEONE glances back, his father-in-law steps into some shadows.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS107
SOMEONE peers back around the corner.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS112
Frowning, SOMEONE sticks his head outside and glances up and down the platform.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS115
Door to SOMEONE's train car, SOMEONE steps inside.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS116
SOMEONE appears behind him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS117
Turns around.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS118
He stares at SOMEONE, who gives a halfhearted smile.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS121
They enter a convention room.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS122
Narrowing his eyes, SOMEONE shifts them mischievously.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS123
At the apartment, SOMEONE turns on a light in the coat closet. He crouches then inspects SOMEONE's hidden bag. With a furrowed brow, he finds pamphlets for Sustengo then removes a sample box.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS124
As he reads it, SOMEONE creeps up behind him wearing a trench coat over a negligee.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS125
She kisses his cheek.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS126
She unzips his jacket and he frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS127
She kisses her finger then blows him the kiss. As she leaves, SOMEONE eyes the sample box of Sustengo. Now at a bar, three doctors approach SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS128
He strolls over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS129
He wanders over to the bar.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS130
SOMEONE lifts his gaze to SOMEONE's face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS131
SOMEONE gives a nod and SOMEONE looks away. Later, SOMEONE opens the apartment door and steps into the dark living room.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS132
As he slides off his coat, a lamp shines its light on him. SOMEONE sits in an armchair beside it.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS133
SOMEONE shields his eyes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS134
SOMEONE holds up the box of Sustengo.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS135
SOMEONE brightens the light.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS136
SOMEONE hangs up his coat.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS137
As SOMEONE rises, SOMEONE stops and turns to him. He points to SOMEONE's crotch.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS138
SOMEONE steps closer.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS139
In the bathroom, SOMEONE pulls on Latex gloves then opens the needle and syringe.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS140
He gestures at the bulge in SOMEONE's pants.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS141
His shoulders heave as he reaches toward SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS142
As he readies the needle, two slippered feet walk down the hall.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS143
SOMEONE heads to the bathroom. He holds the knob.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS145
He congests himself as he walks down the hall toward SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS146
He gives two thumbs up then heads away. SOMEONE looks at her mother and winces.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS147
Now, SOMEONE tucks SOMEONE in.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS148
SOMEONE lets SOMEONE shut the door then enters anyway.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS149
SOMEONE stands by.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS150
SOMEONE glowers.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS151
Later in the hallway, SOMEONE gently shuts SOMEONE's door.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS152
Without breaking eye contact, the two men circle. SOMEONE gives a mock scowl. He and SOMEONE back away from each other.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS153
SOMEONE tauntingly shrugs his hands apart. SOMEONE does the same. SOMEONE repeats the gesture. Then they go their separate ways.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS154
Daytime, SOMEONE peers out the cracked open door of the guest bedroom while on his cell.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS155
He glances back.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS156
Later at a computer, SOMEONE types A-N-D-I-G-A-R-C-I-A into the Google search field and gets back image results and links for the handsome dark-haired actor. He adds the keyword, Chicago and finds a link to a Myspace profile. Leaning in, SOMEONE opens the zebra print page then scrolls down to find the photo of SOMEONE kissing SOMEONE on the cheek. The retired CIA man reads the caption, "Crazy night at the Hilton." He minimizes the page as SOMEONE enters.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS158
SOMEONE joins the rest of the family. SOMEONE checks his watch.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS159
SOMEONE gives them a kiss.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS161
The vehicles park and they step out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS162
SOMEONE lifts his shirt to reveal his lower back. The other study a large tattoo of SOMEONE's smiling face above the banner, forever.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS163
It's only half of SOMEONE's face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS164
Later in SOMEONE's office.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS165
They swap an icy look.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS166
Now, SOMEONE sits in an easel.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS167
The family watches behind a mirrored window.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS168
She shows SOMEONE a phony eye chart.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS169
SOMEONE starts the timer.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS170
Back at the easel.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS171
SOMEONE recoils.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS172
A stick figure holds a syringe to another's penis.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS173
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS174
SOMEONE smiles proudly toward the mirrored window. SOMEONE gapes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS176
On the playground. They spot a surveillance camera. The boy glares at his dad.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS179
SOMEONE beams.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS180
Now, SOMEONE approaches the nurses' station.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS181
SOMEONE pulls him aside.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS183
Back in the hall. SOMEONE emerges.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS184
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, who holds an arm around SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS185
SOMEONE presses the elevator button.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS188
He park at the new house's driveway.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS190
She leaves and SOMEONE stares ahead.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS191
Now in the new house, SOMEONE stands alone in the middle of an unfinished room. SOMEONE turns away from a three-foot hole in the wall and crosses to the front door, where he finds SOMEONE with a bottle of wine.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS198
Meanwhile, SOMEONE's car arrives out front.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS199
The retired CIA agent gets out and marches gravely toward the house.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS200
Glancing aside, he pauses and stares. His flashlight beam hits the license plate of SOMEONE's convertible. It reads, "RX GRRRL."
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS201
Killing his light, SOMEONE creeps around toward the side of the house.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS203
As SOMEONE moves through the shadows outside, SOMEONE takes off her blouse.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS204
SOMEONE pounces on him. Outside, SOMEONE pauses and turns. Finding a bay window, he steps close and peeks in. He sees SOMEONE in her bra and skirt.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS206
Her arms and legs wrapped around SOMEONE as she smothers him with kisses. His hands clenching her waist. He spins around the room erratically. SOMEONE looks away. His gaze heartbroken. He backs away from the window. He licks his lips, presses them tight, and leaves. Inside, lands - they knock heads - cut to black.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS207
His legs clad in white pants.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS208
In the pit, SOMEONE snores under SOMEONE. His eyes blink open and he gets his bearings. As SOMEONE arrives out back, SOMEONE's hand slaps down on the pit's rim.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS209
Straining with effort, he pulls himself up.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS210
SOMEONE stares and points at her.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS211
At the birthday party.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS213
SOMEONE nods.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS214
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS216
SOMEONE leaves his car with the valet. A monk greets him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS217
Approach chauffeured carts. Passing a valet stand, SOMEONE pauses to dance.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS218
He's off in a cart. SOMEONE stretches his quadriceps.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS219
Clinging by his legs, he opens his arms.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS220
SOMEONE turns and sees SOMEONE approaching.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS221
SOMEONE grins.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS223
SOMEONE opens a shoebox.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS224
Kissing as the twins hug them.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS225
He starts to cry. His tears landing on the stage below.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS226
He gets dizzily to his feet.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS227
As he hobbles off, a boy offers him his cotton candy. SOMEONE takes it and goes to a tent.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS228
Roz peeks inside and finds him sitting pensively.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS229
Now, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who sits.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS230
SOMEONE lifts his chin.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS231
SOMEONE eyes the drawing.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS232
SOMEONE scowls, holding a balloon.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS233
With a smile, he holds out a plate of cake. SOMEONE punches him in the nose.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS234
He punches him again.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS235
SOMEONE blocks a strike then hits SOMEONE in the face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS236
SOMEONE slides off his jacket.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS237
Pump his fists.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS238
He punches him then beckons.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS239
Removes his sweatshirt.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS240
SOMEONE raises his fists and the two men face off. As SOMEONE throws a punch, SOMEONE blocks him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS241
To push him away. The older man flings him into a giant ball pit. SOMEONE disappears below the balls.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS243
He glances around but sees only the playing
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS244
Behind him move then stop as he whip
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS245
They shift in another part of the pit.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS246
SOMEONE notices and stares with intense eyes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS249
Other balls shift and SOMEONE turns to them.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS250
Behind him, SOMEONE burst through the surface.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS251
Punches him. He grabs his son-in-law.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS253
Pulled over, SOMEONE kicks his leg back and hits again to a bouncy castle.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS255
Meanwhile, SOMEONE looks in the shoebox.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS256
In the grass, SOMEONE faces Jinx, who stares at him. The cat licks its lips then advances.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS257
He sniffs the lizard. Now, SOMEONE throws himself
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS259
Dangling for Jinx's mouth.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS260
As SOMEONE races past him after the cat, SOMEONE stops. His chest heaving.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS261
He stretches his shoulders back.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS262
Meanwhile, SOMEONE kisses her.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS264
SOMEONE lowers his arms.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS265
Outside, SOMEONE races after Jinx. He stops. SOMEONE lies on the ground clutching his chest. She sprints over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS267
His cat approaching.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS268
Pushing the cat's stomach like the Heimlich maneuver, he forces the lizard out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS269
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and SOMEONE returns his gaze to SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS270
He rubs SOMEONE's shoulder.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS271
Later, Medics wheel SOMEONE to an ambulance.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS272
He gives SOMEONE a look.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS273
SOMEONE winks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS274
In the ambulance.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS275
Again looks at SOMEONE. SOMEONE replaces the mask.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS278
He smiles as he holds SOMEONE's gaze.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS279
He pats SOMEONE's cheek. His smile growing wider.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS280
SOMEONE gives him a tender look.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS281
SOMEONE winks at him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS282
They lift the stretcher into their ridge.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS284
Now, snowfalls onto a group of SOMEONEers. Words appear, "Four Months Later."
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS286
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS287
He lifts his leg.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS288
Now in his basement lair, SOMEONE types on a computer.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS289
As Jinx looks on, SOMEONE types his name into a Google search window. He trails his cursor over the search results then selects a YouTube video. It's title, Nurse Rags on Psycho Father-in-Law. The image loads up showing SOMEONE speaking at the medical convention. SOMEONE scowls. The video plays.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS18
SOMEONE drives through dark streets and pulls into a car park.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS19
Morning Glory.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS20
SOMEONE hurries into a building. She walks down a corridor.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS21
She talks manically in a meeting.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS22
The meeting room is behind a studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS23
A guy in the meeting has fallen asleep in front of his computer.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS24
SOMEONE chuckles with one of her colleagues. A female presenter, SOMEONE, yawns and sits at a desk in the studio. A male presenter, Ralph Pollard, sits next to her and a make-up artist brushes him with powder.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS25
SOMEONE has headphones around her neck. She listens to one of them.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS26
Staff listen to headphones and watch screens.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS31
In the studio, SOMEONE has fallen asleep.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS32
SOMEONE holds a headphone to her ear.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS33
SOMEONE wakes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS34
A floor manager threw Post-It notes at her to wake her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS35
In the staff kitchen, SOMEONE gulps. In an office,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS36
her friend that told her the news, SOMEONE leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS37
The female presenter, SOMEONE, is onscreen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS38
A guy in the gallery directs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS39
The studio, now empty, SOMEONE stands in it with a pile of papers in one hand and two mugs in the other.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS40
She smiles and turns to leave.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS41
SOMEONE takes a t-shirt from a gift bag.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS42
It's a red t-shirt with the words, Yes, I accept in white. SOMEONE puts it on under a denim jacket.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS43
In her boss's office,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS44
tears well in her eyes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS45
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE. Her and other ex-colleagues are wearing Way to go, SOMEONE t-shirts. At her mum's.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS46
SOMEONE lowers her gaze. She nods miserably.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS47
SOMEONE's sitting in bed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS48
Her alarm goes off at 1:30.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS49
She hugs her knees, then folds her arms across her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS50
She fidgets and stares into space.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS51
She switches on the TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS52
She switches on another TV. On the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS53
In a diner.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS54
In the park.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS55
Now dressed in a suit, SOMEONE runs off a bus towards a ferry.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS56
On the other side of the river lies New York City.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS57
She walks through the smart IBS high rise with a tall, lean guy,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS58
SOMEONE SOMEONE
MORNING_GLORY_DVS59
She balls her fists.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS60
He eyes her wryly. She balls her fists tighter.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS61
SOMEONE looks down,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS62
then smiles sadly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS63
She gets up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS64
She opens the door and leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS65
Wearing a mournful expression, she trudges down a hallway and into a lift.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS67
A fair-haired guy of about 30 walks in behind her, glances at her,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS68
then turns to the lift buttons and push it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS69
He presses the button.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS70
As the lift doors are closing, a man jams his arms in the doors and pushes them open.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS71
SOMEONE watches the guy get into the lift.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS72
He's in his 60s and wears black-rimmed specs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS73
SOMEONE gawps at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS74
She puts her hand on her heart.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS75
The two guys get out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS76
SOMEONE jams her arm in the doors to stop them from closing.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS77
She strolls along the street outside, her shoulders hunched.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS78
She throws a bit of paper into a bin.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS79
She takes a call on her mobile.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS80
She hangs up the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS81
She jumps in the air. Pigeons fly off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS82
Sped-up footage. She packs up her apartment until it's completely empty.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS83
She carries the last things into the removal truck and closes the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS84
She jogs out of a subway in New York.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS85
She runs across a busy road towards IBS.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS86
The skyscraper is white with large, dark windows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS87
Inside, SOMEONE waits on a bench in the wood-paneled reception area. There's a smart, gold desk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS88
The attendant is watching a small TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS89
He smirks.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS90
Then he takes SOMEONE's mug and goes. SOMEONE straightens up her fridge and knocks on a door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS91
The door handle comes off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS92
They smile.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS93
SOMEONE smiles uncertainly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS94
She raises her brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS95
SOMEONE glances around at everyone talking at once.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS96
SOMEONE licks her lips and turns to SOMEONE with interest. SOMEONE grins. SOMEONE frowns and pauses. She looks up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS97
SOMEONE heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS98
He steps back into the room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS99
She hits the table. SOMEONE loses his smirk and stares sourly at her. She holds his gaze.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS100
A member of staff takes a photo on his phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS101
SOMEONE leaves. The others gape at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS102
SOMEONE giggles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS104
SOMEONE walks off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS105
SOMEONE hurries along the street. She dials on her mobile, then holds it to her ear.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS106
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch a horse-faced news anchor on TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS107
She glances at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS108
SOMEONE's heading out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS109
She has a box of tapes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS110
SOMEONE rolls his eyes sardonically as he turns to camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS111
A woman is waiting for SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS112
SOMEONE stares at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS113
SOMEONE sits at a bench outside. She's eating a salad and going through the contract with a marker pen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS114
Her brow is furrowed with intense concentration.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS115
She lifts the contract and highlights a line.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS116
She strides across long grass.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS117
A man stands on the crest of the hill she's climbing with a shotgun in his hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS118
She stops just short of him,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS120
throws her arms out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS121
He turns to her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS122
SOMEONE shoots two pheasants flying above the trees. SOMEONE claps her hands over her ears
MORNING_GLORY_DVS123
then follows SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS124
SOMEONE beams. Frowning, SOMEONE stares, lines showing on his forehead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS125
SOMEONE smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS126
He walks off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS128
they stare.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS129
SOMEONE steps slowly across the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS130
SOMEONE stands at the other side of it, his hand in his pockets, gazing down at the floor.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS131
SOMEONE raises his brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS132
She nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS133
She smiles and turns back to the rest of the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS134
They change the name on SOMEONE's dressing room and paint over the huge poster of him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS135
They walk through the office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS136
A fruit plate
MORNING_GLORY_DVS137
He hands her an orchid.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS138
He picks up a newspaper and sits down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS139
SOMEONE takes the orchid to SOMEONE's dressing room and knocks.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS140
SOMEONE sets down the flower.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS141
SOMEONE tosses a card aside.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS142
SOMEONE goes from one dressing room to the other.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS143
SOMEONE marches from one end of the corridor to the other, then finds the central point.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS144
SOMEONE and SOMEONE meet
MORNING_GLORY_DVS145
in the middle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS146
SOMEONE stares at her blankly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS147
SOMEONE goes into his room and slams the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS148
SOMEONE marches off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS149
SOMEONE and SOMEONE on a photo shoot.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS150
SOMEONE hands his specs to an assistant.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS151
They smile and pose. SOMEONE links her arm through his.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS152
She takes off her jacket.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS153
They stand close.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS154
SOMEONE walks through the office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS156
She stares at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS157
SOMEONE tries to suppress giggles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS158
Everyone turns to look at SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS159
SOMEONE smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS160
SOMEONE smiles anxiously.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS161
SOMEONE plays with her fringe nervously. SOMEONE chucks an apple core past her into a bin.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS162
SOMEONE saunters off casually.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS163
SOMEONE runs up steps.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS164
He glares.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS165
He screams silently. She heads a meeting outside.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS166
It's SOMEONE. He points at SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS167
SOMEONE grins and waves,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS168
then heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS169
SOMEONE covers her face.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS170
SOMEONE drinks a glass of beer at a bar and chats to a friend.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS171
SOMEONE enters the bar.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS172
She poses and looks over at SOMEONE who turns.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS174
and notices her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS175
She waves
MORNING_GLORY_DVS176
and accidentally throws her phone up in the air.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS177
In a booth
MORNING_GLORY_DVS178
a tall, slender blonde kisses him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS179
SOMEONE sinks back into his seat and the woman leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS180
SOMEONE frowns with confusion as SOMEONE hurries off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS181
He comes out of the bar
MORNING_GLORY_DVS182
and presses herself against the wall in shame.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS184
At the studio
MORNING_GLORY_DVS185
he gets up and walks off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS186
SOMEONE watches TV in his dressing room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS187
SOMEONE has a notebook.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS188
He's drinking whisky.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS189
He stands up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS190
On TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS191
SOMEONE backs out of SOMEONE's dressing room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS192
In the toilet, she bangs her head against the dryer.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS193
She stops and turns to regard herself in the mirror.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS194
She tidies up her fringe.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS195
She makes her way through a large, open-plan office. The sign reads, IBS News.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS196
She sidles along, peering into a private office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS197
In the office, SOMEONE sits at a desk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS198
She pulls the door closed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS199
She's sitting on a sofa. She bangs her head on a lamp above her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS200
She puts down two heavy bags.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS201
She mimes rowing.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS202
Her goofy smile fades.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS203
In a large, plush apartment, SOMEONE and SOMEONE make out. He leans her over a worktop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS204
She checks her watch.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS205
SOMEONE's taken her skirt off. They roll over the back of the couch onto it. Suddenly, SOMEONE pulls back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS206
SOMEONE eyes her dubiously. She looks at him sharply.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS207
She grabs her bags and runs out without her skirt on.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS208
She grabs her bags and runs out without her skirt on. without her skirt on.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS209
SOMEONE picks up her skirt
MORNING_GLORY_DVS210
and waits for her to run back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS211
She kisses him and leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS212
SOMEONE asks a tubby, middle-aged woman sitting at the bar in her lines.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS213
She comes out onto the dark streets where several musicians are basking.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS214
Next she visits the Algonquin.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS215
As she runs out, a model is being photographed at the entrance.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS216
She runs out of another cocktail lounge, then another bar just as two guys are thrown out into the street.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS217
She pulls open the doors of the 21 Club in Manhattan.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS218
She walks into the wood-paneled bar and spots SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS219
She takes a deep breath and heads towards him with a look of grim determination.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS220
She raises her brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS221
She shoves him into a taxi.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS222
The taxi drives off without her. It pulls up outside an apartment building.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS223
They walk slowly into SOMEONE's dark apartment.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS224
SOMEONE walks through different rooms in the huge apartment.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS225
SOMEONE walks through a dark room towards another lamp lit room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS226
He eats a nut.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS227
He wanders off through the dark apartment as she sets up her laptop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS228
He stops and turns back to wish her goodnight.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS230
SOMEONE sits on the sofa in front of her laptop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS231
Later she dozes in front of it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS232
She nods off, but awakens as her head drops.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS233
She sits upright again.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS234
She nods off again.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS235
She opens her eyes and blinks. Her vision is blurred.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS236
She falls asleep once more.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS237
She collapses over onto the sofa.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS238
SOMEONE stands over her with a rain stick which makes the sound reminiscent of rain.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS239
SOMEONE wakes with a start.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS240
SOMEONE's wearing a cream dressing gown.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS241
He plods off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS242
SOMEONE buries her head in a cushion then sits upright.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS243
She races into the kitchen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS245
He's whisking eggs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS246
They head into the Daybreak offices.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS247
The cast and crew all gawp at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS248
SOMEONE grins sheepishly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS249
The crew sits in the gallery with their headphones on.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS250
SOMEONE grins irritated.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS251
SOMEONE and SOMEONE in the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS252
SOMEONE shrugs on air.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS254
The caption, Sexual Offender, remained under the photo of SOMEONE SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS255
SOMEONE stares into the distance wearily.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS256
SOMEONE watches Daybreak in his office. The attendant at the reception desk has it on his small TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS257
They both gaze into the camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS258
SOMEONE's smile vanishes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS259
SOMEONE gets up and heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS261
He's getting his shoes shined.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS262
SOMEONE storms off, throwing her arms out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS263
Dusk falls over New York.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS264
SOMEONE opens his front door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS265
She grabs him and kisses him hard.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS266
She wraps her arms around his neck and they make out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS267
She reaches into her pocket for her phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS268
He grabs it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS269
He won't let her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS270
He puts it in the fridge.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS271
He carries her into his bedroom.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS272
SOMEONE wakes. SOMEONE isn't there.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS273
He sits up and eyes the empty space in his bed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS274
He goes into the living room where SOMEONE is watching the news and typing on her laptop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS275
He smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS276
She shifts and looks at him uncertainly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS277
SOMEONE smiles gleefully. She picks up her laptop and jogs off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS278
She stops
MORNING_GLORY_DVS279
and goes back to SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS280
She kisses him tenderly on the lips and heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS281
It's dark with the first wisps of pink morning light as SOMEONE strides over a bridge.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS282
The moon still shines in the sky.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS283
SOMEONE sits in the Daybreak office and smiles to herself,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS284
fiddling with a strand of hair.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS285
SOMEONE glances up at her as she gazes ahead,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS286
a wistful smile on her face.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS287
He grins to himself.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS288
She shrugs at him and he mocks her gesture.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS290
She slams her hands on the table.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS291
SOMEONE's on the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS292
They walk along the street.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS294
She took a photo.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS295
SOMEONE scowls, then turns away.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS296
On air,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS297
SOMEONE points upwards.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS298
A guy delivers a note to SOMEONE. She glances disapprovingly at SOMEONE, then reads the note, raises her hand, and points upwards.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS299
She gets up, taking a flask with her. In SOMEONE's office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS300
She cocks her head.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS301
SOMEONE frowns.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS302
Horrified, SOMEONE sits down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS303
SOMEONE takes off his glasses and throws them down. SOMEONE gazes down miserably.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS304
Her shoulders sag.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS305
He makes a call.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS306
SOMEONE sits alone on a sofa, going through papers.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS307
On the verge of tears, she rubs her nose.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS308
She puts her hand over her eyes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS309
Onset, a stage manager reads out words to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS310
She seethes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS312
She storms onto the set.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS313
They watch in the news office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS314
SOMEONE drops down out of the camera shot.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS315
A producer watches in the gallery.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS316
SOMEONE struggles with the door that leads to SOMEONE's office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS317
She heads out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS318
SOMEONE's slack-jawed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS319
SOMEONE heads back into the gallery.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS320
SOMEONE looks nervous.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS321
In his office, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE on TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS322
In the studio, SOMEONE cringes. SOMEONE and SOMEONE are glued to the screens.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS323
Watching the TV, the attendant is cracking up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS324
After the show
MORNING_GLORY_DVS325
she stares at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS326
He raises his brows and shoves a pastry into his mouth.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS327
SOMEONE beams.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS328
Live on Daybreak, SOMEONE is dressed in a sumo suit.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS329
Out on the plaza, she wrestles with a real sumo who bashes her repeatedly with his flabby belly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS330
On set
MORNING_GLORY_DVS335
she handles a sugar glider, a raven, and a skunk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS336
SOMEONE's in a plane.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS337
He jumps out strapped to another guy.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS338
With his mouth stretched open, his cheeks jiggle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS339
In the studio, SOMEONE slinks down towards the desk with an agonized expression.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS341
She gives the frog a sloppy kiss.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS342
SOMEONE lands, skidding along grass. SOMEONE plays the bagpipes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS343
50 Cent in the Daybreak studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS344
SOMEONE performs with him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS345
SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance in the gallery.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS346
SOMEONE's in an aircraft.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS347
He faints.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS348
His head lolls backwards as he spirals upwards.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS349
She talks to the producer in the corridor. In the studio, SOMEONE is getting a tattoo on his ass.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS350
SOMEONE gawps. SOMEONE's stony faced.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS351
Some papers.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS352
SOMEONE glances down awkwardly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS353
SOMEONE watches a man screwing on a door handle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS354
SOMEONE smiles, impressed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS355
SOMEONE's fallen asleep on a couch. SOMEONE throws a pencil at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS356
SOMEONE is jogging. SOMEONE races after him with the ratings.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS357
In a SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS358
To SOMEONE
MORNING_GLORY_DVS359
SOMEONE jogs off. SOMEONE stands there holding the bag, figures and sags.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS360
In SOMEONE's apartment they have dinner together.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS361
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS362
He shakes his head. Then pulls a face.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS363
She switches off the TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS364
She looks at graphs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS365
He eyes her gravely.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS366
She carries her plate away.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS367
She leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS369
It's dark. She sits in the back of a taxi and presses her hand to her forehead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS370
Morning - a golden sky over the silhouetted skyscrapers of Manhattan.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS371
SOMEONE's in his dressing room on the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS372
SOMEONE overhears. SOMEONE shuts his door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS373
Everyone sits back down. SOMEONE removes his spectacles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS374
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE in surprise.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS375
SOMEONE smiles at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS377
She stands by a monument.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS378
An IBS van pulls up and she runs to it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS379
SOMEONE's in the front.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS380
She gets in the back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS381
They pull up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS382
SOMEONE, who's striding toward the Colonial-style clapboard country mansion, stops in his tracks.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS383
SOMEONE nods gravely and beckons SOMEONE, the cameraman.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS384
He marches towards the mansion. SOMEONE follows with his camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS385
On the phone,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS386
SOMEONE knocks on the Governor's door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS387
The Governor answers the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS388
He points.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS389
SOMEONE grabs a weather vane.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS390
He trips.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS392
Squad cars pull up outside the mansion.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS393
On air, SOMEONE glances at the squad cars.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS394
Watching, SOMEONE beams.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS395
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a bench. SOMEONE smokes a cigar.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS396
He frowns thoughtfully.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS397
SOMEONE looks down and shakes her head.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS398
She smiles at him warmly. He nods pensively and gazes ahead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS399
She meets his gaze directly and he turns in towards her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS400
Her brow pinched, SOMEONE glances down at the ground.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS401
SOMEONE looks down and pinches the material of his trousers nervously.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS402
He gives her a gentle smile, then looks down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS403
SOMEONE and SOMEONE head back into the Daybreak offices to find the team gathered around a table.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS404
They all stand and clap as the pair enter.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS405
SOMEONE leans over and kisses SOMEONE on the cheek, then wipes off her lipstick SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS406
She sits opposite SOMEONE in his office, as he leafs through graphs and charts.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS407
She eyes him with anticipation wearing a slight smile and raising her brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS408
SOMEONE smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS409
She stares in surprise.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS410
Her eyes widen and dart about.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS411
He smiles at her. Her jaw slackens. She looks down. Her eyes flit from side to side.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS412
Their eyes meet.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS413
SOMEONE lowers her gaze again and frowns.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS414
Deep in thought.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS415
SOMEONE drinks in a bar at a table with a group of friends.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS416
They all laugh and joke with one another.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS417
SOMEONE turns to the window with his brow furrowed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS418
SOMEONE stands gazing in from outside. She smiles at him nervously.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS419
SOMEONE stands on the street outside with SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS420
They sit inside the local bar where they first went for a drink.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS421
She smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS422
SOMEONE nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS423
Coming out of IBS.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS424
He glowers at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS425
SOMEONE fights back tears.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS427
SOMEONE looks down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS428
He hangs his head, glances up briefly, then walks away, putting on his sunglasses.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS429
SOMEONE stands on the plaza, her chest heaving, her eyes wet with tears.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS430
She turns and heads back towards the entrance of the building.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS431
In the Daybreak offices, she stands in a doorway staring down, and puts her hand on her hip.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS432
A woman approaches carrying a note.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS433
The woman leaves the note with SOMEONE and heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS434
Later, SOMEONE sits on the couch with the note still in her hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS435
SOMEONE remembers.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS436
SOMEONE laughs and jokes with a couple of other members of staff.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS437
SOMEONE chats animatedly with colleagues.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS438
One of them throws a screwed up piece of paper at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS439
They all smile.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS440
Two members of staff chat and study a piece of paper. SOMEONE walks through the corridor behind them.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS441
He gazes in through the window, his craggy face set in its usual curmudgeonly expression.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS442
SOMEONE shakes her head and looks down at the note in her hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS444
SOMEONE stands outside the NBC building and examines the note in her hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS445
She looks up at the enormous skyscraper
MORNING_GLORY_DVS446
then heads in.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS447
She heads through the spacious lobby with classical style paintings on the walls
MORNING_GLORY_DVS448
and goes up to the reception desk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS449
At Daybreak, SOMEONE sighs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS450
SOMEONE stares ahead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS451
Daybreak plays on the screen in the interview.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS452
He comes into the gallery,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS453
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE's bewildered.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS454
He stops at a table of food.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS455
He steals food from a guy's takeaway container.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS456
The interview.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS457
SOMEONE hurries back onto the set with the food.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS458
She eyes the screen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS459
The interviewers all turn to see SOMEONE breaking eggs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS460
SOMEONE gawps.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS461
He pours in whisked eggs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS462
He looks into the camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS463
On the phone,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS464
SOMEONE nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS465
SOMEONE runs through the lobby.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS466
She leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS467
She runs past a huge golden statue by a fountain.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS468
SOMEONE sprinkles salt into the frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS469
SOMEONE grinds pepper onto the frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS470
SOMEONE races up steps and across a plaza filled with trees and plants.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS471
In the gallery,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS472
SOMEONE bends down to pick something up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS473
SOMEONE races across a road.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS474
SOMEONE opens a large oven on the set.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS475
SOMEONE runs past the IBS building. Pigeons scatter in her wake.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS476
SOMEONE runs a spatula around the edge of the saucepan in which he has cooked the frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS477
SOMEONE steps, light-footed, through the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS478
She wears a pretty, floaty dress.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS479
She stops just off the set and watches SOMEONE
MORNING_GLORY_DVS480
who eventually looks up and spots her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS481
He looks down again
MORNING_GLORY_DVS482
then glances up and smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS483
SOMEONE smiles back. Tears glisten in her eyes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS484
SOMEONE grins. Her eyes sparkle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS485
SOMEONE sneaks up behind SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS486
SOMEONE touches his chest gently.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS487
SOMEONE tries his frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS488
SOMEONE beams and nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS489
MORNING_GLORY_DVS490
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who grins cheekily. SOMEONE waves to her from across the studio and she waves back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS491
SOMEONE presents a gift bag to her friend, SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS492
It's a t-shirt that reads, Welcome to Daybreak.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS493
SOMEONE smiles and hugs her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS494
SOMEONE ambles along with SOMEONE, chatting.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS495
SOMEONE's mum pins up a newspaper clipping on a notice board that reads Daybreak revitalized.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS496
She smiles proudly, tears in her eyes, and puts her hand over her mouth.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS497
SOMEONE reads a huge dictionary.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS498
A magician with an assistant saws SOMEONE in half.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS499
In SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE runs to the fridge
MORNING_GLORY_DVS500
and puts her phone in it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS501
SOMEONE goes into SOMEONE's dressing room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS502
He has a hand on her butt
MORNING_GLORY_DVS503
and her hand is over his.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS504
SOMEONE gazes down the corridor
MORNING_GLORY_DVS505
then shuts the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS506
A pink sky over New York.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS507
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll along together.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS26
The both stared straight ahead.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS27
No String Attached
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS28
Five years ago, a large white fraternity house with columns on the ground, white pediment at the front
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS40
Standing beside his buddy, SOMEONE, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS42
SOMEONE points a massive foam hand.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS44
SOMEONE slinks up behind the girl and dances in time with her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS49
It's her father's funeral.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS50
Standing by the coffin everyone's in black. Apart from SOMEONE who's wearing a bright yellow Michigan top and beige chinos
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS51
the men wear skullcaps.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS52
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE's attractive mom a big hug.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS54
Mourners gather at SOMEONE's family home, a colonial-style mansion with white walls, shuttered windows, and a red-tiled roof.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS55
Two boys run down the stairs.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS56
SOMEONE's mother, SOMEONE, is standing outside by a pretty rose garden.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS59
SOMEONE walks SOMEONE to his car, a blue BMW.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS60
He gets in the driving seat and SOMEONE leans by the door.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS61
Looking slightly lost he drives away.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS62
Pretty, dark-haired SOMEONE watches him with her arms folded.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS65
One year ago, a bright sunny day, the steel and glass skyscraper of Los Angeles gleam.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS66
People mill about at a farmer's market by an artificial lake.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS69
SOMEONE's friend SOMEONE is nearby. He's stocky guy with a friendly face he sees SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS70
SOMEONE's with a girl.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS71
SOMEONE walks over, SOMEONE's nearby watching.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS76
SOMEONE and SOMEONE smiled approvingly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS86
A guy shows a picture to the girls.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS93
SOMEONE walks down to see him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS95
SOMEONE lights the joint.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS96
He takes a script from his back.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS97
SOMEONE proudly points to the name on the cover page.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS98
SOMEONE takes a drag on the joint.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS100
SOMEONE raises his brows and Vanessa runs off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS102
SOMEONE has a drag.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS106
In a bar SOMEONE makes some calls.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS111
sunlight washes over SOMEONE's face.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS112
He frowns as he slowly wakes up on a couch.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS113
He opens his eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS114
He holds up his hand to block out the bright sunlight.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS117
She sits in the kitchen counter eating cereal.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS118
SOMEONE squints at her blearily.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS119
SOMEONE's naked apart from the towel he's clutching over his groin.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS121
He sits up and looks around.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS122
He hugs the cup and drinks.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS123
SOMEONE stands watching.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS124
SOMEONE looks up at her with his eye narrowed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS128
She smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS129
He goes to stand but stops himself.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS130
He clutches the towel over his penis.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS132
SOMEONE turns away SOMEONE sits on her bed and pulls on his jeans.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS133
She wiggles her hips and waves her hand around provocatively.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS134
She sits beside him and puts her arm around his shoulder.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS135
He clutches her knee.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS137
He undoes the belt in her blue robe.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS138
They gaze at each other for a moment,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS139
SOMEONE leans closer.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS140
and kisses SOMEONE passionately.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS141
He lays her on her back, gets on top of her, and pulls off her robe.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS145
Her chest heaves as he struggles with the packet.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS147
They make love.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS150
Outside the room, SOMEONE smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS153
He puts his hand over her mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS154
SOMEONE's mouth gapes. She gazes into Adams eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS155
Later they get dressed and SOMEONE hand SOMEONE his top.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS156
He puts it on.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS157
She smiles and pats his arm.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS158
At an outside restaurant SOMEONE checks messages on his iPhone, SOMEONE gets up.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS160
He frowns heavily.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS162
SOMEONE stands up.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS163
SOMEONE stops SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS164
With an awkward look she walks off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS166
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE go into to the restaurant SOMEONE wearily shakes his head.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS168
They high five.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS169
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walked past with their lunch.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS170
SOMEONE watches them go and get in SOMEONE's red Prius.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS171
SOMEONE's in the hospital cafeteria, SOMEONE comes in with a congrats balloon.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS176
She snatches the balloon.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS178
they walk past the doctor.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS180
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk up outside.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS184
SOMEONE looks at his phone a message from SOMEONE reads, "You’re placed in 30."
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS186
He and SOMEONE lay side-by-side in bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS187
SOMEONE leans over and snuggles closer.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS189
As she gets dressed she smiles and steps closer to SOMEONE who's sitting up in bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS190
He presses his lips together thoughtfully,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS191
a smile spreads across his face.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS192
Grinning she puts on her top.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS193
Beside her car he kisses her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS194
She gets in her car. A neighbor walks up with his dog.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS195
They guy shakes his head and walks by.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS209
SOMEONE's on the couch.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS210
SOMEONE and SOMEONE have wild sex in a variety of locations. At work SOMEONE receives a text.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS211
She looks at SOMEONE's penis through 3D glasses.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS214
In the operating theater SOMEONE lies on the operating table. SOMEONE shines a light on his naked body and runs her finger along his leg.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS216
In a park near the water, SOMEONE and SOMEONE have a barbecue with some of their friends. SOMEONE throws a Frisbee to SOMEONE and runs at her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS217
He wrestles her to the ground.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS220
SOMEONE tosses the salad.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS222
SOMEONE frowns and sends a text message to SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS224
He has really small hands,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS228
he smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS229
SOMEONE and SOMEONE load the car.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS234
He parks in front of the garage door and goes inside. SOMEONE's lying on the couch holding his hands and feet in the air and slowly moving them back and forth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS235
He wiggles his toes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS237
SOMEONE's at work.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS240
She chases her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS241
At the hospital, SOMEONE goes to the lobby where her sister SOMEONE is waiting.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS242
She's wearing an engagement ring,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS244
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE frowns unsurely and nods.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS245
At home, SOMEONE has made herbal teas.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS246
SOMEONE goes to the intercom.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS249
SOMEONE opens the lobby door and hurries upstairs holding a box of cupcakes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS250
SOMEONE opens the apartment door
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS251
and SOMEONE cautiously steps in. SOMEONE's curled up on the couch in pain.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS254
She nonchalantly shrugs.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS255
SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE on her bed and tries to feed her soup.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS256
She has a spoonful.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS258
SOMEONE lies on his side with his arms around SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS259
She wakes looks right him
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS260
and pries herself free.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS261
She looks at him earnestly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS262
He looks away from her and grabs his coat.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS263
Smiling bitterly he picks up his sneakers.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS264
In the park.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS265
At the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS266
A man looks at SOMEONE surprised.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS268
the city is a sea of lights.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS269
SOMEONE gets out of a black car at the hospital Christmas party at the plush W Hotel.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS271
He opens the passenger door for SOMEONE
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS273
and then opens the door again, SOMEONE smiles - touched.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS277
SOMEONE goes over and taps him on the shoulder.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS281
SOMEONE smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS283
SOMEONE walks up to her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS284
SOMEONE wraps her arms around SOMEONE and kisses him on the mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS287
He twirls her under his arm.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS291
she takes another call.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS294
wearing a pretty purple strapless dress SOMEONE totters to a taxi in her high heels.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS299
He carries them over to SOMEONE and SOMEONE,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS303
he smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS305
He goes outside
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS306
and stands face-to-face with SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS307
She stares at him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS308
SOMEONE comes out.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS310
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow him inside.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS312
SOMEONE carries SOMEONE inside,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS314
she nibbles his lips.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS315
She kisses him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS318
The cast and crew are gathered around SOMEONE who's sitting at the piano.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS320
SOMEONE stares at his father.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS322
SOMEONE blows out the candles on the cake which has the painting The Creation of SOMEONE by Michelangelo.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS330
At the hospital, SOMEONE runs to SOMEONE who's with Dr. SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS331
SOMEONE lies on a bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS332
He gives it to SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS333
SOMEONE pops a pill and looks at SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS334
She slaps his cheek.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS335
SOMEONE head-butts the table.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS336
SOMEONE looks touched.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS338
SOMEONE raises his eyebrows
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS339
They walk out.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS340
SOMEONE's stunned.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS341
SOMEONE gives an embarrassed smile and a wave.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS343
She turns and gives SOMEONE an inquiring look,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS344
she nods.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS346
He smiles and steps closer for a kiss.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS347
She looks unsure and sighs,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS348
she walks off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS349
A smartly dressed SOMEONE sits on the bonnet of his car waiting outside the hospital,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS350
SOMEONE walks up wearing a raincoat over a shimmering silver shirt dress.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS351
Her long brown hair hangs lose.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS352
SOMEONE steps up to her
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS353
with his hands behind his back.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS354
He holds up a bunch of carrots.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS355
They drive through town. SOMEONE sits with the carrots lying next to her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS356
She holds up a card,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS357
stuck to it was sticking plasters
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS358
is a cutout picture of a human heart.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS359
He hands her a document.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS363
He goes straight in the hole.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS366
She takes the shot,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS367
the ball hits an angled block,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS368
takes a shot, left turn, nudges against the concrete curb, and heads straight for the hole.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS370
The ball passes through a tube beneath the shrubbery and rolls straight toward the hole.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS374
In a diner, they both suck through straws. SOMEONE gets an extra straw.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS375
SOMEONE grabs a handful of straws and has a big slurp of the chocolate milkshake.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS376
She wipes his lip and licks her finger.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS377
They gaze at each other.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS378
Avoiding his gaze she leans forward and has a drink.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS379
Later, SOMEONE drives along smiling. He glances at SOMEONE who stares ahead.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS380
Preoccupied, she looks out at the window to her side.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS381
They walk through the urban light instillation at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS382
A rectangular arrangement of 202 vintage street lamps from the city all painted gray.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS384
They stand facing each other.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS386
She slaps his chest.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS387
A security guard breaks them up. SOMEONE walks away and SOMEONE jumps on his back,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS388
the guard runs over to them he breaks them up a second time.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS389
SOMEONE drives SOMEONE up outside the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS390
They both sit staring ahead stony faced.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS391
Tears glistened in SOMEONE's eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS392
SOMEONE undoes her seat belt. She turns towards SOMEONE, but doesn't look at him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS393
She gets out of the car and walks towards the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS394
She stops beneath the red and white emergency sign and looks back,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS395
SOMEONE drives away.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS396
Still in her pretty silver dress SOMEONE walks into the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS398
In a daze, she slowly walks past the front desk.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS400
SOMEONE sees her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS402
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE concerned. Clutching her coat she wanders down the corridor oblivious to Dr. SOMEONE, who glances around at her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS404
SOMEONE is having a candle lit dinner with SOMEONE. SOMEONE comes in.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS409
In SOMEONE's bedroom, he pulls a chair up for her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS410
She sits decisively.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS411
She smiles he sits facing her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS413
Six weeks later. At the hospital,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS417
SOMEONE stands leaning against the worktop in a kitchen area. SOMEONE doesn't acknowledge her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS418
SOMEONE goes outside.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS420
SOMEONE looks around at Dr. SOMEONE as he walks by.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS421
SOMEONE drives along a highway by the ocean with her mom SOMEONE beside her. SOMEONE's new boyfriend, Bones, is sleeping on the backseat. He's a thick-set old guy with a mustache and a ponytail.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS422
SOMEONE looks back and smiles. SOMEONE frowns disapprovingly and blinks.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS429
They drive over a long bridge by the ocean,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS430
then along a palm tree-lined road.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS431
Under the pale blue sky the ocean has a shimmering silver sheen.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS432
They turn up a driveway through lush gardens.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS433
On the sound stage, the cast of SOMEONE's show, Secret High, perform a prom dance number.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS435
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Wallace are also there watching.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS436
Young couples dance together elegantly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS439
As the number comes to a close, dancers surround the male and female leads, SOMEONE and SOMEONE, and slowly raise their arms.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS443
a satisfied smile spreads across SOMEONE's face. SOMEONE and SOMEONE both elegantly dressed in white kiss passionately.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS445
At SOMEONE's wedding rehearsal dinner,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS450
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS451
SOMEONE smiles fondly. She grabs SOMEONE's phone and hands it to her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS454
He looks tense. His eyes glaze. SOMEONE calls SOMEONE as he stares at his phone, which SOMEONE holds aloft. At the other end of the line SOMEONE waits expectantly. SOMEONE hangs up and sits on a bench.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS459
With a look of disbelief SOMEONE slowly lowers her phone.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS463
She smiles at him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS467
She stares ahead intently.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS469
Lights glow beneath the porch roof.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS470
SOMEONE switches off the car headlights and gets out, Wearing a pretty pale lilac SOMEONE dress.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS476
SOMEONE sighs and creeps out from behind the bush.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS479
She walks down the steps to the road. She calls SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS481
SOMEONE gets in the car.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS482
They sip red wine, then lean in for a kiss at the same time, and bash heads.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS483
Faces on the couch, SOMEONE leans close and kisses SOMEONE forcefully on the mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS485
She kisses him, then frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS486
She stands and unbuttons her shirt.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS487
He checks his phone. SOMEONE frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS488
SOMEONE stands with her shirt hanging off and clicks her fingers.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS490
SOMEONE drives along the freeway listening to SOMEONE's Period mix.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS492
She munches from a large box of doughnut holes. She has sugar-frosting smushed around her mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS493
She grabs her phone, a message from SOMEONE reads, "Call me."
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS495
She makes the call. SOMEONE meets SOMEONE and her little dog at the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS496
She frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS497
She shakes her head.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS498
He looks away bewildered.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS499
She holds out the fluffy white Pomeranian.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS500
SOMEONE takes Freckles and walks off. With a look of distaste, SOMEONE wipes her hands together and goes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS501
With Freckles hidden inside his blue cardigan
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS503
SOMEONE sneaks past reception.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS504
SOMEONE covers Freckles completely with his cardigan and heads along a corridor.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS505
He walks into a room where SOMEONE lies in a slightly tilted bed SOMEONE shuts the door.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS508
SOMEONE opens his cardigan and puts Freckles on the bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS509
SOMEONE sits beside the bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS511
SOMEONE wearily shakes his head.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS512
SOMEONE smiles,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS513
he holds Freckles up close to his face.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS514
SOMEONE stands and gently touches SOMEONE's brow.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS515
SOMEONE wanders out and SOMEONE strokes the dog. He smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS517
SOMEONE walks along beneath the covered walkway with the red and white emergency sign at the end of it.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS518
He makes a phone call.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS519
SOMEONE gets out of the car and walks over to him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS521
He steps closer then frowns. He gestures for her to wipe the sugar frosting from beside her mouth and she does that.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS522
She blinks back tears.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS523
SOMEONE's chest heaves. SOMEONE stares at her with tears glistening in his eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS526
They go to each other and kiss passionately.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS527
SOMEONE cups her hands around the back of SOMEONE's neck and pulls him closer.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS528
They squeeze each other tight and kiss tenderly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS529
They both smile.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS530
A massive breakfast of pancakes and waffles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS531
SOMEONE cuts herself a big helping of pancakes. SOMEONE frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS533
They drive along the coast road.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS535
They get out of the car.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS536
SOMEONE's still in the pale lilac SOMEONE dress. SOMEONE wears jeans and a t-shirt.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS539
They stand side-by-side and watch the proceedings.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS540
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE smiling nervously.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS541
With a wry smile he looks down and takes her hand in his
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS542
gently knitting their fingers together.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS545
SOMEONE frowns anxiously.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS546
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and his two dads all hug.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS548
The door opens and she stares distastefully at an elderly gentleman.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS549
She cautiously enters the elevator
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS551
and the door starts to close.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS553
A guy runs up, stops the door with his briefcase, and gets in. He's followed by several more people.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS554
Suddenly, Vanessa is surrounded by elderly men and women. She looks decidedly uncomfortable and makes a bid for freedom.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS556
The door closes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS558
In a sunny park, SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE close and they kiss passionately,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS560
then nonchalantly walks off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS561
SOMEONE gives a weary look and follows him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS570
Fully clothed, he behind her with his arm around her
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS571
they sleep peacefully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS18
In a classroom the teenage boy draws in his textbook, sketching a mustached man with a worried face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS19
As a matronly teacher makes her way down an aisle other students hand her their assignments.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS20
The young artist sits concentrating, shading a shirt collar under the worried face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS21
SOMEONE collects his things and heads out. Now outside, he cuts across a grove of leafless trees beside a river. He stops and gazes ahead. He stands alone in his dark coat before a backdrop of buildings and a stonewall. Now he enters the school office where an assistant does paperwork.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS22
A man behind a window beckons SOMEONE sternly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS23
In the Principal's office the young man slings his backpack to the floor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS24
SOMEONE drops his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS25
SOMEONE gazes a scant at the departing student.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS26
Collecting his book bag, SOMEONE heads off. Now he emerges from a stairwell unto the school roof. With parted lips he stares through the chain linked fence toward a highway and a distant bridge spanning the nearby river. Glancing over his shoulder, he spots an onlooker across the rooftop.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS27
One of the three students from the lunchroom, a blond girl, exhales smoke and meets his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS28
As SOMEONE faintly smiles, the stairwell door opens.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS29
The blond tosses her cigarette through the fence.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS30
SOMEONE quickly takes out a cigarette.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS31
A dark haired faculty member arrives.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS32
The blond mouths thank you as she leaves.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS33
Later. Entering a stylish apartment, SOMEONE walks a hall to a spacious living room with a comfy sitting area and a baby grand piano. In the kitchen he pours a bowl of cereal. A middle-aged woman enters and sets a briefcase on the table. SOMEONE averts his gaze from hers as he gets milk from the fridge.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS34
He takes his leave. Now seated at a white canvas in school he draws in pencil. Charcoal portraits decorate the walls.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS35
A gray haired bearded instructor approaches glowering.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS36
His drawing shows a fist punching the teeth out of the bearded teacher's grotesque caricature. SOMEONE punches him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS38
Other art students glance up from their work. Now, SOMEONE exits the building. As the blond girl tries to walk abreast of him, SOMEONE ignores her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS39
She catches up on the sidewalk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS40
On a nearby court boys shoot baskets.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS41
SOMEONE bites her lip thoughtfully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS42
SOMEONE glares as she spots
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS43
a couple canoodling on a brown stone stairway.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS44
SOMEONE in a negligee and robe, the woman kisses a younger man, then flirtatiously touches his coat lapel. Her gaze follows as he makes his way past SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS45
SOMEONE's mother heads indoors. SOMEONE stares, transfixed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS46
The kids enter a well-appointed dining area where SOMEONE's mom holds a drink.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS47
Now, the three share drinks on a patio.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS48
Mrs. SOMEONE touches SOMEONE's leg. He jolts spilling his beer.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS49
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS50
Mrs. SOMEONE steps away.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS51
SOMEONE grins, his eyes darting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS52
SOMEONE rises, smiling. SOMEONE's gaze meet his expectantly
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS53
and she offers a demure smile. SOMEONE returns a winsome shrug.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS54
He lingers a moment then heads inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS55
SOMEONE leans forward, resting her head on her hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS56
Now, leafless trees silhouette the dusky horizon where SOMEONE stops and gazes off.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS57
He opens the door to his dimly lit apartment.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS58
He flicks a light switch, then another with no effect. Candles illuminate the living room and dining area.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS59
At the table, SOMEONE's mother shares a meal with a middle aged man.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS61
Later on a balcony, he gazes toward the twinkling Manhattan skyline.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS62
At school a pretty teacher in bookish glasses leads a class.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS63
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE in the desk to his right.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS64
SOMEONE adds detail to a doodle die ball.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS65
He looks up.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS66
SOMEONE absent-mindedly thumbs the pages of a book.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS67
SOMEONE grins.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS68
Under the teacher's beaming gaze he fidgets.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS69
He shoots a glance at SOMEONE. Now he crosses the lunchroom where SOMEONE sits with her two friends, a dark haired girl and a preppy guy. SOMEONE catches his eye as SOMEONE starts to take a seat at an empty table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS70
He approaches, tray in hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS71
SOMEONE hands him a textbook.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS72
SOMEONE scans the pages revealing severe black and white renderings of faces, eyes and mouths. Some punctuated with red.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS73
SOMEONE nods tentatively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS74
Now in his bedroom, SOMEONE sits at a desk. He leans over a sketchbook with a pen and adds to a drawing which includes a horned Cyclops wearing a party hat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS75
SOMEONE covers his sketch with homework as SOMEONE enters.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS76
As SOMEONE pretends to resume his homework, a pleased SOMEONE steps out. The teen sticks the assignment into a textbook, then returns to his drawing.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS77
He adds shoulders to a grimacing demon within a starburst design.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS78
The next day he arrives at school and opens the doors which have been decorated with paper snowflakes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS79
At lunch. His drawing shows the demon punching through the page.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS80
He cracks a smile. Now Asian lettering adorns shops in Chinatown. SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk up from a Subway station.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS81
Later they eat from takeout containers. Now a film shows a man and boy descending a spiral staircase on the Eiffel Tower.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS82
Subtitles. Tell me why aren't you married? I haven't found my dream girl. In the movie theater, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE who wears glasses.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS83
Do you like me? Of course not. A Marquee reads Zazie Dans le Metro.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS84
Across the street SOMEONE walks alone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS86
SOMEONE and SOMEONE round a corner and spy on him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS87
Wearing his trench coat SOMEONE slowly ambles along with a briefcase in hand. SOMEONE and SOMEONE peer around the nose of a truck and watch him enter a coffee shop called, The Cup & Saucer.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS88
SOMEONE takes a seat at a window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS89
SOMEONE watches his stepfather do paperwork.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS90
Now at school, as the teen heads up a stairwell the Principal blocks his path.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS91
He sips from a mug.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS92
The principal heads off. Now a banner hangs over the school entrance, Career Fair. SOMEONE steps outside with his shirt tucked in and a nametag on his chest. He looks around.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS93
He spots a scruffy looking guy standing across the street then heads in his direction. With his back turned to the approaching student the unshaven man hunches over to light a cigarette.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS95
A monitor shows an abstract painting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS96
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a boulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS97
SOMEONE musses up his own hair. SOMEONE sits back and folds his arms.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS98
Holding a coffee with both hands, SOMEONE stares at him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS99
SOMEONE glances at his coffee. Now, he and SOMEONE stroll along a sidewalk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS100
SOMEONE smirks, then shakes her head and continues on alone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS101
Watching her go, SOMEONE smiles to himself. About 50 yards away SOMEONE glances back.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS102
Now traffic passes several evergreens adorned with lights. The image dissolves to the trees at night as more traffic crawls by. On another day, a taxi drives over the Manhattan Bridge. Riding in the back seat, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE who sits beside him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS103
She glances out his window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS104
SOMEONE sits up following her gaze past a railing to a cluster of industrial brick buildings.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS105
An American flag waves atop a pillar on the distant Brooklyn Bridge. SOMEONE smiles to himself.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS106
Now he presses a doorbell.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS107
The teens wait outside a blue building. SOMEONE shoves the door open.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS108
Seeing SOMEONE with SOMEONE, he giggles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS109
He gestures inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS110
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter. SOMEONE yanks the door shut behind them.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS111
Inside his studio they look over various paintings.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS112
He points to one.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS113
SOMEONE wanders off alone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS114
Later, SOMEONE looks over SOMEONE's sketchbook.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS115
He glances at SOMEONE who sits in the next room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS116
SOMEONE looks at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS117
He peers out the window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS118
He returns his attention to the sketchbook. SOMEONE shifts his gaze. That night he and SOMEONE ride back in a cab.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS119
SOMEONE rolls her eyes curiously then folds her legs. She and SOMEONE each look out their windows. Traffic drives past the median lined with Christmas trees.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS120
Now at dinner.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS121
SOMEONE text messages.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS122
Later in his room, he lies on his bed with an art book. He flips back several pages and studies a red hued painting of a figure standing under bare trees before a distant building.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS123
Turning to the next page he studies an oil painting of a woman in a ruffled dress facing a mirror.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS124
He turns the page again and studies a portrait of a sickly somber faced boy. The transfixed teen focuses on the boy's dark eyes,
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS125
which seem to stair back at him. Shades of peach represent the subject's
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS126
fair skin. Now in a gallery, patrons gather around SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS127
He notices SOMEONE approaching. A photographer snaps a picture.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS128
SOMEONE stares past SOMEONE and frowns.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS129
He turns around and sees only blank canvases adorning the walls.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS130
Now he awakes in bed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS131
On a busy city street, traffic lights turn from green to red. In the kitchen SOMEONE fills a bowl with cereal, then glances around.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS132
He pours in the last few drops of milk from a carton.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS133
Stepping into a doorway, he sees SOMEONE hunched over paperwork in an office across the hall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS134
SOMEONE watches his frustrated stepfather set one page aside and grab another.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS135
The teen takes out his cellphone and reads a text message from SOMEONE, Happy New Year. Meet me at SOMEONE's. 6 SOMEONE Circle. 20th floor. SOMEONE walks off. Now he knocks on a door.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS136
SOMEONE answers it wearing a shiny Lamé dress.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS137
SOMEONE gawks at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS138
He follows her inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS139
She leads him downstairs to a chic living room where they join SOMEONE and a girlfriend.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS140
A blond guy sits across from them. His friend sits beside SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS141
SOMEONE arrives.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS142
SOMEONE picks up a card reading, New Year's Eve Party. Then flips it over to find his drawing.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS143
He smiles at his work.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS144
Later on a quiet street SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk together following the others.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS145
Now in a trendy nightclub, she leads him through the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS146
She leads him across the dance floor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS147
SOMEONE hands him a bottle of champagne. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE to the middle of the dance floor. A strobe light flashes on the anxious teen. Facing him, SOMEONE brushes back her hair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS148
SOMEONE tries to dance, awkwardly swaying to the music.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS149
SOMEONE grins as she watches him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS150
SOMEONE smiles and watches her dance ecstatically with her eyes closed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS151
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hug. As he dances close to her she looks at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS152
He pleasantly raises his bottle of champagne then backs away disappearing within the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS153
SOMEONE watches him go, then turns her attention back to SOMEONE as she dances with him joyfully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS154
Now, SOMEONE walks through the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS155
He approaches SOMEONE's friends at the bar. SOMEONE turns to him, holding a shot.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS156
They all raise shots.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS157
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS158
A blond girl whispers in SOMEONE's ear then leads her off.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS159
SOMEONE watches her go.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS161
Wandering through the crowded dance floor SOMEONE glimpses SOMEONE still dancing with SOMEONE. As SOMEONE moves on someone hands him a shot.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS162
He toasts with the group.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS163
A brilliant disco lights swings by overhead as he shifts his dull gaze. Strobe-like flashes of the tightly packed club goers go in and out of focus.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS164
SOMEONE stumbles through the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS165
Outside, he shuffles across the street and vomits, catching the attention of two bystanders.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS166
He sits back against a wall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS167
He spits.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS168
A string of saliva falls from his mouth as he sits up and catches his breath.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS169
He undoes a button of his shirt, then hangs his head with his eyes half closed. Down the block, a group of pedestrians walks by.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS170
Later, SOMEONE lies alone, passed out against the wall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS171
Crossing the street, SOMEONE picks up her pace as she finds her lost friend.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS172
She crouches at SOMEONE's side and helps him sit up against the graffitied wall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS173
Now, with SOMEONE's arm draped over her shoulders, SOMEONE helps him into her bedroom. Leaning him against the door jam, she doffs her coat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS174
She rolls out the lower level of a trundle bed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS175
She grabs a pillow and a comforter.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS176
She twitches a smile then straightens SOMEONE's overcoat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS177
SOMEONE blinks over her smile and averts her gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS178
With a kind look she reaches for him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS179
She slides his coat off then steadies him as he staggers to the bed. Holding his side, she guides him to the lower bed beside her own. He flops back on it, then watches as she spreads the comforter over him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS180
SOMEONE turns her back to him and switches off a lamp on a dresser.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS181
As SOMEONE's eyelids open and close between wakefulness and sleep, he glimpses her intermittently.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS182
With her back to him, SOMEONE slides out a dresser drawer.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS183
She pulls her dress up over her head, revealing her bra.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS184
She puts on a three quarter sleeve baseball T.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS185
As she dons pajama pants, she glances over her shoulder at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS186
He sees her just before his eyes fall shut.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS187
One last glimpse shows the dresser without SOMEONE in front of it.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS188
Now, pale light glows on SOMEONE's sleeping face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS189
His eyelids flutter and he wakes up.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS190
Shifting his head on the pillow, he turns to SOMEONE and watches her sleep.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS191
He props himself up on his elbows and sweeps his gaze up SOMEONE's face, taking in her rosy lips, smooth cheeks, and closed eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS193
Still studying her beauty, he lies back.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS194
With his thoughtful gaze fixed on the sleeping girl, SOMEONE lets his eyelids shut.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS195
Morning. Propped on one elbow, SOMEONE sits awake in bed, her eyes darting to the lower regions of SOMEONE's blanket. She presses her lips together to stifle a smile, then shifts her gaze to SOMEONE who blinks awake and looks up at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS196
He smiles. Following SOMEONE's gaze, he sees his morning wood jetting up under the blanket. He rolls off the bed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS197
He glances at SOMEONE, then drops his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS198
Later in the dining room, Mrs. SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a Bloody SOMEONE garnished with a celery stalk and bendy straw.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS199
Sitting kitty corner to SOMEONE's mom SOMEONE nods, then sips the drink.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS200
He shoots her an alarmed look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS201
She pushes her chair out and strides away. Her mother glances after her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS202
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS203
He lifts the straw to his lips and drinks. Now he follows SOMEONE down a sidewalk. Slowing his pace, he watches his stepfather grab a newspaper off the top of a trash can then cross the street. With his eyes fixed on the man, SOMEONE remains on the opposite sidewalk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS204
He pauses behind a pair of pay phones then takes a few steps and sees
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS205
SOMEONE sitting on a bench in a crowded bus shelter.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS206
The people waiting around him stir as a bus pulls up.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS207
The bus glides away to reveal SOMEONE alone on the shelter bench.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS208
He reads the newspaper. Later SOMEONE exits an elevator in an office building. He walks down a barren corridor and stops in front of a door. His jaw drops as he spots an eviction notice taped to it. The door's shiny nameplate reads, SOMEONE Sargent. Marketing Research Incorporated.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS209
Nighttime. Wearing dark framed glasses, SOMEONE sits on her bed and reads. Her mother joins her as she folds her daughter's clothes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS210
SOMEONE gives her mother a pointed look. With a faint smile, Charlotte glances away. Now in a gallery at the Whitney Museum, SOMEONE and SOMEONE face a gray canvas covered with chalky scribbles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS211
Wearing a coiled white scarf, SOMEONE moves to a painting of two red rectangles below a white one.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS212
SOMEONE nods uncertainly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS213
He glances at SOMEONE then returns his gaze to the paintings.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS214
SOMEONE shrugs, then moves to another painting. SOMEONE joins him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS215
SOMEONE gazes at the piece of art.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS216
SOMEONE eyes him thoughtfully, then steps in front of the next piece.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS217
The sharp perspective canvas shows six rows of plates each holding a slice of cake or pie identical to the others in its row.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS219
He gives an embarrassed shrug.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS220
SOMEONE eyes the plates.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS221
With a knowing smile, SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE staring at the image. SOMEONE leaves.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS222
Now SOMEONE sits across from SOMEONE at a restaurant.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS223
A plastic table stand between them reads, Valentine's Day menu.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS224
SOMEONE nods and smiles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS225
Nodding, SOMEONE stares down at the table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS226
He folds his hands on the table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS228
Staring at SOMEONE, he gives a faint sad smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS229
SOMEONE shoots him a thoughtful look, then lowers her eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS230
She meets his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS231
Starring into SOMEONE's eyes, SOMEONE gives a tiny nod.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS232
She twitches a smile then brushes hair away from her face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS233
He grins. SOMEONE rumples her lips.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS234
SOMEONE stares at her with hard eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS235
SOMEONE presses his lips into a tight line. He averts his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS236
As she peers directly at SOMEONE his eyes widen. His lips part fumbling.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS237
SOMEONE bows her head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS238
She averts her gaze as SOMEONE stares crestfallen, SOMEONE leans toward him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS239
As she sits back and sips her drink SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS240
Later, heading down a sidewalk with SOMEONE, SOMEONE stares straight ahead. His hands in his pockets and his face sullen.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS241
SOMEONE glances at him but he avoids her gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS242
He looks down thoughtfully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS243
He stops walking.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS244
SOMEONE blinks her confused eyes. SOMEONE stares back angrily.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS245
He turns on his heels and strides away.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS246
Staring after him she shakes her head then storms off in the opposite direction.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS247
Now, SOMEONE lies on his bed with his hands folded under his head. His iPod plays beside him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS248
His phone display flashes. SOMEONE calling. With a sour look, he rejects the calls then smooths the front of his shirt and folds his hands behind his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS249
SOMEONE shoots his cell a brooding glance, then reaches for his iPod and hits play.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS250
Now he wears a different but similar outfit as he lies on his bed with his eyes closed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS251
His mother raps on the door. She opens it and looks in.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS252
His mother stares at him, her brow creased.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS253
Slack jawed, she closes the door as she leaves. SOMEONE lies with his arms folded over his stomach and his eyes shut.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS254
He presses play on his iPod and lies back.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS255
Now at school SOMEONE sits in the lunchroom with SOMEONE and SOMEONE. She glances back at SOMEONE reading alone one table away. SOMEONE scrutinizes him curiously, and SOMEONE wears a wounded expression.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS256
Later, SOMEONE lies on his bed gazing dourly at the ceiling. SOMEONE opens the door and gawks.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS257
SOMEONE stares at him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS258
Rolling his eyes, SOMEONE returns his gaze to the ceiling. SOMEONE stares at him for a moment then backs out of the room and closes the door.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS259
SOMEONE shuts his eyes. Meanwhile SOMEONE listens on her phone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS260
She ends the call then hits redial.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS261
With a frustrated look she hangs up. Striding down a waterfront walkway she pauses as she notices someone up ahead. She smiles faintly then heads over to SOMEONE who sits on a low stonewall sketching on a pad. Later, SOMEONE strides down a sidewalk. SOMEONE approaches from the opposite direction. His hands in his coat pockets and his gaze fixed on the ground. The two teens walk right past each other offering no sign of acknowledgment.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS262
Evening. Pale sunlight gleams off cars parked on both sides of a city.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS263
White letters on a red sign outside of a bar read, SOMEONE's. Sitting alone inside SOMEONE brushes her bangs out of her face, then glances at the door as it opens. SOMEONE joins her at the bar.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS264
Shifting uneasily, SOMEONE tucks some hair behind one ear.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS265
One elbow on the bar, SOMEONE runs a hand through his wavy hair. He props his head on it and gazes at SOMEONE with wistful eyes. He offers a restrained smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS266
She gives him an annoyed look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS267
As she gently sways back and forth in her seat, SOMEONE turns away.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS268
SOMEONE slides out of her chair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS269
She offers her hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS270
SOMEONE accepts, then rises from his chair. Gazing into his eyes, she lifts his hand and spins under his arm. As she pulls him in and starts to dance he sits again.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS271
SOMEONE nods then breaks into a flirtatious smile. Closing her eyes, she begins to dance in front of SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS272
She sways sensually and the artist gives a longing look. Daytime. In class, SOMEONE stares out a window at a neighboring building. A bird flies past.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS273
As his English teacher collects the students’ papers, she stops at his desk and touches his shoulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS274
She notes his distant expression.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS275
His teacher frowns.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS276
SOMEONE averts his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS277
Now, SOMEONE arrives at the school office.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS278
The assistant sheepishly meets his gaze. SOMEONE proceeds to the Principal's office. Later he sits wringing his hands.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS279
Three of SOMEONE's teachers sit in the room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS280
The English teacher purses her lip.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS281
With glistening eyes, SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE who avoids his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS282
The math teacher gives him a harsh look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS283
He rubs tears from his eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS284
The sober faced teachers stay put as SOMEONE gets up from the couch and exits. He turns back at the open door.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS285
He continues out with a numb expression.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS286
Now Vivian and SOMEONE sit waiting for him at home.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS287
The distraught mother dabs at the corners of her eyes with her pinkie.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS288
SOMEONE steps into the room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS289
SOMEONE grabs him roughly and they wrestle to the floor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS290
As SOMEONE gets back up his stepfather restrains him from behind.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS291
He backs SOMEONE into the doorframe and the older man slumps to the floor clutching his shoulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS292
The troubled teen runs out.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS293
Later, our view chases after him as he races through the park.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS294
Night falls as he bolts down SOMEONE's street and into her apartment building.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS295
He catches his breath as she answers.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS296
She slips out shutting the door behind her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS297
He presses her up against the door and kisses her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS298
She pushes him back and frowns uncomfortably.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS299
With a heavy blink, she lifts her brown eyes to meet his.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS300
SOMEONE twists the doorknob behind her back. She pushes the door open a crack and SOMEONE takes a look inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS301
Charlotte sits on the sofa near SOMEONE who guiltily leans forward in an armchair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS302
Later, SOMEONE marches away from the apartment building.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS303
SOMEONE runs out after him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS304
The boy turns around with a wounded glare.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS305
SOMEONE pouts, his eyes glistening.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS306
Tears stream down SOMEONE's cheek.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS307
The boy dries his face
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS308
with his sleeve, then glances off pensively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS309
He flashes a wry dimpled smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS310
Dusting contritely shifts his arms at his sides.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS311
SOMEONE's chin furrows sadly as he stares at his mentor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS312
SOMEONE returns a solemn, remorseful look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS313
SOMEONE turns around and mopes off down the block of brown stone buildings. Later he sulks at a bar while SOMEONE, SOMEONE and others have a good time all around him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS314
Someone passes in front of our view as the picture fades to black.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS315
In the early morning under a gray sky SOMEONE walks down the middle of a street.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS316
Later he strolls through a park on a pathway between tall leafy trees and approaches Vivian sitting on a bench. His shoulders sag as he lets out a sigh.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS317
His mother smiles at him and lifts her eyebrows.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS318
SOMEONE tightens his lips and takes a seat beside her on the bench. He folds his overcoat closed as a strong breeze blows through some trees and bushes at a wall behind them.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS319
Smiling gently she closes her eyes and lets out a breath.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS320
She closes her hands over her nose and mouth as she sobs. SOMEONE puts his arm around her and kisses her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS321
He rests his cheek against her honey blond hair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS322
Later, SOMEONE strides into the Principal's office.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS323
SOMEONE hurries out.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS324
Now in the art room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS325
Later, SOMEONE leaves the school with a tall stack of assignments.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS326
SOMEONE falls into step with him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS327
SOMEONE stops and faces her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS328
SOMEONE's mouth creases as she stares at him remorsefully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS329
He walks off leaving her behind.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS330
Later at home.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS332
As he heads off, Vivian watches him fondly. In his bedroom SOMEONE plops the thick stack of assignments down on his desk. He removes his coat. Rolling up his sleeves he takes a seat at his desk and straightens the pile of homework. He stares at the daunting stack of folders and assignment books for a moment then turns on a lamp and opens up his laptop.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS333
On another day, our view travels across his bedroom to find him hard at work at his desk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS334
He works out a trigonometry equation. Vivian shows in another couple.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS335
Later, SOMEONE sets up a blank canvas on an easel and stares at it. In the kitchen Vivian wraps up pieces of pottery in newspaper and boxes them.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS336
SOMEONE writes an essay on ruled notebook paper.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS337
He now takes a brush to his canvas and starts his painting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS338
He mixes shades of emerald and white to form a pale green. Later on the canvas, he uses thick brush strokes to apply streaks of white over the green. He paints a purple vertical line, then shadows it in burnt sienna. Now at school he writes an essay for his English final. Later he uses a calculator to work out a problem for his trig final. Back at home, he solves another long equation, types on his laptop and fills in answers on some French homework.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS339
He types up a paper citing the Thoreau's Civil Disobedience. Taking an essay test he begins an answer with a mention of SOMEONE Bacon and SOMEONE Hockney. For a multiple-choice question he circles the answer, Renaissance. Back at home he rubs his eye then places a completed assignment atop a stack and grabs the next piece of homework. Now in his loft, SOMEONE works on a painting as dawn breaks outside his windows. SOMEONE wakes up in his bed and watches him deliberately stub out a lit cigarette near the bottom corner of the canvas. Her eyes lower pensively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS340
Meanwhile, SOMEONE works on his own painting in a white T-shirt.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS341
Vivian smiles in his doorway drying her hands on a towel. SOMEONE grins.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS342
Vivian looks around the bare walls.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS343
He eyes his canvas. Later.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS344
Vivian admires her son as she shakes her head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS345
Later, SOMEONE strolls into his room where only his twin size bed remains.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS346
He gets a text from SOMEONE, I need to see you.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS347
Now an illuminated awning over an entry way reads, Lou's. Inside the softly lit bar, SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a booth, each with a bottle of beer on the table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS348
Her friend musters a tight smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS349
SOMEONE responds with a forgiving nod.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS350
SOMEONE's eyes glisten and he presses his lip.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS351
SOMEONE gives him a grave nod. He bravely looks her in the eye.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS352
SOMEONE lowers her gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS353
She rubs her neck then rests her head in her hand and allows a brief sad smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS354
SOMEONE looks down and bites her lips.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS355
With a faint smile, she reaches out and takes his hand in hers stroking his fingers with her thumb.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS356
Later as they follow the sidewalk, the young beauty casually bumps against SOMEONE, then tucks her hair behind her ear.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS357
Their interlocked hands sway gently with their
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS358
Now they arrive at her deserted apartment.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS359
They sit before laced curtained windows filled with soft golden light and kiss tenderly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS360
Pulling back SOMEONE beams at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS361
He invitingly brushes the tip of her nose with his.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS362
Her smile grows and she brings her lips to his again.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS363
As they share a series of soft gentle kisses, her hand moves up to his shoulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS364
Now in the soft predawn light, street lamps twinkle beyond a weathered wooden bench. SOMEONE strolls into view and takes a seat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS365
He stares off, his lips pursed in a thoughtful pout.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS366
Back in Charlotte's empty apartment SOMEONE pulls away abruptly and looks up at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS367
SOMEONE gives her an eager kiss.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS368
SOMEONE kisses him and drapes her arms around his shoulders.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS369
He smiles down at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS370
On the bench SOMEONE gives a hopeful smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS371
He lowers his gaze and licks his lips
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS372
Now, verdant tree branches dapple our view of a bright blue sky patched
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS373
with wispy clouds.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS375
She sets a heavy backpack at her feet.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS376
Then slips her hands in her pockets and cranes her neck for a view up the street.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS377
Elsewhere, SOMEONE leaves his building with his now draped canvas tucked under one arm. His other arm curls around the massive stack of completed homework assignments as he heads down the sidewalk at a brisk pace.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS378
Now, cars line up outside an international terminal at an airport.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS379
A black luxury car with tinted windows pulls into view and parks at the curb. SOMEONE and SOMEONE get out.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS380
The trunk pops open and they reach in for their bags. In the Principal's office SOMEONE's hands set the massive stack of assignments down on the desk. Working facing the wall, the administrator turns and looks up at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS381
He eyes the stack.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS382
At the airport, SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive at the boarding area where other passengers file through a gate.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS383
The teen girl hesitates and looks around. In the art room, SOMEONE sets SOMEONE's canvas on an easel.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS384
He steps back, his hands on his hips and regards it shrewdly as his troubled student stands nearby.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS385
The art teacher faces SOMEONE with a cocked eyebrow.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS386
He shoves the boy, then envelops him in a proud embrace. The teen gives a dimpled smile as he returns the hug, then faces his work with gleaming eyes. SOMEONE puts an arm around his shoulder and looks at the painting with an appreciative scowl.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS387
At the boarding gate, SOMEONE lingers by a window. Now a banner over the school entrance reads, Morgan. Congratulations, Seniors.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS388
SOMEONE sits by SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS389
He shakes his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS390
On her other side SOMEONE stands, goes to the stage and shakes the Principal's hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS391
The teen takes his diploma and executes a groovy spin.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS392
SOMEONE chuckles fondly and SOMEONE laughs into her hand. They briefly share a smile. At the boarding gate, SOMEONE checks with a ticket agent then joins SOMEONE at the sun lit window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS393
With a fond smirk SOMEONE steps closer, cradles her head in his hands and gives her a tender kiss.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS394
SOMEONE briefly averts her gaze then flashes a wan smile. SOMEONE kisses her again. At graduation, SOMEONE's expression grows pensive. At the airport SOMEONE lowers her gaze then smiles at SOMEONE again. At school, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE's tense demeanor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS395
SOMEONE beams warmly at him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS396
The principal leans over the podium looking straight at him. SOMEONE lifts his gaze, his hazel eyes gleaming. In slow motion he stands and makes his way to the stage. SOMEONE and SOMEONE grin after him. His mother beams happily. As he reaches the stage SOMEONE winks at him. SOMEONE regards him proudly. His math teacher gives a delighted round of applause and his English teacher nods approvingly. The Principal meets him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS397
Smiling faintly he shakes SOMEONE's hand then leans in.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS398
He holds out SOMEONE's diploma. As the teen accepts it the Principal pats him on the arm and steps away. SOMEONE smiles after him appreciatively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS399
As he faces the audience, sunlight flares in brightly through a window behind him. His mother beams proudly, her eyes glistening. The teen scans the room. Elsewhere SOMEONE turns, her surroundings washed out by sunlight. At graduation, SOMEONE's eyes shine as he lingers on the stage. Outside, tree branches bordering the streets sway gently in a breeze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS400
At the school a teen girl comes outside in her cap and gown and joins two fellow graduates.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS401
In the art room, SOMEONE stands with his graduation robe slung over one arm. On the easel, his painting offers a portrait of SOMEONE in
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS402
tints of green and purple.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS403
The subject gazes off with a stoic expression hinting at wisdom beyond her years. Turning away, SOMEONE sets his diploma and graduation robes on a chair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS404
As he turns back he halts and stares. In the doorway SOMEONE stands with her hands clasped before her. She offers a little smile and he regards her with shining eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS405
The teen girl enters the room holding SOMEONE in a solemn gaze. SOMEONE's eyes follow her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS406
As she passes obliviously behind her own portrait, moving with slow deliberate steps,
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS407
she keeps her gaze on him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS408
Approaching the young artist, she regards the portrait appraisingly then tilts her head and smiles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS409
SOMEONE glances at the painting then eyes SOMEONE anxiously.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS411
SOMEONE's gaze cools and his smile vanishes. She joins him at his side then faces the portrait again.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS412
She looks up at him with a teasing smirk. SOMEONE beams understandingly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS413
His hand reaches out taking a gentle hold of SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS414
As they linger facing the painting together she glances at him fondly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS415
SOMEONE heaves a grave sigh. She faces SOMEONE intently then looks back at the painting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS416
The two teens hesitantly met each other's gaze. SOMEONE yields a coy smile and turns toward the painting. SOMEONE follows her example with a hopeful gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS34
Headlights glow behind them.
THE_VOW_DVS35
The couple kisses passionately.
THE_VOW_DVS37
The driver side window shatters. The slipping truck veers right, and the pushed car slams into something.
THE_VOW_DVS38
Still seen in slow motion the brunette woman appears weightless as she drifts headfirst toward the windshield.
THE_VOW_DVS40
It shatters on contact. She lands halfway outside, face down on the hood.
THE_VOW_DVS41
The front bumpers crushed against a utility pole.
THE_VOW_DVS45
Later, emergency personnel wheel the unconscious couple into a hospital on stretchers.
THE_VOW_DVS46
Words appear. Inspired by true events.
THE_VOW_DVS47
In the ER a doctor intubates the wife while another cuts the husband's shirt.
THE_VOW_DVS48
In a corridor, three guys and two women anxiously heed the words of a nurse. The husband briefly opens his eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS49
Four years ago.
THE_VOW_DVS50
In a government building the broad shouldered man waits in line.
THE_VOW_DVS51
He sees his future wife with dark chin length hair leaving the counter ahead of him.
THE_VOW_DVS52
As she passes, he glances after her. Their gazes meet.
THE_VOW_DVS53
They share a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS54
Now he catches up with her, wearing a hip straw fedora.
THE_VOW_DVS55
She turns and finds him right there.
THE_VOW_DVS56
He holds it out.
THE_VOW_DVS57
He notices a sticker on her car.
THE_VOW_DVS58
She smiles, he drops his gaze and grins sheepishly.
THE_VOW_DVS59
She opens her car door.
THE_VOW_DVS60
She looks him in the eye.
THE_VOW_DVS61
Considering, she allows an amused smile.
THE_VOW_DVS62
She nods and he grins brightly.
THE_VOW_DVS63
She closes her driver side door and triggers her keychain remote.
THE_VOW_DVS64
Later in a dine-in spot called SOMEONE Mnemonic,
THE_VOW_DVS65
SOMEONE hides two chocolates from a box behind his back.
THE_VOW_DVS66
They each take a bite from a chocolate.
THE_VOW_DVS67
She offers her glass of red wine.
THE_VOW_DVS68
As he takes a sip, she plucks the straw fedora off his head and tries it on herself.
THE_VOW_DVS69
He tweaks the brim lower on her brow, and she wipes chocolate off his mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS70
At another SOMEONE, a pale and red-nosed SOMEONE shrugs her open sweater onto her shoulders and serves drinks.
THE_VOW_DVS71
She frowns at a box left on a table by a window.
THE_VOW_DVS72
She wipes her nose with a tissue, then heads over.
THE_VOW_DVS73
Finding a photo of herself on the box's lid,
THE_VOW_DVS74
she lifts her gaze and sees her handsome companion standing outside in the pouring rain.
THE_VOW_DVS75
He gestures and she opens the gift.
THE_VOW_DVS76
She reads a note on a box of tissues.
THE_VOW_DVS77
She finds medicine.
THE_VOW_DVS78
She takes out a photo of SOMEONE holding a guitar.
THE_VOW_DVS79
Holding his gaze, she presses the photo to her chest. Finding another note, she reads.
THE_VOW_DVS80
She pulls out a sexy lingerie bask with a black laced trimmed bust.
THE_VOW_DVS81
Holding it up, she purses her lips and mocks a seductive expression.
THE_VOW_DVS82
SOMEONE grins.
THE_VOW_DVS83
SOMEONE glances around, then hurriedly lowers the lingerie.
THE_VOW_DVS84
With a wave, SOMEONE heads away.
THE_VOW_DVS85
SOMEONE’s reflection in the window shows her loving smile as she waves back.
THE_VOW_DVS87
SOMEONE holds an arm out of a car window, as SOMEONE drives. She tickles him.
THE_VOW_DVS88
His eyes squint merrily as he leans back laughing.
THE_VOW_DVS89
SOMEONE beams at him, SOMEONE’s grin wilts and he clenches his jaw. SOMEONE stares.
THE_VOW_DVS90
With a smile, SOMEONE hits a switch. As she puts her power window up she holds SOMEONE’s gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS91
In the present, a CT machine scans an unconscious SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS94
At his wife’s bedside,
THE_VOW_DVS95
he returns her wedding ring to her finger. A ventilator tube juts from her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS96
In a flashback, SOMEONE exits an apartment and finds her in an alley.
THE_VOW_DVS97
She feeds a stray cat.
THE_VOW_DVS98
She heads inside.
THE_VOW_DVS99
SOMEONE’s three guy friends join them.
THE_VOW_DVS100
SOMEONE serves her pancakes with words spelled in blueberries.
THE_VOW_DVS101
He adjusts a few berries, clarifying the message, Move in, with a question SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS102
SOMEONE beams and SOMEONE’s guy friends swap happy looks.
THE_VOW_DVS103
She kisses SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS104
Now SOMEONE wears a wedding veil.
THE_VOW_DVS105
They stand with friends in a gallery.
THE_VOW_DVS106
He takes out his vows. Grinning, SOMEONE shows her identical SOMEONE Mnemonic menu. SOMEONE’s guy friends, a brunette woman with a beauty SOMEONE and a few others witness the event.
THE_VOW_DVS107
Beaming, SOMEONE nods. Their friends smile.
THE_VOW_DVS108
Their officiating friend spots two guards.
THE_VOW_DVS109
The newlyweds share a quick kiss, then flee the museum gallery with their small group of friends. The guards chase them.
THE_VOW_DVS110
Hurrying up a flight of stairs, SOMEONE drops his SOMEONE Mnemonic menu and pauses to snatch it up.
THE_VOW_DVS111
Outside, he holds SOMEONE’s hand as they race across a footbridge.
THE_VOW_DVS112
The guards give up the chase.
THE_VOW_DVS113
A sign below reads, The Art Institute of Chicago.
THE_VOW_DVS115
In Millennium Park, SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss under the steel, bean shaped archway of cloud gate.
THE_VOW_DVS116
A wider view shows people strolling the plaza around the 40-foot high sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS117
Their warped figures reflected on its seamless, chrome like surface. In another flashback,
THE_VOW_DVS118
SOMEONE works a mound of clay on the table in an art studio.
THE_VOW_DVS119
Her pulled back hair is now shoulder length.
THE_VOW_DVS120
With a frustrated look, she smacks the unfinished sculpture, then shoves the table away.
THE_VOW_DVS121
SOMEONE enters and turns off the stereo.
THE_VOW_DVS122
SOMEONE stomps irritably.
THE_VOW_DVS123
SOMEONE holds up a piece of clay, shaped like a person.
THE_VOW_DVS124
He makes the tiny figure dance.
THE_VOW_DVS125
SOMEONE playfully bites her neck.
THE_VOW_DVS126
He tickles her sides and she sinks to the floor in the fetal position.
THE_VOW_DVS127
He eyes clay on a table.
THE_VOW_DVS128
Nodding, SOMEONE gives him a tender smile.
THE_VOW_DVS129
She points at a different table.
THE_VOW_DVS130
She eyes the subject of his commentary.
THE_VOW_DVS131
Grinning, she cups his face in her hands and presses her lips to his abashed smirk.
THE_VOW_DVS132
As they kiss, she lies back on the floor, pulling him down on top of her.
THE_VOW_DVS133
He brushes his fingers over her hair,
THE_VOW_DVS135
then lowers his lips to her neck.
THE_VOW_DVS136
She pulls up his shirt to reveal his toned back, and works it over his head.
THE_VOW_DVS139
His fingers move to the buttons on her top.
THE_VOW_DVS140
Sunlight glows through the studio windows as SOMEONE lies asleep face down on SOMEONE’s chest. A rumpled sheet covers their waists.
THE_VOW_DVS141
SOMEONE stirs and caresses his wife’s arm with his thumb.
THE_VOW_DVS142
In the present, SOMEONE breaths with a nasal cannula as she lies in bed.
THE_VOW_DVS143
Wound scars barely show on the right side of her face.
THE_VOW_DVS144
SOMEONE stands with SOMEONE’s doctor at the foot of the bed.
THE_VOW_DVS145
The brunette shifts her groggy gaze, then closes her eyes and winces.
THE_VOW_DVS146
SOMEONE’s eyes grow misty.
THE_VOW_DVS147
SOMEONE gives him an uncertain look.
THE_VOW_DVS148
SOMEONE turns to the doctor.
THE_VOW_DVS149
SOMEONE addresses the question to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS150
He shoots her doctor a glance.
THE_VOW_DVS151
SOMEONE eyes him expectantly.
THE_VOW_DVS152
The real doctor turns to SOMEONE who returns a nonplussed glance.
THE_VOW_DVS153
The physician watches as SOMEONE’s distressed husband takes a seat at his wife’s bedside.
THE_VOW_DVS154
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE with perplexed eyes, and he meets her gaze solemnly.
THE_VOW_DVS155
She glances away.
THE_VOW_DVS156
He touches her arm, but she pulls it back with an alarmed look.
THE_VOW_DVS157
SOMEONE drops his dejected gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS158
The doctor observes closely.
THE_VOW_DVS159
SOMEONE lifts her hand and stares at the gold rope designed wedding ring on her finger.
THE_VOW_DVS160
She shifts her shocked eyes to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS161
Now he exits to the hall.
THE_VOW_DVS162
He storms off.
THE_VOW_DVS163
Now in a corridor, SOMEONE paces by a vending machine, clenching and unclenching his fists.
THE_VOW_DVS164
He leans against the machine.
THE_VOW_DVS165
With his back against it, he sinks to the floor.
THE_VOW_DVS166
He touches the wedding band around his finger, then wrings his hands.
THE_VOW_DVS168
SOMEONE enters a waiting room and finds SOMEONE asleep on a couch.
THE_VOW_DVS169
She pokes his shoulder with one finger.
THE_VOW_DVS170
Waking, he hurriedly sits up and rubs his face.
THE_VOW_DVS171
She flashes a nervous grin.
THE_VOW_DVS172
Smiling he collects his belongings.
THE_VOW_DVS173
He takes her to the cafeteria.
THE_VOW_DVS174
SOMEONE frowns dubiously.
THE_VOW_DVS175
SOMEONE shifts her shocked gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS176
She moves down the serving line. Now, SOMEONE’s friends visit at the hospital.
THE_VOW_DVS177
A guy throws a packaged salad at another.
THE_VOW_DVS179
The girl with the beauty SOMEONE crouches in front of SOMEONE and looks up at him.
THE_VOW_DVS180
SOMEONE gazes downward.
THE_VOW_DVS182
he reclines in the large, industrial room, serving as his and SOMEONE’s trendy Bohemian apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS183
Now, he arrives in the recovery ward with a tote bag and strides cheerfully to SOMEONE’s curtained off bed.
THE_VOW_DVS184
Pulling the curtains aside,
THE_VOW_DVS185
he finds the bed crisply made and unoccupied.
THE_VOW_DVS186
He goes to the nurse’s station.
THE_VOW_DVS187
Leaving the recovery area, SOMEONE breaks into a run.
THE_VOW_DVS188
Now in a comfortable private suite,
THE_VOW_DVS189
an elegant older couple regards SOMEONE coldly.
THE_VOW_DVS190
SOMEONE’s mother kisses her hand.
THE_VOW_DVS191
In the cafeteria.
THE_VOW_DVS192
SOMEONE meets her gaze reluctantly.
THE_VOW_DVS193
SOMEONE hangs his head.
THE_VOW_DVS194
SOMEONE leaves the table and he gestures helplessly.
THE_VOW_DVS195
Standing he gathers their things.
THE_VOW_DVS196
SOMEONE shrugs and shakes her head.
THE_VOW_DVS197
She moves off.
THE_VOW_DVS198
SOMEONE briefly hangs his head then takes a deep breath.
THE_VOW_DVS199
Now SOMEONE enters the VIP recovery room, clad in a short crocheted sweater dress and boots.
THE_VOW_DVS200
Her doctor arrives.
THE_VOW_DVS201
Meanwhile, SOMEONE runs through the hospital.
THE_VOW_DVS202
SOMEONE hurries in.
THE_VOW_DVS203
Her brow knitted, SOMEONE blinks at SOMEONE. He lowers the phone.
THE_VOW_DVS204
SOMEONE stares at him, her gaze softening.
THE_VOW_DVS205
Lowering her thoughtful eyes, SOMEONE puffs her cheeks out then exhales.
THE_VOW_DVS206
Her parents glower.
THE_VOW_DVS207
SOMEONE fixes his fond eyes on his wife.
THE_VOW_DVS208
Now, as he drives her through the city, SOMEONE faces her side view mirror. She briefly lifts her bangs back and studies the scar at her hairline.
THE_VOW_DVS209
Noting her husband’s earnest expression, SOMEONE yields a shy smile. An elevated train passes nearby.
THE_VOW_DVS210
SOMEONE smiles wistfully.
THE_VOW_DVS211
SOMEONE averts her surprised, slack-jawed gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS212
At night, SOMEONE shuts her door for her as she gets out of his 80s era Wagoneer.
THE_VOW_DVS213
He shyly walks her to their apartment’s entrance.
THE_VOW_DVS214
He leads her in to a foyer, then gestures.
THE_VOW_DVS215
As he shuts the door and carries their things, SOMEONE wrings her hands and ventures warily into the living room.
THE_VOW_DVS216
SOMEONE’s eyes widen. The girl with the beauty SOMEONE hugs her.
THE_VOW_DVS217
The lovely woman recovers her smile.
THE_VOW_DVS218
The wedding officiant.
THE_VOW_DVS219
As SOMEONE hurries off, SOMEONE watches her go. SOMEONE follows his wife.
THE_VOW_DVS220
Later, the guests file out.
THE_VOW_DVS221
SOMEONE sees off a trendy couple, then withdraws into the apartment and shuts the door.
THE_VOW_DVS222
At a dressing table, SOMEONE’s fingers glide over a drawing of a reclined female figure in a sketchbook.
THE_VOW_DVS223
Quaint odds and ends litter the surface.
THE_VOW_DVS224
SOMEONE’s reflections shows in a small round mirror trimmed along the bottom with photos and illustrations.
THE_VOW_DVS225
She picks up a bottle of perfume, and gives it a sniff.
THE_VOW_DVS226
SOMEONE approaches and sits in a nearby armchair.
THE_VOW_DVS227
Her gaze anguished, SOMEONE shuts her eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS228
SOMEONE gets up and leaves the room.
THE_VOW_DVS230
Staring ahead, SOMEONE’s features twist in a remorseful SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS231
In the living room, a shirtless SOMEONE covers his bare feet with a nappy blanket
THE_VOW_DVS232
and curls up beneath it on a couch.
THE_VOW_DVS233
SOMEONE remains at the dressing table.
THE_VOW_DVS234
She props her chin on her fist.
THE_VOW_DVS235
An artfully made, queen sized bed lies unoccupied behind her.
THE_VOW_DVS236
On the couch, SOMEONE stares off with a melancholy gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS237
Now, the sun shines brightly outside their converted warehouse building.
THE_VOW_DVS238
Inside a framed photo of a shirtless SOMEONE stands beside a baroque vanity mirror painted yellow.
THE_VOW_DVS239
The frame of a much larger wall mirror is home to several more candids, lovingly tucked in place.
THE_VOW_DVS240
SOMEONE approaches in a towel and spies a photo of her tattooed back.
THE_VOW_DVS241
She anxiously locates the swirling crescent shaped fish tattoo on her actual back.
THE_VOW_DVS242
SOMEONE steps away from the mirror.
THE_VOW_DVS243
On the living room couch, SOMEONE stirs groggily and wakes.
THE_VOW_DVS244
He sits up and throws off the blanket.
THE_VOW_DVS245
He rests his elbows on his knees,
THE_VOW_DVS246
then stands and plods bare bottomed across the room.
THE_VOW_DVS247
As SOMEONE puts on a bra, her naked husband straggles by, rubbing his eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS248
SOMEONE cracks up.
THE_VOW_DVS249
Smiling, SOMEONE shuts himself in an adjacent bathroom.
THE_VOW_DVS250
Now, a door opens to reveal SOMEONE wearing a Chicago Cubs sweatshirt and a sporty ponytail.
THE_VOW_DVS251
She enters the kitchen.
THE_VOW_DVS252
Sitting at the island, SOMEONE beams at her.
THE_VOW_DVS253
She opens a cabinet.
THE_VOW_DVS254
SOMEONE continues through the kitchen, opening the high cabinets one at a time.
THE_VOW_DVS255
SOMEONE watches her intently.
THE_VOW_DVS256
She notices.
THE_VOW_DVS257
SOMEONE notices fresh fruit, coffee, and French toast on the island.
THE_VOW_DVS258
SOMEONE sits at a place setting.
THE_VOW_DVS259
SOMEONE nods and sets down a newspaper.
THE_VOW_DVS260
SOMEONE shrugs inquisitively.
THE_VOW_DVS261
SOMEONE bites his lip and stifles a boyish smile.
THE_VOW_DVS262
SOMEONE nods demurely.
THE_VOW_DVS263
As SOMEONE gets the coffee pot his wife bites into a strip of bacon.
THE_VOW_DVS264
SOMEONE stares at the bacon.
THE_VOW_DVS265
She sets it down and picks bacon bits off her tongue.
THE_VOW_DVS266
SOMEONE steps toward his wife, hesitates, and pats her back.
THE_VOW_DVS267
He heads for the door.
THE_VOW_DVS268
Going out, he glances at her repeatedly.
THE_VOW_DVS269
SOMEONE offers a small wave and he shuts the door.
THE_VOW_DVS270
Left alone, she bites into a strip of bacon.
THE_VOW_DVS271
Now SOMEONE’s Wagoneer pulls up outside a converted garage with corrugated metal walls and a red door.
THE_VOW_DVS272
Inside, SOMEONE works at a soundboard.
THE_VOW_DVS273
SOMEONE comes in and deposits his things near the door.
THE_VOW_DVS274
SOMEONE hangs his head unhappily.
THE_VOW_DVS275
At the apartment, SOMEONE slides aside a grated door, protecting shelves of records, books, and DVDs.
THE_VOW_DVS276
She finds a sticky note from SOMEONE attached to one disc’s box. It reads More Evidence.
THE_VOW_DVS277
She winces as she watches.
THE_VOW_DVS278
SOMEONE laughs at her recorded comment.
THE_VOW_DVS279
In the video, SOMEONE holds up her menu.
THE_VOW_DVS280
SOMEONE sorrowfully covers her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS281
Later, she clutches a hard-covered book to her chest, as she strides into SOMEONE Mnemonic.
THE_VOW_DVS282
Crouching in front of a display case, she eyes shelves of pastries, then straightens.
THE_VOW_DVS283
She points,
THE_VOW_DVS284
she grins. Now she exits with her purchase.
THE_VOW_DVS285
At a store across the street, SOMEONE pays a florist.
THE_VOW_DVS286
Outside SOMEONE Mnemonic, SOMEONE glances around without seeing him, then heads down a sidewalk.
THE_VOW_DVS287
SOMEONE takes his bouquet of flowers and hurries in another direction.
THE_VOW_DVS288
Later, SOMEONE stands by a stairway to an L-train platform and looks around in confusion.
THE_VOW_DVS289
Meanwhile, SOMEONE arrives at their apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS290
Elsewhere in the city, SOMEONE stands at a bustling intersection and blinks her frustrated eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS292
At the apartment, SOMEONE spots his wife’s cellphone left on the kitchen island. He picks it up and checks its display,
THE_VOW_DVS293
then heads outside.
THE_VOW_DVS294
On the sidewalk out front, he glances around, then breaks into a run.
THE_VOW_DVS297
SOMEONE enters a restaurant equipment store and approaches a worker at a counter.
THE_VOW_DVS298
SOMEONE continues his search.
THE_VOW_DVS299
Now a car pulls up in front of SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS300
Her mother beckons.
THE_VOW_DVS301
Climbing into the convertible Mercedes, SOMEONE hugs her.
THE_VOW_DVS302
They drive off.
THE_VOW_DVS303
Later at the apartment, SOMEONE waits in the living room area and anxiously rubs his head.
THE_VOW_DVS304
SOMEONE arrives wearing a classy, contemporary dress and a half sleeved cardigan.
THE_VOW_DVS306
SOMEONE strides over.
THE_VOW_DVS307
SOMEONE gives a helpless shrug.
THE_VOW_DVS308
SOMEONE bows his head then meets her imploring gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS309
SOMEONE trudges out of the kitchen.
THE_VOW_DVS310
Later he drives her through an upscale neighborhood.
THE_VOW_DVS311
She holds the bouquet he purchased.
THE_VOW_DVS312
SOMEONE blinks.
THE_VOW_DVS313
She mulls it over.
THE_VOW_DVS314
They approach a Tudor style house.
THE_VOW_DVS315
Now in a dining room, SOMEONE casually displays a ring on her finger.
THE_VOW_DVS316
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE who mouths, It’s okay.
THE_VOW_DVS317
Already seated, SOMEONE stands awkwardly, then sits again.
THE_VOW_DVS318
SOMEONE raises his glass with the others.
THE_VOW_DVS319
SOMEONE gives a wry look.
THE_VOW_DVS320
SOMEONE eyes her lovingly, and she twitches an uneasy smile.
THE_VOW_DVS321
SOMEONE nods equivocating.
THE_VOW_DVS322
SOMEONE gives her fiancé a look.
THE_VOW_DVS323
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at him with blank expressions.
THE_VOW_DVS324
SOMEONE gives a puzzled shrug.
THE_VOW_DVS325
Later, patrons queue up outside a chic bar.
THE_VOW_DVS326
Entering, SOMEONE and SOMEONE trail behind SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS327
SOMEONE waves at a blonde, who averts her gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS328
SOMEONE glances over.
THE_VOW_DVS329
They reach a table.
THE_VOW_DVS330
Three women greet them.
THE_VOW_DVS331
SOMEONE slaps SOMEONE on the back.
THE_VOW_DVS332
SOMEONE observes the group, tentatively.
THE_VOW_DVS333
Turning, SOMEONE stares with an enamored look.
THE_VOW_DVS334
A clean-cut blonde man in a suit holds her gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS335
SOMEONE smirks.
THE_VOW_DVS336
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE who gives SOMEONE a haughty glance on his way to the bar.
THE_VOW_DVS337
As the reunited friends chat, SOMEONE stands awkwardly apart.
THE_VOW_DVS338
Later, at his recording studio.
THE_VOW_DVS339
SOMEONE frowns dizzily.
THE_VOW_DVS340
Now they sit outside.
THE_VOW_DVS341
SOMEONE glances over, then shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS342
SOMEONE stares off thoughtfully.
THE_VOW_DVS343
Now, an L-train trundles over a bridge. Riding on board, SOMEONE glances out her window, as her train crosses an intersecting rail line.
THE_VOW_DVS344
Later, elevator doors open and she strides past a reception desk in an upscale office.
THE_VOW_DVS345
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE on the phone in his office. They swap a wave.
THE_VOW_DVS346
Facing his ex, he grins from ear to ear.
THE_VOW_DVS347
He gestures cordially, and SOMEONE takes a seat in front of his desk.
THE_VOW_DVS348
Sitting behind it, he shoots her a quizzical look.
THE_VOW_DVS349
Wincing, SOMEONE glances away.
THE_VOW_DVS350
He rises.
THE_VOW_DVS351
He half-sits on the front of his desk.
THE_VOW_DVS352
Averting her gaze, SOMEONE nods disappointedly.
THE_VOW_DVS353
They both stand.
THE_VOW_DVS354
With a bashful smile, SOMEONE hugs him.
THE_VOW_DVS355
He hesitates then wraps his arms around her and wraps his arms around her and rests this chin on her shoulder.
THE_VOW_DVS356
As they inch apart, SOMEONE cradles the back of his head and they kiss.
THE_VOW_DVS358
Blinking back tears, she struggles to remain composed.
THE_VOW_DVS359
She bites her lip.
THE_VOW_DVS361
Later, at the apartment, she kneels on the dining table, adding photographs to rows of images organized in front of her. Other photos lie in disarray behind her.
THE_VOW_DVS363
SOMEONE enters.
THE_VOW_DVS364
He kisses her cheek, which unsettles her.
THE_VOW_DVS365
As she rests her elbows on the table, he rubs her shoulders.
THE_VOW_DVS366
He tickles her and she jumps.
THE_VOW_DVS367
He ducks into their bedroom.
THE_VOW_DVS368
She stares after him.
THE_VOW_DVS369
Standing just out of view by the doorway, SOMEONE clenches a fist. SOMEONE shifts her sad eyes, then turns away.
THE_VOW_DVS372
SOMEONE pours herself coffee then walks to SOMEONE who reads the paper.
THE_VOW_DVS373
She sits in front of him.
THE_VOW_DVS374
Smiling, he heads off. Outside they walk an alley.
THE_VOW_DVS376
Entering the studio, SOMEONE gazes around the spacious, rugged room, cluttered with works in progress and supplies. One bronzy 10-foot sculpture, shaped vaguely like a mermaid bears a pebbled texture. Sketches hang out of a few half-open drawers and a dresser 10 drawers high.
THE_VOW_DVS377
They explore the room.
THE_VOW_DVS378
SOMEONE examines a treelike nymph sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS379
Its trunk resembles a woman’s torso.
THE_VOW_DVS380
SOMEONE gives a sad smile.
THE_VOW_DVS381
She edges past an industrial pedestal fan.
THE_VOW_DVS382
She wrings her hands, eying a feminine sculpture in repose.
THE_VOW_DVS383
He moves to her unfinished piece.
THE_VOW_DVS384
He offers a sculpting knife.
THE_VOW_DVS385
Standing at a partially-formed clay sculpture, SOMEONE gives a tense look.
THE_VOW_DVS386
He bounces over to the stereo and turns it on.
THE_VOW_DVS387
He dances back to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS388
As SOMEONE trudges back to the stereo, SOMEONE heaves a ponderous breath.
THE_VOW_DVS389
SOMEONE slams down the sound system’s control deck.
THE_VOW_DVS390
SOMEONE straightens and peers morosely at him.
THE_VOW_DVS391
She drops her admonished gaze. He shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS392
With an exasperated look, he heads to the door.
THE_VOW_DVS393
SOMEONE watches him leave the studio,
THE_VOW_DVS394
then blinks her troubled eyes. She turns away from the unfinished sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS395
Outside, SOMEONE trudges down the alley. His hands curl tensely as they swing at his sides.
THE_VOW_DVS397
In the studio, SOMEONE eyes the section of wall covered in drawings and other artwork,
THE_VOW_DVS398
then faces her towering, treelike sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS399
She eyes its twisted trunk with branches jutting out from the top, like hair on its head.
THE_VOW_DVS400
Lowering her gaze, she strides for the door and irritably tosses down a piece of clay on her way out.
THE_VOW_DVS401
Now, SOMEONE’s Wagoneer rounds a corner by the apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS402
At home, SOMEONE writes in a notebook.
THE_VOW_DVS403
She tears out a sheet.
THE_VOW_DVS404
She folds it hurriedly as SOMEONE walks in.
THE_VOW_DVS405
SOMEONE faces the bathroom. Seated at her desk, SOMEONE stands nervously.
THE_VOW_DVS406
SOMEONE goes to a bag on the bed.
THE_VOW_DVS407
Her father SOMEONE exits the bathroom.
THE_VOW_DVS408
SOMEONE continues packing.
THE_VOW_DVS409
SOMEONE carries two bags out.
THE_VOW_DVS410
SOMEONE puts down his shoulder satchel and regards SOMEONE with a wounded expression.
THE_VOW_DVS411
SOMEONE averts his considerate gaze, shakes his head and shifts on his feet.
THE_VOW_DVS412
SOMEONE gives a relieved grin and nods.
THE_VOW_DVS413
Coming forward, she obliges warmly.
THE_VOW_DVS414
She steps back, smiles at SOMEONE and leaves.
THE_VOW_DVS415
Her husband turns on the spot.
THE_VOW_DVS416
His jaw clenches, agonizing.
THE_VOW_DVS417
Now a penlight shines directly on SOMEONE’s jade green eye.
THE_VOW_DVS418
She looks to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS419
Her mom looks away worriedly then puts on a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS420
Her smile tenses.
THE_VOW_DVS421
She moves stiffly past SOMEONE’s doctor and leaves the room.
THE_VOW_DVS422
Under the doctor’s compassionate smile,
THE_VOW_DVS423
the young woman briefly hangs her head.
THE_VOW_DVS425
SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
THE_VOW_DVS426
At the studio, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE as she works a recording session.
THE_VOW_DVS427
Teens play on the other side of the glass.
THE_VOW_DVS428
SOMEONE wears a suit jacket and narrow tie worn over a crisp white shirt.
THE_VOW_DVS429
SOMEONE flips a control board switch.
THE_VOW_DVS430
Lily’s gaze softens, sympathetically.
THE_VOW_DVS431
SOMEONE marches out.
THE_VOW_DVS433
Outside the Thornton’s mansion, elegant guests attend an engagement party in an immaculately tended back yard.
THE_VOW_DVS434
Passing SOMEONE, SOMEONE happens upon SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS435
Nearby, SOMEONE glowers.
THE_VOW_DVS436
As he leaves, SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS437
He smirks cryptically.
THE_VOW_DVS438
As he steps away, SOMEONE beams after him.
THE_VOW_DVS439
Now, SOMEONE strolls the patio, sipping a glass of red wine.
THE_VOW_DVS440
He turns.
THE_VOW_DVS441
Her styled hair has highlights.
THE_VOW_DVS442
He stares at her groomed and lightened tresses.
THE_VOW_DVS443
Behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE and a blonde woman converse with SOMEONE Thornton.
THE_VOW_DVS444
Now, at home, SOMEONE puts on a dark blazer over a muted blue button down, then picks up a tie.
THE_VOW_DVS445
Later, he walks a demurely dressed SOMEONE to his Wagoneer.
THE_VOW_DVS446
SOMEONE chuckles as he strides briskly around the car.
THE_VOW_DVS447
Later, under gleaming skyscraper windows, the SUV pulls into a space in a deserted civic parking lot
THE_VOW_DVS448
situated before a crosswalk.
THE_VOW_DVS449
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE, then looks around uncertainly.
THE_VOW_DVS450
Her husband regards her with a tender gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS451
SOMEONE responds with a warm appreciative smile.
THE_VOW_DVS452
Now at SOMEONE Mnemonic, the front window shows SOMEONE and SOMEONE enjoying a meal and wine at a table for two.
THE_VOW_DVS453
He presents chocolates.
THE_VOW_DVS454
She smirks inquisitively.
THE_VOW_DVS455
She selects a chocolate, then pops it in her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS456
She frowns.
THE_VOW_DVS457
As SOMEONE chews the second truffle her eyes light up with a surprised smile.
THE_VOW_DVS458
She turns the box of chocolates to face SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS459
SOMEONE eats one, SOMEONE pops another in her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS460
SOMEONE takes a deep breath, then tries another.
THE_VOW_DVS461
SOMEONE skeptically chews another truffle.
THE_VOW_DVS462
A fleck of truffle filling drops from her mouth onto her hair.
THE_VOW_DVS463
They both crack up.
THE_VOW_DVS464
SOMEONE reaches for the fleck. SOMEONE rocks in her seat.
THE_VOW_DVS465
Later, in the night air,
THE_VOW_DVS466
SOMEONE’s SUV halts on a narrow lane in a quaintly lit public park.
THE_VOW_DVS467
He smiles at SOMEONE and directs her gaze out the windshield.
THE_VOW_DVS468
SOMEONE unbuttons his shirt and SOMEONE’s smile fades.
THE_VOW_DVS469
He removes his shirt.
THE_VOW_DVS470
He sets a small wetsuit beside her and regards her with a subdued, wily smile.
THE_VOW_DVS471
SOMEONE frowns, intrigued.
THE_VOW_DVS472
SOMEONE unbuckles her safety belt, then writhes in her seat, working her demure dress off over her head.
THE_VOW_DVS473
SOMEONE takes a peek.
THE_VOW_DVS475
SOMEONE shakes her hair out.
THE_VOW_DVS476
SOMEONE turns.
THE_VOW_DVS477
He laughs as she dashes out in her bra and panties. Grabbing blankets and towels he hustles after her and does high steps to get out of his jeans.
THE_VOW_DVS478
SOMEONE runs into the water up to her ankles and bids a hasty retreat.
THE_VOW_DVS479
Clad in biker briefs, SOMEONE grabs her around the waist and carries her back in.
THE_VOW_DVS480
Joining hands they run further out into the glistening lake.
THE_VOW_DVS481
SOMEONE plunges in and SOMEONE submerges up to her shoulders.
THE_VOW_DVS482
SOMEONE lifts both her feet and her upper body dunks up to her chin.
THE_VOW_DVS483
Now he helps SOMEONE up and gives her a piggyback ride ashore.
THE_VOW_DVS484
Grabbing a towel and blanket, he wraps both around her.
THE_VOW_DVS485
SOMEONE hurries back into his car and he follows.
THE_VOW_DVS486
SOMEONE wraps a blanket around his shivering shoulders and laughs with SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS487
SOMEONE considers, then envelops her hands in both his own.
THE_VOW_DVS488
He blows on her fingers then kisses them tenderly.
THE_VOW_DVS490
Now at the apartment, keys slide along the dining table. At its far end, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sway in an embrace.
THE_VOW_DVS491
SOMEONE smiles fondly.
THE_VOW_DVS492
In the soft light of the streetlamps outside, he plants two tender kisses on her lips.
THE_VOW_DVS494
Leaning close, she brushes SOMEONE’s blanket off his shoulders, while letting her own fall to the floor.
THE_VOW_DVS495
Standing in their underwear, they kiss again.
THE_VOW_DVS496
SOMEONE smiles up at him sweetly, and his parted lips find hers.
THE_VOW_DVS497
The young woman wraps an arm around her husband’s bare shoulder
THE_VOW_DVS498
and he cradles her head in his hand.
THE_VOW_DVS499
SOMEONE’s hand finds his cheek and caresses it softly.
THE_VOW_DVS500
As they make out, we look on from the far end of the table.
THE_VOW_DVS501
Our view sinks into the shadows.
THE_VOW_DVS502
Now, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE out of his car.
THE_VOW_DVS503
SOMEONE heads toward her parents' house.
THE_VOW_DVS504
She faces him.
THE_VOW_DVS506
Her smile gone, SOMEONE shifts her uneasy gaze. SOMEONE shakes his head earnestly.
THE_VOW_DVS507
SOMEONE hunches her shoulders and looks away.
THE_VOW_DVS508
She meets his gaze with a gentle smile.
THE_VOW_DVS509
SOMEONE lingers on the spot, shifting boyishly on his feet as his wife enters her parents’ home.
THE_VOW_DVS510
As she shuts the door, he turns away and steps around his car.
THE_VOW_DVS511
Inside the house, SOMEONE sets down her keys and takes off her shoes.
THE_VOW_DVS512
In the next room, SOMEONE waits up seated with a book.
THE_VOW_DVS513
SOMEONE smiles sadly, her eyes welling up.
THE_VOW_DVS514
SOMEONE shakes her head tearfully.
THE_VOW_DVS515
SOMEONE gives her a hug.
THE_VOW_DVS516
On a sunny day, SOMEONE walks with his friends.
THE_VOW_DVS517
At the Thornton’s.
THE_VOW_DVS518
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a folder.
THE_VOW_DVS519
SOMEONE’s mother joins them.
THE_VOW_DVS520
SOMEONE hands the file to his daughter.
THE_VOW_DVS522
At dusk in the city, two elevated trains pass one another under the Chicago skyline.
THE_VOW_DVS523
In the apartment, SOMEONE drops a jacket on a chair and carries a stack of mail to a coffee table.
THE_VOW_DVS524
Sitting, he flips through the envelopes.
THE_VOW_DVS525
He pauses, then tosses them down.
THE_VOW_DVS527
a pink envelope bears a stamp reading Past Due.
THE_VOW_DVS528
SOMEONE wearily leans back on the sofa and stares at the ceiling.
THE_VOW_DVS529
Now, on a sunny day,
THE_VOW_DVS530
yellow rose petals arc through the air as wedding guests shower them on SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS531
In their tux and gown,
THE_VOW_DVS532
the newlyweds joyfully make their way up a narrow aisle between the well-wishers.
THE_VOW_DVS533
Later, the groom sweeps his bride up in his arms.
THE_VOW_DVS534
She laughs delightedly and he kisses her cheek.
THE_VOW_DVS535
Later still, SOMEONE steps toward SOMEONE, but then holds back as she joins her sister for a wedding photo.
THE_VOW_DVS537
the photographer takes a picture of the sisters, their parents, and SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS538
The bridal party moves on without SOMEONE, who stands among the guests.
THE_VOW_DVS539
He turns on the spot, watching SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS540
She smiles briefly at him, then turns away.
THE_VOW_DVS541
SOMEONE moves unhappily through the crowd.
THE_VOW_DVS542
Later, with his necktie loosened,
THE_VOW_DVS543
he strolls through a lavish outdoor reception
THE_VOW_DVS544
and spies SOMEONE dancing with her sister.
THE_VOW_DVS545
She fails to notice him and he moves on sullenly.
THE_VOW_DVS546
Reaching the edge of the party, he arrives at a crenelated terrace, overlooking the city’s distant gleaming skyline.
THE_VOW_DVS547
As he gazes off morosely,
THE_VOW_DVS548
SOMEONE approaches with a bottle of fine liquor.
THE_VOW_DVS549
He sets two glasses on the parapet.
THE_VOW_DVS550
SOMEONE pours the drinks.
THE_VOW_DVS551
They clink glasses.
THE_VOW_DVS552
The two men sip the amber liquor.
THE_VOW_DVS553
SOMEONE cocks his head and nods appreciatively.
THE_VOW_DVS554
SOMEONE puts down his glass, SOMEONE does the same.
THE_VOW_DVS555
SOMEONE takes another sip.
THE_VOW_DVS556
The young man turns away.
THE_VOW_DVS557
SOMEONE stares at him.
THE_VOW_DVS558
From the reception, Mrs. Thornton notices the exchange.
THE_VOW_DVS559
Moving past him, SOMEONE leaves the terrace.
THE_VOW_DVS560
The older man hesitantly takes a drink of his whiskey.
THE_VOW_DVS561
Behind him, SOMEONE goes inside.
THE_VOW_DVS562
Setting his drink on a coaster, he plunks onto an elegant leather sofa.
THE_VOW_DVS563
SOMEONE approaches, finishing off his own drink.
THE_VOW_DVS564
They stand toe to toe.
THE_VOW_DVS565
SOMEONE swallows and vaguely flashes a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS567
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE staring at him, stunned.
THE_VOW_DVS568
She marches off.
THE_VOW_DVS569
SOMEONE looks down at SOMEONE, who sprawls on the floor with a bleeding nose, then follows SOMEONE outside.
THE_VOW_DVS570
SOMEONE’s eyes glisten.
THE_VOW_DVS571
SOMEONE wears a bitter, tearful smile.
THE_VOW_DVS572
Blinking back tears, SOMEONE bravely meets her forgiving gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS573
He grows stoic.
THE_VOW_DVS574
SOMEONE averts her regretful gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS575
Bowing his head, SOMEONE shuffles back a few steps, then heads inside.
THE_VOW_DVS576
SOMEONE helplessly turns on the spot.
THE_VOW_DVS577
Pausing by the door he faces his wife.
THE_VOW_DVS578
SOMEONE regards her longingly, then turns away and walks back inside.
THE_VOW_DVS579
SOMEONE stares after her estranged husband, then takes a few deep steadying breaths and shuts her eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS580
Back in the city, SOMEONE lumbers down a sidewalk parallel to elevated train tracks.
THE_VOW_DVS581
His suit jacket dangling from one hand, and his tie hanging from the other.
THE_VOW_DVS582
His head droops forward and he transfers his coat to his other hand.
THE_VOW_DVS583
Now in his recording studio, SOMEONE sits playing an acoustic guitar.
THE_VOW_DVS584
The view drifts past stacked equipment and microphone stands as we watch the heartbroken young man play.
THE_VOW_DVS585
On the other side of the glass, two lamps turn on in the mixing room.
THE_VOW_DVS586
SOMEONE walks into view casually and peers at the soundboard.
THE_VOW_DVS587
In the recording room SOMEONE gently plucks the guitar strings.
THE_VOW_DVS588
His lips hold a pensive frown.
THE_VOW_DVS589
From the other side of the glass, SOMEONE stares at him, then leaves the room.
THE_VOW_DVS590
Unnoticing, SOMEONE’s eyes remain on the instrument in his hands.
THE_VOW_DVS591
His wedding ring gleams on his finger as his left hand sets up cords on the fret board.
THE_VOW_DVS592
SOMEONE walks up to him with folded arms.
THE_VOW_DVS593
SOMEONE gives a tearful sympathetic nod.
THE_VOW_DVS594
SOMEONE stares off, tears welling in his deep set eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS595
He wipes one away, sets his guitar down and faces his friend.
THE_VOW_DVS596
With a knowing shake of his head, he leaves his sorrowful friend stunned.
THE_VOW_DVS597
Out in the night, a gliding view of Chicago’s streets and high rises presents a vast expanse of speckled lights.
THE_VOW_DVS598
In SOMEONE’s now cleaned out studio,
THE_VOW_DVS599
SOMEONE finishes packing a box.
THE_VOW_DVS600
A half dozen empty worktables fill the room.
THE_VOW_DVS601
SOMEONE closes the box and carries it out.
THE_VOW_DVS602
Passing a trio of tall gracefully curved sculptures.
THE_VOW_DVS603
Outside, SOMEONE loads the box on top of another in the back of his Wagoneer, then shuts the rear gate.
THE_VOW_DVS604
As he goes back inside,
THE_VOW_DVS605
a few pots of leggy dying flowers come into view.
THE_VOW_DVS606
The plank mounded with SOMEONE’s clay scraps sits discarded beside them.
THE_VOW_DVS607
Now the bean shaped  cloud gate in Millennium Park reflects an overcast day.
THE_VOW_DVS608
Inside a high-rise building,
THE_VOW_DVS609
a woman at a conference table slides legal documents to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS610
Next to a notary’s embossed stamp, he locates SOMEONE’s signature on a line labeled Plaintiff.
THE_VOW_DVS611
Above a phrase reads, Joint Petition for Simplified Dissolution of Marriage.
THE_VOW_DVS612
SOMEONE glances at the lawyer and signs his name on a line marked Defendant.
THE_VOW_DVS613
He twists the pen shut, drops it and leaves the table.
THE_VOW_DVS614
Now shirtless on a cloudy day,
THE_VOW_DVS615
the broad chested young man takes the garbage out
THE_VOW_DVS616
and finds the stray cat perched on the trash bin.
THE_VOW_DVS617
Munching a slice of pizza, he offers some to the cat.
THE_VOW_DVS618
The feline shows no interest in the food, but lets SOMEONE pick him up.
THE_VOW_DVS619
The cat’s paws rest on SOMEONE’s shoulder, as he carries the animal inside.
THE_VOW_DVS620
Now SOMEONE spots SOMEONE at a market and quickly turns tail.
THE_VOW_DVS621
SOMEONE grins at the apprehensive woman.
THE_VOW_DVS622
SOMEONE's words sink in hard.
THE_VOW_DVS623
SOMEONE approaches.
THE_VOW_DVS624
She sees SOMEONE hurrying out the door.
THE_VOW_DVS625
With a reluctant look, she faces her sister and meets her gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS626
SOMEONE shrugs her hands.
THE_VOW_DVS627
SOMEONE nods.
THE_VOW_DVS628
SOMEONE rushes away.
THE_VOW_DVS629
Now SOMEONE finds her mother gardening in front of the house.
THE_VOW_DVS630
SOMEONE shoves down her bicycle.
THE_VOW_DVS631
Her mother bows her head.
THE_VOW_DVS632
Shaking her head, her mother lowers her tearful eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS633
Smiling, she wipes away tears.
THE_VOW_DVS634
SOMEONE’s eyes brim with tears.
THE_VOW_DVS635
SOMEONE slouches and shakes her head to herself.
THE_VOW_DVS636
She shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS637
Glaring, she walks away.
THE_VOW_DVS638
Her mother remains kneeling before the autumn flowerbed.
THE_VOW_DVS639
Now in the city, a water taxi glides under a bridge.
THE_VOW_DVS640
SOMEONE and a young woman follow the sidewalk in front of his apartment building.
THE_VOW_DVS641
As they stroll into the alley, SOMEONE’s grin fades.
THE_VOW_DVS642
His ex-wife sits on a stoop with her head rested on her hands. She awkwardly gets to her feet.
THE_VOW_DVS643
Closing her eyes for a moment, SOMEONE winces.
THE_VOW_DVS644
SOMEONE watches his female friend leave, then faces SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS645
He steps closer.
THE_VOW_DVS646
SOMEONE glances aside.
THE_VOW_DVS647
She sits back down on the stoop.
THE_VOW_DVS648
SOMEONE takes a seat beside her.
THE_VOW_DVS649
SOMEONE studies him, her expression growing tender.
THE_VOW_DVS650
As SOMEONE regards her, she sucks in a breath and gazes off thoughtfully.
THE_VOW_DVS651
SOMEONE shakes her head and drops her face in her hands.
THE_VOW_DVS652
Folding them she stares off.
THE_VOW_DVS653
Meeting SOMEONE’s gaze, she shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS654
He returns a gentle look and she considers him.
THE_VOW_DVS655
Now at North Western Law,
THE_VOW_DVS656
SOMEONE sits in a lecture classroom with her notebook open.
THE_VOW_DVS657
As the other students around her diligently take notes and type on laptops,
THE_VOW_DVS658
SOMEONE draws in her notebook,
THE_VOW_DVS659
making sketches that resemble the treelike sculptures in her former studio.
THE_VOW_DVS660
Later, at a water taxi stop on the river, she walks with SOMEONE up a flight of stairs.
THE_VOW_DVS661
SOMEONE glances away.
THE_VOW_DVS662
She gazes at him with an apologetic look.
THE_VOW_DVS663
He forces a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS664
As they head up to the street, she takes his arm in a friendly gesture.
THE_VOW_DVS665
Now SOMEONE sits on a bench on the law school’s quad and stares into the distance.
THE_VOW_DVS666
Her father approaches.
THE_VOW_DVS667
He takes a seat beside her.
THE_VOW_DVS668
SOMEONE’s smile fades.
THE_VOW_DVS669
He stands.
THE_VOW_DVS670
Her gaze flickers over him.
THE_VOW_DVS671
He eyes her lovingly and gives a faint smile.
THE_VOW_DVS673
Seen in slow motion, SOMEONE hugs him, her chin pressing firmly to his shoulder.
THE_VOW_DVS674
Now in the alley by the flowerpot garden, fall turns to winter. Snow veils SOMEONE’s clay scrap pile.
THE_VOW_DVS675
Now Page paints animals on a nursery wall.
THE_VOW_DVS676
Her pregnant sister smiles, watching.
THE_VOW_DVS677
The sisters admire the mural which shows a giraffe, an elephant, and a lion balancing atop round trees.
THE_VOW_DVS678
SOMEONE listens as a band records in his studio.
THE_VOW_DVS679
In a new apartment, SOMEONE ladles her parents’ soup.
THE_VOW_DVS680
The cat lies on SOMEONE’s stomach.
THE_VOW_DVS681
SOMEONE sculpts in her apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS682
Rifling through an unpacked box, SOMEONE finds the SOMEONE Mnemonic menu with her vows written on it. She reads.
THE_VOW_DVS683
A factory style window shows a nighttime view of a light snowfall and a car traveling the warmly lit street.
THE_VOW_DVS684
SOMEONE looks away thoughtfully.
THE_VOW_DVS685
Now SOMEONE holds his coat, closed around his neck as he walks past a row of snow dusted Christmas trees for sale.
THE_VOW_DVS686
Striding down a sidewalk with hunched shoulders,
THE_VOW_DVS687
he blows on his cupped hands.
THE_VOW_DVS688
As he reaches the entrance to SOMEONE Mnemonic,
THE_VOW_DVS689
he finds a note written on a menu taped to the glass.
THE_VOW_DVS690
It reads, snow day.
THE_VOW_DVS691
He gives a disappointed look.
THE_VOW_DVS692
Meanwhile SOMEONE heads toward the SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS693
Turning from the entrance SOMEONE starts to walk off, but spots SOMEONE approaching.
THE_VOW_DVS694
She stops and puts her hands in her coat pockets.
THE_VOW_DVS695
Grinning, she steps closer.
THE_VOW_DVS696
He gazes tenderly at her, then glances at the SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS697
He stares at her radiant smile.
THE_VOW_DVS698
He smiles.
THE_VOW_DVS699
His eyes shine with tears.
THE_VOW_DVS700
She nods then lifts her eyes to the falling snow.
THE_VOW_DVS701
He follows her gaze skyward.
THE_VOW_DVS702
The corners of SOMEONE’s mouth tug into a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS703
She shakes her head.
THE_VOW_DVS704
Stifling a grin, he gives a satisfied nod.
THE_VOW_DVS705
They head down the sidewalk.
THE_VOW_DVS706
She takes his arm as they head down the snowy street in the opposite direction.
THE_VOW_DVS707
An L train glides overhead.
THE_VOW_DVS708
Our view widens to show the glittering city scape.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS19
Opening it, she finds earrings inside.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS20
Stifling a disappointed look, she holds them up and forces a grin.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS22
His five friends all turn and stare at him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS24
Cooking in her kitchen, SOMEONE gets a text: Mind if I hang with the guys? I'll pick up some pizza on the way home.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS26
He leans in too close.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS28
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trade places.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS29
The woman averts her gloomy gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS30
With a smile, he turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS31
SOMEONE counts down on his fingers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS32
He cocks his head at SOMEONE, then turns back to the pretty woman.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS34
Everyone but SOMEONE raises their beer.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS37
At the Ritz-Carlton.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS38
She watches from her treadmill in a kitchen.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS39
A young man with tattoos across his pecs, shoulders, and arms sleeps in bed. The woman from the coffee shop stands over him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS40
Stretching, he opens his eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS42
She gives him another quick kiss, then heads into the bathroom.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS43
He dresses hastily.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS45
She reemerges.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS46
She finds a note on the bed reading, Michelle, it was fun.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS50
People fight over copies.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS53
SOMEONE reads as she heads down a sidewalk. The successful business woman crosses paths with her and rolls her eyes. Now words type out: The Mama's Boy vs. The Single Mom
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS54
In a SOMEONE and Noble, SOMEONE spots the single mother two paces ahead of him in line.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS55
She hides her SOMEONE Harvey book under a kitten calendar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS56
He dawns glasses from a display and grins.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS57
SOMEONE steps up to the register. SOMEONE gives the next guy a pleading look, and he lets him cut ahead.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS58
Noting his disappointed look, SOMEONE turns away and collects her purchase.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS59
She faces him with a surprised expression, then allows a hopeful smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS60
At an open house: The Non-Committer vs. The Girl Who Wants The Ring
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS61
A pregnant couple enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS62
As the well-dressed husband helps his wife down a few steps, SOMEONE's friend's jaw drops.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS63
The guys play horse.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS64
Steadying himself on SOMEONE, SOMEONE lifts his leg and shoots the ball with one hand. It bounces off the rim.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS65
SOMEONE sneers at displayed toys and a bong.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS66
She knocks over a giant toy robot.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS69
SOMEONE arrives.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS70
Words appear: The Dreamer vs. The Woman Who Is Her Own Man
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS72
He and two friends eyed the successful woman.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS73
At the table, she sits with SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS75
She shows the book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS77
Now SOMEONE returns home to find bare walls and empty shelves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS78
He drops his pizza box.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS79
A brown lumpy sofa with duct taped cushions
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS80
She shows some catalogs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS81
He kisses her cheek.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS83
He turns on the TV.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS84
With SOMEONE and a friend.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS85
SOMEONE approaches.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS86
The Player vs. The 90-Day Rule Girl
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS87
SOMEONE gives a downward twitch of her lip.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS89
SOMEONE stands nearby.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS91
As her friend chuckles, SOMEONE's face relaxes with a conceding smile. She shakes his hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS92
At the restaurant the chef approaches SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS93
Outside, SOMEONE approaches her car and hands over her valet ticket.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS96
SOMEONE watches her slide her jacket off revealing her silky smooth bare shoulders.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS97
With a little smile, she gets in behind the wheel.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS98
Keeping his eyes on her, SOMEONE opens the car's gull-wing door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS99
As SOMEONE drives away, he speeds off after her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS100
Now that Mercedes races around a corner. Stopped at a red light, SOMEONE watches it in her rear view mirror as it slows and pulls up to her right side.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS101
She lowers her passenger side window.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS102
SOMEONE searches the many buttons on the console.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS103
He self-consciously lifts a finger signaling her to wait.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS104
His gull-wing door slowly rises.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS106
She tosses it across the room.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS107
Sucking in her cheeks, she gazes out at the city through floor-to-ceiling windows. Her eyes slowly shift back toward it.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS108
Now SOMEONE highlights a question in SOMEONE's book,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS109
What are your short-term goals?
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS111
The guys play a half court three-on-three game. SOMEONE tries for a three-pointer, but it bounces off the rim and SOMEONE gets the rebound.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS112
SOMEONE rubs the ball against his crotch, then tosses it to SOMEONEt. He catches it in his shirt.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS113
Later, SOMEONE arrives at home to find it completely redecorated.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS114
Exiting a room, a well-dressed man almost collides with him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS115
He spots two guys moving a chair.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS116
He grabs his chair as movers carry it off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS118
The designer turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS119
Now at SOMEONE's apartment, her friend grins as SOMEONE enters the living room wearing a tight black dress.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS120
SOMEONE returns to the living room in a form-fitting sheath dress, with a longer skirt.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS121
She examines her reflection in a full-length mirror.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS122
SOMEONE gives Sonia a disappointed look, then turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS124
At the Ritz-Carlton Residences, two suited men open the front double doors for SOMEONE as she strides out,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS125
dressed in the form-fitting cocktail dress.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS127
He holds a Town Car's door open and she climbs in. He gratefully blows kisses skyward.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS128
Sitting beside her, he gives her a rose.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS129
Dressed in a chauffeur's uniform, SOMEONE turns forward and drives off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS130
Now as SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk toward his car, he hits the locks remote.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS131
He heads to the driver's side.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS133
He speeds off. SOMEONE stares after him, her jaw hanging.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS134
The car backs up, returning to the curb in front of her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS135
SOMEONE takes a steadying breath.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS136
She rolls her eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS137
SOMEONE climbs out of the car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS138
He opens her door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS140
Now his red Taurus sedan drives off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS142
SOMEONE nods.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS143
She gives SOMEONE a frustrated look. He holds up a placating hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS145
At dinner with SOMEONE and SOMEONE
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS146
With SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS147
She sips wine.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS148
Lifting her brow, she drinks innocently.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS149
She offers a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS150
He lifts his wine glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS151
Now lying back on the bed beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE exhales smoke.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS152
SOMEONE releases a stream of it as well.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS153
Furrowing his brow, he gives her a baffled look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS154
Later in the car with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS155
She looks away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS156
He hands her the case.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS157
She eyes his photo.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS158
He turns away thoughtfully.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS159
He hits a button on his steering wheel.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS160
He closes his eyes, then gazes at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS162
As SOMEONE gazes off, his eyes forlorn, SOMEONE listens intently.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS163
He shifts his gaze to the stereo's display panel.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS164
SOMEONE scrutinizes him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS165
He locks eyes with her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS166
She glances away, then shoots him a contemplative look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS167
Now at SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE kisses her neck as she takes off his belt.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS168
He picks her up with her knees straddling his waist.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS169
He sets her down.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS170
She kisses him passionately. Now at SOMEONE's front door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS171
SOMEONE tentatively leans in for a kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS172
She meets his lips with hers. As they separate, SOMEONE grins.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS173
The door opens.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS174
Watching him, SOMEONE grins.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS175
Duke slams the door. Outside SOMEONE's
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS176
Smiling, she gazes at him hungrily, then gives him a passionate kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS177
With a cool look, she opens the door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS178
She flashes a smile, then closes it.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS179
SOMEONE turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS180
Inside, SOMEONE places a red X beside another on a monthly calendar. Morning.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS181
Our view drifts toward downtown Los Angeles where pale, pink light lines the horizon.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS182
In her apartment,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS183
SOMEONE stretches her arm across the bed as she awakes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS184
Finding the spot beside her vacant, she sits up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS185
Shirtless, SOMEONE enters the room.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS186
He offers a glass of orange juice.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS187
He takes her glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS188
She forks up a bite.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS189
He hands her the glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS190
Averting her gaze, she takes a sip, then returns the drink.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS191
He spots a framed photo with SOMEONE in it.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS192
He crawls onto the bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS193
He kisses her, then lowers himself on top of her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS194
Now, at his loft apartment,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS195
SOMEONE pads into the kitchen wearing only pajama pants.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS197
SOMEONE receives a text message.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS198
She reads.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS200
SOMEONE arrives
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS201
with SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS202
SOMEONE frowns.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS203
Now SOMEONE joins his friends at the bar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS207
She settles into bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS208
He does the same, but they both lie awake.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS209
SOMEONE plays a video game with Duke. Later, he shows a photo.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS210
Turning, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in his underwear.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS211
Ron Artest approaches.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS214
He turns and slaps each of his reluctant friends' hands. Behind him, SOMEONE Leslie and three more NBA players approach.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS215
He turns.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS216
SOMEONE turns back to his friends, leaning his hands on his knees.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS217
SOMEONE tries to grab the ball out of Ron's hands. He hangs on it, pulling with his full weight, then falls to the floor.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS218
He points to SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS219
Now at a luncheon at a JW Marriott banquet room.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS222
As she goes to the podium, SOMEONE brings out a tray of salads. His jaw drops. As he turns to leave, he knocks over another server. SOMEONE sees him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS223
SOMEONE enters his mother's house.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS224
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE looks around.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS225
SOMEONE's mom glares over her wine glass, taking a long sip. SOMEONE notices a picture of SOMEONE as a boy.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS226
Frowning, his mom leaves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS227
At a wall of photos,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS228
SOMEONE peeks into a room decorated with trophies and posters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS230
SOMEONE shifts her wide-eyed gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS231
Now SOMEONE reads a chapter titled, Mama's Boys. Snippets read, Excessively attached to their mother's. He doesn't want to grow up. They just can't compete.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS232
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in his car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS233
Now she leads the way into her apartment.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS235
As SOMEONE steps down the hall, SOMEONE flips through her collection of record albums.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS236
He flips a record between his hands, sets it on the player, and gently drops the needle.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS237
Stepping back,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS238
SOMEONE takes breath spray from his pocket and squirts some into his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS239
He gets out two condoms and looks at their different wrappings,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS240
stuffing a gold one back in his pocket,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS242
unbuttons his shirt and peels off his jacket.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS243
SOMEONE returns with a tray.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS244
Now at the loft, SOMEONE rubs his fingers in between his toes, smells them, then wipes them on the arm of his leather chair.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS246
He takes two beers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS247
With SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS248
They see SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS249
As he strides off, Sonia laughs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS250
With SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS251
The guys head out of the gym.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS252
She takes SOMEONE's wine glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS254
Inside, the guys toast with shots.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS259
She playfully waves a bite in front of his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS260
He finds SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS262
SOMEONE makes a call.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS263
SOMEONE enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS264
SOMEONE starts toward him, and SOMEONE quickly leaves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS265
SOMEONE's eyes dart searchingly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS266
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE on a modern sofa.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS268
SOMEONE comes down the stairs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS269
SOMEONE sips some milk.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS270
SOMEONE spits out his water.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS271
Now SOMEONE opens the loft door for SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS272
With a little pout, she enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS273
Gazing around the expansive modern space, she mouths, Whoa.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS274
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE watches him pour a glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS275
He steps close, offering a glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS276
SOMEONE side-steps away from him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS277
SOMEONE stifles a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS278
He moves closer. She toasts bluntly, then takes another side-step.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS279
Finishing her sip of wine, SOMEONE closes her eyes ecstatically.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS281
Before an impressive view of the city, an elegantly set table for two sits surrounded by candlelight.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS282
Keeping his gaze on here, SOMEONE gives a soft nod.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS283
The couple approaches the table and a nearby service cart.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS284
As SOMEONE wraps his arms around SOMEONE from behind,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS285
SOMEONE arrives bearing a covered tray.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS286
He fumbles the trays lid.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS287
As SOMEONE leaves the couple, he shoves one of the hors d'oeuvres into his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS289
As they hold each other close, they gaze out at the city rooftops.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS290
Tucking her hair behind her ear, she gives him a little shrug.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS291
She closes her eyes for a moment,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS292
then faces SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS295
SOMEONE tosses away the rest of her hors d'oeuvre
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS296
and wraps her arms around SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS297
Now SOMEONE sits alone in his parked car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS298
Sitting on the closed toilet, SOMEONE consults SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS300
Now SOMEONE answers her door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS302
Later, spotlights at L.A. Live shine into the sky as SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll a bustling walkway.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS303
The couple looks expectantly at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS304
SOMEONE eyes her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS305
SOMEONE glances at Xavier.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS306
He meets her surprised gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS307
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE make out in his car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS309
Just as her granny panties come into view, she jumps back.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS310
She covers herself up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS311
She kisses him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS312
She hurries out of the car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS314
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's phone.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS315
SOMEONE pulls out of the driveway.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS318
SOMEONE hits his car's remote, then leaves SOMEONE's side.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS319
He opens her door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS322
SOMEONE stands at a street.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS323
SOMEONE helps Duke ride a bike.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS325
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie on the floor beside her bed, surrounded by rose petals.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS326
He kisses her, then runs his tongue along her knee.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS327
Reaching for a dish with raspberries and chocolate cake,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS328
he grabs some of the dessert and feeds it to her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS329
Now SOMEONE enters his living room, framed by one of SOMEONE's bare, bent legs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS330
He pauses and shakes his head.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS331
He sits beside her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS332
They kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS333
She nuzzles his nose with hers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS334
SOMEONE opens his eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS335
SOMEONE eyes him skeptically.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS336
With a disappointed look, she gets up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS337
Now SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE outside the Ritz.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS338
A battered sedan pulls up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS339
SOMEONE eyes the beat up silver car, with its missing front bumper, and exposed radiator as it peels out.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS340
A woman waiting in the valet area shoots SOMEONE a dubious look. The successful business woman meets her gaze with a challenging expression.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS341
A sleek black Porsche pulls into the valet area. SOMEONE's lips part in a lustful look as her eyes trail after the arriving car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS342
In slow motion, a valet heads over.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS343
A gentle breeze lifts SOMEONE's hair as she watches a tall, handsome man exit the Porsche.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS345
Sliding on a suit jacket he turns and looks at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS346
She stares, her jaw slack.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS348
He hugs her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS349
She heads off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS350
She climbs into her silver Mercedes. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch The Jefferson's.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS351
She wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS352
Grinning, he retreats. SOMEONE leans against SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS353
She turns off the TV.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS354
Now at the Santa SOMEONE SOMEONE, SOMEONE stifles a smile as she strolls with SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS355
She breaks into a grin.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS357
As she embraces her, a horrified look crosses his face.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS358
Pulling away, SOMEONE gazes into his eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS359
Later, in his bedroom, SOMEONE strips off SOMEONE's vest.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS360
Kissing her, he backs her up against a dresser and knocks over a lamp.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS362
He gazes up at her as she slides her silky tank top over her head,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS363
then lowers herself over him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS364
On the wall behind her, a framed painting shows a boxer with both gloves raised triumphantly in the air.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS366
SOMEONE lies asleep in SOMEONE's bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS368
Waking up, she finds a note in the vacant spot beside her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS369
With a dejected look, she opens it and reads, SOMEONE, ran out for breakfast. Be right back. SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS370
She shifts her thoughtful eyes, then gives a pleased look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS371
Sitting up, she scoots to the edge of the bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS372
She opens a drawer in a bedside table.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS373
Finding a photo of SOMEONE as a boy, dressed in a football uniform and posing on one knee, she picks it up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS374
Returning it, she slides the drawer open farther.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS375
She finds a copy of SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS376
She opens it to a bookmarked chapter with its heading circled: The 90-Day Rule.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS377
Later, she sits on the steps with the book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS378
SOMEONE enters, clutching a bag in his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS379
He holds a box in one hand and a drink carrier in the other.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS380
He sets the food down.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS381
His smile fades as he sees the book in her hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS383
SOMEONE opens his mouth as if to speak.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS384
She pushes him away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS385
Now SOMEONE's caller ID flashes, Work.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS386
She heads outside where SOMEONE and Duke play basketball.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS387
SOMEONE's lips stutter.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS388
SOMEONE glances away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS389
He gives an injured look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS390
She hands him his keys and phone and he heads off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS391
Later, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in an upscale restaurant.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS392
He hugs her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS393
She opens her mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS394
With a wry grin, he shakes his head and stands.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS395
Placing a hand on her shoulder,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS396
he kisses the top of her head, then leaves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS397
She gazes after him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS398
Now SOMEONE enters his apartment.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS399
He sees his posters and action figures sitting on the couch and coffee table along with a copy of SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS400
A sticky note on it reads, Found this with your stuff.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS401
Boys shack, men build homes. I'm out, K.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS402
Between its pages, he finds a printout of his unsubmitted résumé where the words, Blah, blah, blah, filled the blurb for the professional development section.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS403
Dropping the book on the coffee table,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS405
he plops down on the couch. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE drink at the bar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS406
Daytime. At Candace's, Duke sits on the stoop with a basketball and gazes off with forlorn eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS407
SOMEONE spots him from the doorway.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS408
Meanwhile, SOMEONE pushes a plate of half-eaten food away and rests his head on his hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS409
His mother looks on from the kitchen.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS410
As SOMEONE works at a valet station, a silver Mercedes, like SOMEONE's, pulls up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS411
He uncomfortably averts his eyes, then opens the driver's side door and a businessman climbs out.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS414
Later, SOMEONE gazes at a framed photo of himself and SOMEONE dressed as blue Na'vi from Avatar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS415
He sets it face down on a table.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS416
At an open house, SOMEONE stares off sadly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS417
The pregnant couple enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS418
She flashes a tight smile, which fades to a glum look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS420
Following the bartender's gaze, SOMEONE sees a woman at the end of the bar. She offers him a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS421
Now at her apartment, SOMEONE rips down her monthly calendar, which shows almost three weeks filled with red Xs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS422
Later, SOMEONE strolls down a street, stopping as he notices a for sale sign on a food truck's windshield.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS423
Now, in a dress shirt and slacks, SOMEONE joins his friends at the bar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS425
He stares at his phone.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS427
He turns to SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS428
As they clink their shots, SOMEONE stares off with wistful eyes. He shakes his head. The others drink.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS429
He downs his drink.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS430
Entering the bathroom, SOMEONE checks the stalls as he makes a phone call.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS431
In a kitchen, a full-figured woman answers the phone.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS432
Lowering the phone, he glances around.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS433
He hangs up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS434
He looks skyward.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS436
He claps a hand on SOMEONE's back.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS437
SOMEONE stares after the departing guy, who wears a pageboy cap.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS438
He checks the back of his shirt in a mirror.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS439
He glances at the vacated stall.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS440
Now SOMEONE returns to his friends' booth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS441
A woman passes behind him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS443
SOMEONE enters his mother's house, catching her in her robe as she heads upstairs with a mug in each hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS444
Frowning, she looks away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS445
SOMEONE watches her resolutely.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS446
He gives a confused look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS448
He extends a bath-brush.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS449
Now at the open house.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS450
The pregnant couple.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS451
She leads him into the backyard.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS452
The couple listens in.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS453
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS454
He drops to one knee.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS455
Gina and the wife gawk. The husband smiles. SOMEONE opens and holds out a jewelry box.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS456
SOMEONE blinks back tears.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS457
He frowns and SOMEONE stifles a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS458
Taking the ring from its box, he slides it onto SOMEONE's finger.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS459
As she gazes at it,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS460
a tear trickles down her cheek.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS461
SOMEONE lifts his glistening eyes to hers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS462
Shrugging her brow, she smirks.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS463
He eyes her questioningly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS464
The three of them watch as the engaged couple kisses.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS465
Now Sonia and SOMEONE enter the cafe during another open mic event.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS467
Sonia sees SOMEONE taking the stage.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS468
SOMEONE looks over.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS470
She tears up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS471
SOMEONE plays guitar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS472
As he glances at SOMEONE, some patrons follow his gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS473
SOMEONE follows her outside.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS475
He gives a resigned look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS476
He gives a desperate look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS477
He locks his eyes on hers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS478
He blinks earnestly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS479
As she gazes at him,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS480
her eyes filled with tears. SOMEONE steps forward and kisses her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS481
She wraps an arm around his neck.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS482
Now at her family reunion, SOMEONE sits at a picnic table with three women.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS483
As she eats, SOMEONE stares off with a distant look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS485
Duke drags SOMEONE over by the hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS486
He waves at the table.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS488
SOMEONE gives the crowd a bashful smile. Duke claps enthusiastically.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS489
SOMEONE lifts his brow at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS490
She considers him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS492
They kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS493
Later, at her apartment, SOMEONE does her makeup.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS495
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS496
Now at dinner, a waiter serves her and James champagne.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS497
SOMEONE glances away with thoughtful eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS498
Shifting her gaze back to James, she shakes her head.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS499
She closes her eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS501
Stepping out of one, SOMEONE brings a tray to his friends and their significant others.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS502
He beams at the applauding group, then hands out food.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS503
Duke sits with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS506
She nudges the customer aside.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS507
He shakes his head at her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS508
He looks away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS509
She gives a pleading look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS510
Shaking out a bag, SOMEONE ignores her. She trudges away and the customer steps up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS511
Entering the truck SOMEONE gives a determined look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS512
He stares slack-jawed. She gestures at his staff.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS513
His two assistants leave.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS514
He hefty customer stares with wide eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS515
Considering her, he shakes his head, then shrugs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS516
She moves closer.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS517
Their lips rest mere inches apart.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS518
Nodding, he glances away with a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS519
As he meets her gaze again, she leans in closer.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS520
He cups her face and kisses her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS521
Their friends watch through one of the truck's windows.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS523
Now credits appear with scenes of the pickup game with the NBA players.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS524
Directed by SOMEONE Story
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS525
SOMEONE gazes up at SOMEONE Leslie.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS528
Now Leslie checks the ball to SOMEONE who raises an arm in a signal to his team.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS529
SOMEONE sets a pick and SOMEONE dribbles around him. As he shoots, Ron Artest smacks the ball away. Later, Leslie spins past SOMEONE and makes a shot.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS532
Leslie keeps her hand up as he fakes repeatedly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS533
He goes up and she slaps the ball away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS537
Now SOMEONE smacks Leslie's legs as she looks to pass. Artest receives the ball, then elbows SOMEONEt into a padded wall. SOMEONE throws the ball at Artest.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS539
Now Shannon Brown dunks the ball.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS540
As he hangs from the hoop, his legs knock against SOMEONE who stands under the basket.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS541
SOMEONE steps toward him, blustering. SOMEONE leads him away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS542
SOMEONE alley-oops to Butler who hangs from the hoop by one hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS543
High-fiving, the pros find SOMEONE amid their huddle.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS544
Butler tosses the ball down the court as he leaves with the others.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS545
His friends give annoyed looks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS16
Heading toward glass doors onto the helipad, the rugged brother spots SOMEONE's reflection. He turns and shoots into the air.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS17
Using the captured guard as a shield, SOMEONE advances.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS18
As enemy fire, takes his captive out, SOMEONE dives behind the fallen body and shoots.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS20
SOMEONE hands one off as he raise his pass.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS21
He slides on his knees into a guard, knocking him over.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS22
SOMEONE shoots three guards as he runs to the helipad. At the chopper, SOMEONE passes his brother a backpack. Leaping in from the opposite side, SOMEONE swings from the door and kicks SOMEONE back. The briefcase of money opens as it hits the ground. The rugged brother slams Tucks against the chopper. But SOMEONE blocks his strikes and punches him in the face. As SOMEONE throws SOMEONE down, the older brother kicks him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS23
SOMEONE catches himself on the roof's edge as he tumbles off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS26
SOMEONE, his older brother hands him a gun then leaps off the building. A parachute releases from his backpack. Leaping onto the helipad, SOMEONE shoots a bald guard.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS27
SOMEONE aims the gun at SOMEONE. A dark-haired guard attacks SOMEONE who blocks him then knees him. Winding up, he punches the guy out.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS29
He grabs SOMEONE who drops the case with the device over the roof. SOMEONE catches it. SOMEONE snatches SOMEONE's backpack. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's sleeve for balance but it rips and he plummets off the roof.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS30
Drifting to the ground, the older brother watches SOMEONE crash into a car on the street below.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS31
The vehicle careens into another car.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS32
As SOMEONE climbs back onto the helipad, SOMEONE stares down at the destruction.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS33
The surviving Heinrich brother lands safely and slides his parachute off his back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS34
He glances up at the skyscraper then moves to SOMEONE's body which lies sprawled on the car's crushed roof. The rugged Heinrich finds the patch of fabric torn from SOMEONE's suit, still in his brother's clinched hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS35
He takes it then lifts his gaze to the helipad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS36
An aerial view shows him moving away from the crash as bystander’s crowd closer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS37
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from the helipad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS38
Hundred dollar bills flutter all around them.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS39
An all caps title appears, word by word filling the screen. THIS MEANS WAR. The word war is in red. Now a blonde with pixie-like features fires a blowtorch at frying pans. A location types out, Smart Consumer, Inc. Los Angeles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS40
She inspects the pans.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS41
They leave the testing room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS42
Her smile fades as her assistant heads off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS43
Now a location types out, CIA Field Office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS44
Standing on a mezzanine, overlooking an atrium, their boss jerks her thumb.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS45
Later in her office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS46
Later a desks facing each other, SOMEONE watches his gun spin as he reclines with his feet up while SOMEONE sits face down at his desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS47
Drumming a pen at each hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS48
Now in workout clothes, SOMEONE listens to headphones as she walks down a sidewalk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS49
A bicycling couple stops in front of her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS50
She spots SOMEONE's ring.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS51
She watches them kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS52
SOMEONE lovingly eyes SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS53
SOMEONE heads away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS54
Later, she enters a sushi restaurant. The chefs behind the bar cheer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS55
She gives a dispirited look then heads over.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS56
One of the chef hands her a warm towel as she sits.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS57
She drops her face in the towel.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS58
Ken grins at the new arrivals.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS59
Lifting her face from the towel, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS60
SOMEONE glares. Now she shops with her friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS61
She nudges SOMEONE's butt.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS62
Her blonde friend narrows an eye at her. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE attend an elegant lawn party.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS63
He tries some cake.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS64
An older gentleman kisses her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS65
As he leads her off, SOMEONE gazes at his grandparents.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS66
The elderly couple dances on the lawn. A boy with a bucket over his head spins in circles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS67
He falls over. SOMEONE gazes at the dancing couple.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS68
SOMEONE gawks at his friend. Later a woman in a bikini swims the breaststroke in a glass bottom pool, which serves as a foyer ceiling.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS69
Entering his bachelor pad, SOMEONE lifts his gaze to the swimmer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS70
He removes his sunglasses and stares. Sliding off his jacket, he smirks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS71
Now at a Karate Dojo.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS72
Two boys face each other.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS73
A burly father watches his son square off with SOMEONE's smaller one.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS74
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE face.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS76
SOMEONE gives his son two thumbs up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS77
SOMEONE trudges over and sits.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS78
SOMEONE's dad smacks his rear. As SOMEONE faces him, the aggressive father stares into his eyes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS79
Smirking, he slaps SOMEONE's face then leaves. SOMEONE stares after him. SOMEONE shoulders his bag and heads off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS80
As they exit the dojo together, an SUV pulls up and a pretty brunette waves from the driver seat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS81
SOMEONE climbs in back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS82
SOMEONE closes the door behind him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS83
He steps away from the SUV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS84
His ex drives off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS85
Now at his bachelor pad, SOMEONE wears a robe, boxers, and slippers.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS86
Turning on a flat screen TV, he sits on a couch with a bowl of cereal.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS87
Meanwhile, the same program plays on SOMEONE's swanky loft as he spars with a beefy opponent.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS89
Bending his opponent over, SOMEONE eyes the TV ad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS90
SOMEONE watches with the bored look. SOMEONE holds his opponent in a choke hold.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS91
His opponent flips him to a mat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS92
SOMEONE shakes his head as the ad shows an embracing couple.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS93
The burly man picks SOMEONE up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS94
He throws him down again.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS95
With SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS96
Now at Smart Consumer, a receptionist peeks over her computer monitor.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS97
SOMEONE notices her whispering colleagues.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS98
Crossing the office, he glances over her outfit.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS99
Looking back, she heads across the testing area.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS100
SOMEONE steps around her computer and finds in itsfate.net profile with her picture and the headline, Come and Get It Boys.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS101
At a Gymboree Play Center, SOMEONE's friend answers her cellphone.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS102
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE's profile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS104
Now at bustling pub - The Blarney Stone, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE sitting at a table outside.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS105
He takes off his sunglasses and she does the same.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS106
They sit across from each other.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS107
A movie plays on a TV at a video store. SOMEONE takes an escalator down to a lower floor, observing a variety of single women.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS108
He smiles at a dark-haired woman strolling by.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS109
He checks out a short-haired woman then takes out his cellphone and reads a text message.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS111
SOMEONE nods emphatically.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS112
Later at the video store, SOMEONE smiles to herself as she takes the escalator downstairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS113
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE grab the same movie.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS114
He smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS116
She struts pass him and he follows. Later.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS117
She heads off with another movie.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS118
SOMEONE watches her go then shakes his head and leaves as well.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS119
Now at the field office with the tech.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS120
The tech scrolls through customer profiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS121
SOMEONE points.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS122
They view a DMV cross-reference and a tax return.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS124
SOMEONE sits near the back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS125
He approaches her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS127
She rolls her eyes and he walks off with a grin.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS128
Now an aerial view, roves pass downtown Los Angeles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS129
At the CIA Field Office, SOMEONE and SOMEONE work at their opposing desks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS130
Each man turns his laptop to reveal a photo of the same woman.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS131
SOMEONE shuts his laptop. SOMEONE does the same. Then resumes work at his desktop computer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS133
Now a satellite view zooms out from the CIA Field Office locates London, England and zooms in on Saville Row.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS134
In the dimly lit backroom of a tailor shop, a tailor lays out a work in progress over a table then stands upright and finds Heinrich facing him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS136
Cut to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS137
At SOMEONE's pad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS142
SOMEONE carries a huge stuffed pig, SOMEONE notices her taking hold of his hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS143
In a darkened corridor.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS144
SOMEONE covers SOMEONE's eyes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS145
He reveals a trapeze structure adorned with lights in the middle of a circus ring.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS146
He takes her hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS147
As SOMEONE swings, SOMEONE stands on a platform.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS148
He swings under a domed ceiling.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS149
SOMEONE grabs hold of her trapeze.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS150
She jumps from the platform and swings out over the net.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS151
Hanging on by their legs, they grab each other's wrists. SOMEONE lets go and swings with SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS152
He lets her fall and she lands on the net, bouncing high into the air.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS153
He lets himself fall and bounce as well. Then they roll into the middle and lie side by side.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS154
As SOMEONE lies on his back, SOMEONE kisses him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS155
He wraps his arms around her and draws her near.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS156
We glimpse the couple from across the ring as they embrace, surrounded by the several strands of lights adorning the trapeze structure.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS158
At home by a fireplace, SOMEONE kisses a half-naked man lying on his back near an open bottle of red wine. She smacks him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS160
Now at work, SOMEONE sits alone at his desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS161
As his colleagues move on, SOMEONE shifts his gaze. Now with the tech.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS163
He steps aside with his hands in his pockets.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS164
A satellite view zooms in on a street, tracking an Audi convertible which loops around and parks outside a busy nightclub.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS165
SOMEONE hops out of the sports car and joins SOMEONE who stands in a long line to get in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS166
He leads her to the entrance.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS168
SOMEONE shakes hands with the bouncer on the way in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS169
He chats with the coat check girl.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS170
To a bartender.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS175
They enter a VIP section.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS177
A bartender hands him a bottle of wine.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS178
SOMEONE turns to find SOMEONE missing from her chair. He peers across the dance floor then heads after her. Outside, as SOMEONE crosses the street, SOMEONE catches up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS179
She spots SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS180
She grabs SOMEONE as he walks away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS181
She pulls him into a passionate kiss as the happy couple arrives.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS182
SOMEONE glares at her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS183
She glances at SOMEONE. He finally turns to SOMEONE and offers his hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS185
She smacks him playfully.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS186
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch them kiss again.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS187
Later at Pizzeria.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS188
He smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS189
He taps his temple and she brightens.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS190
An aerial view shows the city at dawn. At the field office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS191
SOMEONE strolls cheerfully through a bullpen.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS192
Turning, he finds a bald agent grinning at him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS193
SOMEONE's smile fades to a comprehending scowl.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS194
He marches into the work area he shares with SOMEONE and finds him sitting casually at his desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS196
He drops the file in front of SOMEONE. It contains a photo of the blunt-featured SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS197
SOMEONE sits at his own desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS198
SOMEONE gestures bashfully.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS199
SOMEONE looks up from a file.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS200
Now they hold separate briefings.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS201
Now in a stylish home, SOMEONE dances in a kitchen as she makes microwave popcorn.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS202
A window behind her shows SOMEONE lowering to the ground on a cable.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS204
Wearing shorts, a big comfy shirt, and a ponytail, she struts into the living room and turns on a flat screen TV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS205
Behind her, SOMEONE creeps in and ducks behind a couch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS206
SOMEONE returns to the kitchen obliviously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS207
Getting to his feet, SOMEONE peers at her bookshelf and notices models of vintage sports cars.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS208
In the kitchen, she swivels her hips as she wipes out her popcorn bowl. As she leaves the kitchen, he darts out.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS209
She passes stairs, steps through a doorway, and shuts it behind her. SOMEONE darts down the stairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS210
He glides over to a lamp and sticks a tiny device under the shade's cross-beamed frame.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS211
Noticing a framed poster for a Gustav Klimt Exhibit, he studies it closely.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS212
SOMEONE ducks around a doorway and hides as SOMEONE comes out and eyes an open laptop.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS213
SOMEONE notices a website for a pet shelter on her browser.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS214
SOMEONE waves her hands in the air as she dances to her microwave.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS215
SOMEONE ducks behind the kitchen island then darts around a corner as she takes out her popcorn.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS216
Behind her, SOMEONE dashes off outside.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS218
Now at his desk, SOMEONE throws a crumpled paper ball at a waste basket and misses.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS219
A paper ball flying from another direction goes in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS220
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE who blows on his fingers like a gun barrel and flashes a cocky smile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS221
SOMEONE tries again and his paper ball goes in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS222
Their feet on their desks, they take turns throwing.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS223
Now a marquee reads, The Penthouse - Beautiful Girls Nightly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS224
As a bouncer moves aside, SOMEONE faces his partner.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS225
He sniffs SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS226
Leaning on SOMEONE, SOMEONE staggers drunkenly into a backroom where men play cards.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS227
SOMEONE glares at him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS228
SOMEONE stands revealing his powerful build.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS229
SOMEONE's poker buddies draw guns and fires as he flees.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS230
Dropping to the floor, the agent shoot their assailants.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS232
As he runs through a doorway, a bald man tosses SOMEONE a shotgun then attacks SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS233
The agent fights back, wrapping a payphone cord around his neck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS234
SOMEONE drops to the floor as SOMEONE shoots. The blast misses him and SOMEONE flees. SOMEONE and SOMEONE give chase, dropping the bald man.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS235
Reaching the main floor, SOMEONE trips then draws an ankle pistol and aims.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS237
SOMEONE forces a patron down and SOMEONE shot misses again. SOMEONE dashes over the bar then somersaults across the table. As SOMEONE reaches the dancer stage, SOMEONE knocks him down and falls away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS238
Arriving, SOMEONE disarms SOMEONE and slams him against the pole. SOMEONE charges but SOMEONE kicks him away. SOMEONE forces SOMEONE down and SOMEONE punches him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS239
While his partner straps SOMEONE's neck and cuffs him to the pole, SOMEONE holds him at gun point.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS241
Later, they haul SOMEONE into the field office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS242
I'm not saying anything.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS243
SOMEONE eyes his cell. It reads, Boyles - urgent check in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS244
SOMEONE gets a text from SOMEONE reading, mission alert.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS247
Now at SOMEONE's house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS248
She shows the photo of SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS249
As SOMEONE spies on the women from a surveillance truck, SOMEONE burst in on him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS250
Both men listen worriedly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS251
SOMEONE faces his cackling friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS252
His smile vanishes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS253
The men meet separately with their team leaders.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS255
SOMEONE rides in the Camaro with her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS256
A spy drone flies into view behind them. Tilting his side mirror, SOMEONE spots it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS257
From a surveillance room, SOMEONE watches footage from its camera. SOMEONE sticks up his middle finger.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS258
Behind his back, he discreetly draws a gun then makes a show of resting his hand behind SOMEONE's seat back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS259
He shoots the drone, destroying it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS260
SOMEONE raises both hands, SOMEONE grabs the wheel. The briefings continue.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS261
Now SOMEONE takes SOMEONE to an enormous art vault.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS262
In an alcove, several paintings by Klimt stand propped against crates.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS263
At a remote location, SOMEONE speaks into a headset.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS265
SOMEONE frowns.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS266
With SOMEONE, SOMEONE giggles mischievously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS268
Elsewhere, SOMEONE laughs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS269
He takes her to a draped painting.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS270
He unveils it, revealing Klimt's romantic masterpiece, The Kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS271
It depicts a man kissing a woman's face.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS272
She takes SOMEONE's arm as she gazes wistfully at the stylized yet tender image.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS273
The agent's expression softens affectionately and he faces the painting.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS274
They share a smile. Later, a phone call.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS275
In surveillance.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS276
SOMEONE brings up a video feed from SOMEONE's house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS277
SOMEONE's smile fades.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS278
Now he takes SOMEONE to a dog shelter.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS279
He high fives a boy.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS280
She faces a tiny mutt's cage.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS281
SOMEONE starts to open it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS282
As SOMEONE moves on to the terrier's cage, the tiny mutt springs out and attacks SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS283
The terrier jumps up and down in front of SOMEONE. With great effort, SOMEONE wrestles the mutt into submission.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS284
Turning, SOMEONE smiles fondly at them.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS285
He puts the dog back in its cage.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS286
SOMEONE brushes more hair off his shirt.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS288
Later, SOMEONE spies on SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS289
SOMEONE frowns. Now at a paintball park.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS290
SOMEONE sweeps curtains of netting apart revealing men and boys on a paintball field.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS292
He swings out from a rail, kicking a man down.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS293
He disarms another.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS294
Crouching on a deck, he shoots the players hiding beneath then beacons SOMEONE with the wave.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS295
She fumbles with goggles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS296
Now they peek out from behind a partition.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS297
SOMEONE whips around and shoots players surrounding him. He hits two in their helmets.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS298
In a bunker.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS299
SOMEONE drops onto the roof and throws in a canister.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS300
He swings away, leaving the kids staring from the bunker windows. Blue paint sprays out from inside. SOMEONE leaps from post to post up to a tower with a flag.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS301
He yanks a man from the tower, grabs the flag and proudly shows it to SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS302
He nimbly climbs down to her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS303
Her gun shoots him in the crouch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS304
He straightens his face flushed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS305
At the gymboree.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS306
SOMEONE shakes his hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS307
SOMEONE checks his watch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS308
Later, with Agent SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS309
Now candles filled SOMEONE's loft.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS310
As they kiss, a monitor in the CIA surveillance room shows their glowing heat signature. SOMEONE scowls.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS311
A tech wearing glasses stands behind him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS312
SOMEONE presses a remote.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS313
In the loft, the overhead fires sprinklers go off, extinguishing the candles and drenching SOMEONE and SOMEONE. SOMEONE smirks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS314
On another day, SOMEONE walks with Agent SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS315
At SOMEONE's pad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS316
An old dog wheezes on his couch as they stop and kiss. SOMEONE pulls away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS317
She exists. SOMEONE watches her go then excitedly grabs a wine bottle and two glasses and hurries over to the coffee table.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS318
He sets them down then presses the remote.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS319
He quickly lights a candle then almost sits down on his new pet.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS320
He shoos the dog off the couch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS322
He pulls a dart from his neck. Looking out the window, he sees SOMEONE on the next roof.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS323
Holding a tranquilizer rifle, his partner communicates with him using military hand signals then disappears. SOMEONE's knees slowly buckle and he collapses to the couch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS324
As he falls unconscious, SOMEONE returns.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS325
The next day, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand in an elevator.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS326
As they both try to exit at the same time, they get log-jammed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS327
They enter an interrogation room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS328
He brandish his pliers.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS329
Sitting handcuffed in a chair, SOMEONE chuckles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS330
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS331
who turns to their prisoner.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS333
Sooner or later he'll be coming for you.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS335
He glowers at SOMEONE's poker face.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS336
He turns his harsh eyes on SOMEONE who gives a cool smirk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS337
Now a satellite view zooms out from the CIA Field Office rapidly relocates the Los Angeles harbor and zooms in. At a dock, a henchman clasps hands with Heinrich and helps him disembark off a fishing boat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS338
I'm sorry about SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS339
They get in one of two black Chevy Suburban’s waiting at a curb.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS340
As the cars pull out, the picture fades to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS341
Now SOMEONE brings SOMEONE to his grandparents' estate.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS342
His little nephew spins around with a bucket on his head then collapses.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS344
She pulls SOMEONE away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS345
Left behind with a pie in his hand, SOMEONE lets out a sigh.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS346
Nana walks SOMEONE out to a stable where photographs clutter a wall.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS347
At a family dinner.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS348
SOMEONE raises her glass of white wine.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS349
Everyone toasts.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS350
That night, SOMEONE walks SOMEONE to her house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS351
They both glance away shyly then look each other in the eyes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS352
SOMEONE chuckles nervously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS353
The two surveillance teams watch from the CIA.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS354
SOMEONE and SOMEONE burst into her house. Kissing hungrily as they remove their coats. They start tearing off each other's clothes. She straddles his thighs as he lifts her onto the kitchen island. He whips off his blue button down shirt. Agent SOMEONE watches the video feed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS355
SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE's dress off over her head. She reclines with a sultry smile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS356
Back at the CIA Field Office, SOMEONE's three colleagues crane their necks to watch. As SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie kissing on the kitchen island, the picture fades to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS357
The next morning, he lies asleep in her bed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS358
Dressed for work, SOMEONE tiptoes out from her bathroom and gathers her things.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS359
He winces. SOMEONE makes a call as she heads out.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS360
At the CIA.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS361
Agent SOMEONE reluctantly takes it out of his breast pocket.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS363
Avoiding eye contact, SOMEONE nods tensely.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS364
He chucks the disk in the trash and storms off. Now SOMEONE watches Titanic.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS365
Standing at the prow of the ship, SOMEONE Winslet looks out over the water. SOMEONE smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS366
He goes to an elevator door and answers it to reveal a sexy woman in a flight attendant's uniform.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS367
SOMEONE gives a shock gape then nods and smiles politely.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS368
The elevator doors slide shut.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS369
SOMEONE closes his eyes and lifts his brow then returns to the living room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS370
Pausing in tracks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS371
He looks back over his shoulder toward the elevator.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS373
The satellite view zooms out from the CIA Field Office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS374
It shifts to James Monroe Elementary. SOMEONE comes out from the school.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS375
SOMEONE stands by smiling as SOMEONE gives his son a hug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS376
SOMEONE monitors the conversation.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS377
At the Smart Consumer offices, SOMEONE sits before a toy fire truck. SOMEONE gives him a hammer and lets him smash it to pieces.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS378
Later, the three spray water at some test windows.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS380
They spray him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS381
A water fight ensues between all three of them.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS382
Back in the surveillance room, SOMEONE paces as he monitors the scene.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS384
She waves from his truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS385
SOMEONE's ex comes out of her and watches him give SOMEONE a hug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS386
SOMEONE smiles as he returns to his truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS387
Back in the surveillance room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS388
On screen, a satellite zooms in on SOMEONE's vehicle as it pulls over to the side of the road.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS389
SOMEONE sits and watches SOMEONE and SOMEONE's heat signatures in the front seat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS391
As SOMEONE pulls away, their noses graze and their lips linger an inch apart.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS392
They meet in a tender kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS393
SOMEONE shuts his eyes and bows his head.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS394
Now the couple barges into SOMEONE's house locked in a passionate embrace.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS395
As SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE up onto a console table, he discreetly removes the bug from the lamp and throws it on the floor.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS396
As SOMEONE crashes it under his shoe, the surveillance team loses one of their angles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS397
SOMEONE leans SOMEONE over a dining table and reaches into a center piece.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS401
SOMEONE throws down a pair of headphones.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS402
Now SOMEONE lays SOMEONE down on the couch. He kisses her neck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS403
SOMEONE listens in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS404
SOMEONE tenderly strokes his cheek. In the surveillance room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS405
SOMEONE's head sinks and he covers his eyes. Daytime, at SOMEONE's house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS407
She lifts her son onto her lap.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS408
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand at their desks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS409
As SOMEONE takes a clip from his gun, SOMEONE packs up his belongings in a file box.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS411
SOMEONE takes his cellphone from his pocket.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS412
Keeping his stare on SOMEONE, SOMEONE ends the call.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS413
SOMEONE shuts his laptop. Pockets his phone and grabs his jacket.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS414
As SOMEONE strides out of the room, SOMEONE stands motionless at his box of belongings.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS415
Later, SOMEONE enters the surveillance area with the box under his arm.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS416
He sets it down next to SOMEONE watching surveillance footage.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS418
SOMEONE glances back at the footage and stops.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS419
The camera zooms in from a wide view to a close up of the truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS420
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS421
They see a car parked behind the truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS422
The tech complies. A zoomed in image clarifies, revealing the shadowy face of the driver.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS423
SOMEONE rushes out of the room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS424
SOMEONE approaches.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS425
She heads up some stairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS426
SOMEONE waves. Now SOMEONE is bare feet, move up and down.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS427
She rests from using her fitness ball.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS429
As SOMEONE nods and complies, SOMEONE gives him a slap on the cheek.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS430
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE then delivers a fast right hook.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS431
In a posh ladies room, SOMEONE controls her breath.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS432
In the chic restaurant, customers clear out as the two men brawl. SOMEONE sends SOMEONE rolling over a table then throws a knife into a leather chair by SOMEONE's head.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS433
She sees food on her gum line.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS435
SOMEONE stuns SOMEONE with a throat punch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS436
SOMEONE wheels a coat rack like a quarterstaff.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS437
SOMEONE uses the pole to ram SOMEONE backward through a glass partition.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS439
She mops her cleavage. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE scrap right over a balcony. They plummet 20 feet onto a table below.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS440
In the ladies room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS441
Now bloody face then lying on glass shards, SOMEONE feebly throws a fork at SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS442
SOMEONE comes down the stairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS443
With disappointment in her eyes, SOMEONE turns away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS444
As she clears out, the two battered man wilt.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS445
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in her convertible bug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS446
SOMEONE hands her a sippy cup.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS447
An SUV bumps them from behind. A second bumps them from the front. Trapping the car. Two men approach, one is Heinrich.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS448
Heinrich signals an accomplice. In the trashed restaurant, the guys stand up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS449
Now they exit to the sidewalk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS450
It's SOMEONE's cell calling.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS451
Three SUVs escort SOMEONE's VW.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS452
SOMEONE manipulates his handheld.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS454
SOMEONE flings the valet from the car.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS456
SOMEONE takes the mic.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS457
On the freeway, SOMEONE's convertible is escorted on three sides. The passenger side is unguarded.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS458
As the Jeep comes up fast on the VW's unguarded side, SOMEONE grips the roll bar and leans out. He leaps aboard the convertible and punches a thug in back, sending him tumbling. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS461
SOMEONE shoots the tire on SOMEONE's car which veers off the road and catches air over a decorative man-made lake.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS462
The huge splash blocks everything from view except a free flying license plate.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS463
The water calms. SOMEONE sits safely in the buoyant bobbing bug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS464
On the road, a gunman in one SUV fires on the jeep which evades to the right. Heinrich fires from another SUV. A return shot from SOMEONE tags Heinrich's shoulder. His car halts and he scolds, Drive you idiot. His driver slumps dead. Heinrich shoves the body out and drives on.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS466
In a parking garage, two SUVs race their way. SOMEONE reverses as they advance head on. He beckons SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS468
The Jeep does a tight skidding 180, SOMEONE nearly falls out but SOMEONE pulls him back in. As one SUV gunman aims at them, SOMEONE pulls his trigger and pegs the guy.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS469
With a lug wrench, SOMEONE smashes the window of an enemy driver beside them. Hooks the stirring wheel and yanks. The SUV hits a column and explodes. Meanwhile, SOMEONE's son watches TV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS472
Chased by another SUV, SOMEONE throws a gas jug from the Jeep. As it bounces under the pursuer's bumper, the agents shoot it and it explodes. The SUV gets thrown upside down. Seeing the road's end, SOMEONE breaks. The Jeep spins to a sidelong halt within inches of the sheer drop.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS473
SOMEONE sways outward precariously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS474
Two traffic cones plunge to the highway below.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS475
SOMEONE looks from SOMEONE to SOMEONE. His gaze intense and thoughtful.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS476
He addresses SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS477
Heinrich's SUV speeds toward them. Standing on the road, SOMEONE and SOMEONE both fire at it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS478
SOMEONE stands back by the Jeep, visible between the two agents.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS481
The agents kneel. As the SUV rounds closer, they fire.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS482
A deploying airbag wallops Heinrich's face and he careens into a mobile construction light.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS483
The blast sends the SUV rolling sideways toward the road's unfinished end.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS484
In slow motion, SOMEONE and SOMEONE each race to one side. They both beacon SOMEONE, urging her to clear out of the way. But the tumbling SUV bares down swiftly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS485
Scene from the ground, the SUV and Jeep barrel over the edge and explode on impact.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS486
A bird's-eye-view shows the black smoke hiding the end of the unfinished roadway.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS487
The smoke thins and SOMEONE becomes visible, semi-reclined on the road.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS488
Opposite him, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS489
SOMEONE's squints at them, stunned and knowing.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS490
SOMEONE tenderly caresses her hair and SOMEONE peers longingly at him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS491
As SOMEONE looks on, they both turn their attention to him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS492
He resiliently straightens his posture and gives a few curt nods of his head.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS493
All three notice the news chopper. Meanwhile, SOMEONE's son and ex-wife gawk at the TV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS494
Later, a paramedic faces SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS495
Wrapped in a blanket, SOMEONE goes to SOMEONE who sits at the rear of an ambulance. He stands and they kiss each other's cheeks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS496
He looks to his friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS498
SOMEONE gives him a warm smile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS499
SOMEONE lowers his gaze and nods shyly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS500
Heading off, he pauses and turns back to face his approaching friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS501
SOMEONE adjusts his wrist watch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS502
SOMEONE regards his friend with a concerned frown.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS503
They hug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS504
They part and SOMEONE heads off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS505
Rejoining SOMEONE, SOMEONE wraps his arms around her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS506
His lips meet hers in a smoldering kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS507
They rock back and forth lingering in the embrace.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS508
Looking up at SOMEONE, SOMEONE shakes her head knowingly and smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS509
As they enjoy another kiss, we drift up and away from the unfinished overpass and gaze out over the city.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS510
Now in the SOMEONE Arts Dojo, SOMEONE and SOMEONE face off again as both of their fathers look on.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS511
As SOMEONE charges, SOMEONE swings his leg over the bigger boy's arm and flips him to the mat. He runs proudly to SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS513
Leaning on SOMEONE, the man obeys with effort.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS514
SOMEONE pats his back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS515
As SOMEONE steps away, SOMEONE shyly approaches his ex who waits for him in a doorway.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS516
She smiles and glances away. Her wide eyes glistening.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS517
He presents himself to her humbly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS518
Leaning against the door frame, she steps forward and extends a hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS519
SOMEONE's brow lifts in a delighted smile, he shakes her hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS520
With a tearful smile, she gestures SOMEONE to follow her as she goes over to her son.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS521
In slow motion, the reunited family walks down a hallway together.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS522
SOMEONE lays a hand on SOMEONE's back, gently ushering her through a doorway.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS523
He follows with a hopeful gaze. Fade to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS524
Now a military grade helicopter flies out at a night time mission.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS525
Inside, SOMEONE answers his cell.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS526
In a sporty convertible.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS527
In the helicopter.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS528
They jump up and down, a hatch lowers.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS529
SOMEONE checks SOMEONE's chute.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS530
SOMEONE stares at him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS16
Now, a title appears.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS17
Boston. Zacum Bridge at sunrise.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS18
In a residential neighborhood. Words appear, 5 Years Later. SOMEONE steps on to the porch of a modest three-story.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS19
Now, at a junk yard. SOMEONE buys a waist-high tire.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS21
Is guarding a grand entryway. Arched ironwork above reads "Park Zoo".
ZOOKEEPER_DVS22
Now, SOMEONE drives a golf cart with the tire in back.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS23
Habitat enclosure. SOMEONE lowers a drawbridge over a moat and walks over to it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS24
He takes the monkey's hand.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS25
Who wears a patch over one eye.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS28
Worker dumps his bucket of lettuce over a waist-high wall and into the pit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS29
He unlocks a door which opens at the pit's floor level.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS30
He rolls the tire into a barren habitat. A single shaft of sunlight shines down from the pit's high opening into the otherwise stark enclosure where a gorilla sits with its back to the door. SOMEONE hangs the tire from a rope on a tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS32
He Stands then stumbles back over.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS35
Later, in a lab, a willowy, SOMEONE. Long haired woman places an eagle in a cage. She sees SOMEONE standing at a dry erase board labeled Things to do.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS36
He writes, Fix SOMEONE's tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS40
A heart monitor shows a flat line.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS42
He opens a drawer and rifles through it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS44
He gets his hand down the lioness’s throat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS45
SOMEONE pulls out a crushed Red Bull can.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS46
That night, a banner hanging over a party over the zoo reads, Congratulations.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS49
His hand and pulls her into a tight embrace. Her eyes widen.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS50
He gives a serious look. SOMEONE smiles politely.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS54
In the icy stand behind him. Scanning the crowd, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE. In his perspective, she appears to pull away from the others around her.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS55
SOMEONE's lips twitch.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS57
Venom cringes while Frankie hits play on a boom box.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS58
SOMEONE strides over to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS59
He catches SOMEONE eyeing SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS60
Meanwhile, by the giraffe's enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS61
He perks up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS62
SOMEONE, the Monkey watches them chat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS63
Holding the porcupine, SOMEONE turns away. He yanks the quill out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS68
SOMEONE flinches. Smiling, she dabs his cheek. He stares at her with lovelorn eyes. She returns a tender look. SOMEONE, the Monkey watches.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS69
She gives a flirty smile.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS71
She leaves. As SOMEONE stares after her, Floyd shoots a quill into his forehead. SOMEONE chuckles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS72
SOMEONE winces and grits his teeth. He pulls out the quill.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS76
A net swings from a horizontal arm at its top. The monkey leaps onto it, climbs down the pole and lands in SOMEONE's enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS77
SOMEONE creeps past a man-made waterfall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS78
The panel on it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS79
Swinging it open, he finds a power box inside and
ZOOKEEPER_DVS80
He flips a switch. A dog is licking himself.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS81
on just his hind legs, SOMEONE scurries down a path to a set of heavy iron double doors. He climbs up to the keyhole, glances around, then picks the lock.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS82
Tilts and the doors swing open.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS83
She stretches her neck into another enclosure where the rest of the animals gather at the base of a rock ledge. A lion steps out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS84
He eyes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS85
The next day, SOMEONE peers into SOMEONE's pit to find SOMEONE hanging a giant whiffle ball from the tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS86
He spins it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS87
With a smile, SOMEONE heads away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS88
SOMEONE keeps his back to him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS89
Later, with the giraffe.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS92
SOMEONE gnaws on a carrot as he watches SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk away. The giraffe licks it and he spits it out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS93
She walks away from him and looks at the monkey.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS94
SOMEONE gives a thumbs up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS97
A wire basket drops from his hand.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS98
Flailing his arms. The giraffe looks on.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS99
He drops into the rock ledge and lands on his back.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS100
SOMEONE and SOMEONE board the golf cart. SOMEONE peeks over the rock ledge and watches SOMEONE struggle to his feet.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS101
Lion steps away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS104
His house and shuts the door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS105
Through his window blinds. On TV
ZOOKEEPER_DVS106
Teenage witch listens to her talking cat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS107
The next morning at the zoo, SOMEONE peeks into the lion enclosure and finds SOMEONE lying on his haunches. The zookeeper awkwardly steps out and faces the indifferent lion. Keeping his eyes on the animal, he walks backward out of view again. Now, three kids stand at the lion enclosure. SOMEONE sets down a wheelbarrow, glances around then cautiously approaches. He watches SOMEONE lounge on some rocks. The kids head off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS108
SOMEONE stares at the indifferent lion.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS109
A couple passes by.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS110
The lion while SOMEONE sweeps the sidewalk behind them. He mouths to SOMEONE, What's up?
ZOOKEEPER_DVS111
Later, a security guard rides a cart.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS113
Exiting through a gate, he finds SOMEONE the Lion waiting for him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS114
Feet and falls on his back. The lion sighs.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS115
SOMEONE lies unconscious under a few swaying elephant toys.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS118
SOMEONE licks his own armpit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS120
In his pit, SOMEONE the Gorilla glances up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS121
He turns away sadly. On another day, patrons walk around the zoo. SOMEONE enters the gorilla enclosure with a bucket and shuts the door behind him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS122
SOMEONE sits with his back to him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS123
The somber gorilla sniffs the air.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS125
SOMEONE gives no response.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS126
SOMEONE ambles off with a bucket still in hand. The gorilla shifts his gaze.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS127
SOMEONE brightens and glances over his shoulder. The gorilla rocks back and forth as the zookeeper sets the bucket down and exits.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS128
Now, a boy chucks popcorn at the bears from behind a fence.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS130
The boy lands in the enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS131
He notices the two brown bears eyeing him hungrily.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS132
He jumps out of his golf cart. He runs halfway up a staircase.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS133
Standing on their hind legs, the bears swap a look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS134
He walks the boy through a door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS135
SOMEONE shuts the door, makes sure no one's watching, then approaches the bears.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS136
He walks for them.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS137
SOMEONE lifts his hands.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS138
SOMEONE walks crotch first.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS139
SOMEONE notices the students watching him. SOMEONE stands among them.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS140
He briskly retreats. As the kids disperse, SOMEONE's concerned gaze lingers on her colleague.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS141
In SOMEONE's pit, SOMEONE slides over a bowl of popcorn for the approaching gorilla.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS142
Shane enters through the metal door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS143
He squints at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS144
Shane glances around then points at the gorilla.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS145
He exits and slides the metal door shut.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS149
SOMEONE turns to leave.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS150
With the wolf.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS153
He pees on a pole.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS154
He faces the pole.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS155
SOMEONE shrugs.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS156
Crosses to a tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS157
The wolf crosses to a nearby fence, averting his gaze.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS158
People walk by behind the fence.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS159
The women quickly look away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS160
SOMEONE zips up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS161
The wolf lifts his paw.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS162
He limps around SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS164
SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn their backs. SOMEONE looks at the wolf.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS165
He mouths the word sorry.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS167
Shampoos the wolf's coat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS168
Now, a jazz trio performs at a fancy restaurant. SOMEONE finishes urinating on a potted plant adorned with mini lights.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS169
SOMEONE taps him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS170
Joins SOMEONE at the bar.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS172
As a guy approaches from behind.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS173
SOMEONE heads off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS174
SOMEONE turns back to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS176
He furrows his brow as he considers.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS177
SOMEONE sulks off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS178
Later, at the zoo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS180
Sweeps past SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS181
SOMEONE looks from the giraffe to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS182
He stands.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS184
He gives a desperate look. Now, SOMEONE pumps his legs as he pedals a recumbent tricycle up a hill. An orange flag waves.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS185
Semi’s trailer.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS186
Face plants on the cement.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS190
As she rides off, SOMEONE screeches to a halt.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS191
He pretends to shoot an arrow.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS192
SOMEONE gives him a baffled frown. SOMEONE mounts his bike then rides away throwing SOMEONE a final glance. Nighttime in the lion enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS194
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS195
SOMEONE turns away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS196
SOMEONE nods at the lioness and heads off. Now, as SOMEONE eats her lunch, SOMEONE stands at her desk.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS201
Gorilla stops playing with his swinging ball and turns to find
ZOOKEEPER_DVS202
SOMEONE peering inside.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS203
He enters holding a two-tiered orange cake with lit candles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS204
Watches with a disbelief.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS205
He starts to turn away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS206
Nighttime. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE up a staircase which emerges by the mouth of the pit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS207
They bump fists.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS208
SOMEONE heads to a van in a maintenance lot. SOMEONE follows, now wearing a yellow polo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS211
Lights of downtown skyscrapers. SOMEONE points out the illuminated clock on the Custom House Tower.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS212
His head out his window and watches the city whizz past.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS213
SOMEONE bobs his head while SOMEONE holds his hand out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS214
With the music, SOMEONE pushes his door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS216
Grinning, the zookeeper climbs out. He hurries beside SOMEONE who gallops excitedly towards.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS217
Inside, a waitress approaches their booth.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS218
Eyes widen at SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS219
He eyes his polo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS220
The waitress stares at SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS221
SOMEONE closes his menu.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS222
Frowning, the waitress leaves.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS223
Returns from his game of pool and finds SOMEONE slow dancing with a blonde secretary in his arms.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS224
She smiles dreamily and SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a thumbs up. The zookeeper smiles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS225
The two friends lie side by side on the roof of the van and gaze up at the glowing full moon.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS227
His grin morphs into a frown and he furrows his brow.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS229
Morning. At the zoo, a frog leaps off a ledge.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS231
Puffs out his throat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS232
He bows his head.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS234
At the reptile enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS236
SOMEONE sees an eyeball drawn on Frankie's eye patch.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS237
Venom steps a little closer to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS238
SOMEONE glances down.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS239
The frowning zookeeper hesitates.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS240
He reaches into Venom's left pants pocket and digs around. SOMEONE shoots his colleague an uncomfortable smile.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS241
The zookeeper reaches into his right pocket. He pulls out the keys.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS246
Nodding along to the beat, he looks to an apartment building.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS247
A woman's shapely legs head down the front steps.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS248
He shifts his eyes pensively.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS249
Wedding reception. Acrobats twirl from long swathes of.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS250
Pictures of the bride and groom.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS251
SOMEONE some champagne.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS252
He spots SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS256
SOMEONE holds out her open palm.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS257
SOMEONE puts his hand in hers. She places.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS259
Watches them move to the bar.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS260
As SOMEONE's eyes meet his, he quickly looks away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS261
SOMEONE holds a microphone.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS262
To the DJ. SOMEONE briefly hides her face then dramatically gets up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS263
SOMEONE mouths along to the lyrics as the couple starts dancing.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS264
SOMEONE and SOMEONE square off from across the dancefloor.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS265
SOMEONE tries with SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS267
Return to their table.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS268
SOMEONE looks around the ballroom. SOMEONE slouches defeatedly.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS269
She moves off and waves her arms at the DJ on a balcony, then returns to her date.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS270
She takes SOMEONE's arm and leads him to the dancefloor.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS272
SOMEONE grabs two of the hanging silk drapes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS273
And over one of his shoulders.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS274
Playful smile, she grabs her own pair of drapes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS276
Then twirls in front of him trying.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS277
Get SOMEONE's gorgeous.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS278
He starts to sway a little.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS279
Off her feet and swings.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS280
He were on a swing.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS281
The other woman at SOMEONE's table turns to watch as well.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS282
Spins around, but she swings over SOMEONE again.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS283
As they move apart, we see SOMEONE watching.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS284
SOMEONE turns to the woman at her table.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS286
He frowns to himself as the groom walks off. SOMEONE comes over and pulls up a chair.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS287
SOMEONE blinks for a moment then sets his chunk of ice on the table.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS288
He gets up from his seat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS289
SOMEONE stares at him aggressively. SOMEONE purses his lips and puffs out his cheeks.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS290
And his pants split.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS291
SOMEONE walks off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS292
SOMEONE hangs up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS293
Her eyes widen as she swallows some food.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS294
Moving his arms like a robot, he clanks a fork and knife together.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS295
Stabs the steak off SOMEONE's plate.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS296
He points across the ballroom then squints.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS297
Meanwhile, a bartender hands SOMEONE two drinks.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS298
Spots him and heads over. The two rivals.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS299
SOMEONE leans on the bar with a cocky smirk.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS300
He unflinchingly stares down his rival.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS301
SOMEONE leaves him alone. SOMEONE brings cake.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS302
He flails his arms.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS303
As he leaves, SOMEONE puts down the two slices of cake and self-consciously hides her thumb.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS304
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS305
A valet brings them the Mustang and they get in.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS306
His pretty colleague beams.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS307
Finding SOMEONE outside, he rolls down his window.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS308
As he rolls his window back up, SOMEONE frowns slightly. Staring straight ahead, SOMEONE remains motionless in his seat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS309
SOMEONE exits the car.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS310
She holds the door for Griffins ex who climbs in with him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS311
SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE who nods.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS312
SOMEONE pouts.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS313
She perks up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS314
At the fashion show, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE towards a man.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS315
hair, who holds a Chinese crested.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS316
SOMEONE leans towards her.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS317
SOMEONE's brow creases.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS318
Eyeing SOMEONE, he rests his lips on his fists as if thinking.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS319
SOMEONE watches anxiously.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS320
They ride in the back of a limo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS321
SOMEONE frowns.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS323
As SOMEONE stares with crestfallen eyes, SOMEONE leans.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS324
He gives a dazed look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS325
Blinking, he turns away from her. The corner of his mouth lifts into an.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS327
Tosses Glen the keys.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS328
Holsters his invisible guns. As a middle-aged man exams a sports car.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS329
Keeper stares with predatory eyes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS330
And exchange a glance.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS331
SOMEONE faces the customer.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS332
SOMEONE hits his head on the car's raised scissor door as he tries to climb inside. He hits his rear on the horn as he attempts to back into the seat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS333
Then finally slides his body.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS334
Now, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE standing outside the new eagle enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS335
She looks in a cage.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS336
An eagle flies out and perches beside another eagle.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS338
Frowning, SOMEONE shifts her gaze to the eagles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS339
She scowls at him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS340
She meets his gaze.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS341
Bowing his head, SOMEONE shakes it. As SOMEONE watches expectantly, he lifts his eyes to hers and nods.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS342
Her shoulders sag and she gives a disappointed look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS343
With a resigned smile, she leans against the railing around the eagle enclosure's glass observation wall and stares out at the birds. SOMEONE blinks at her, his lips parted in a discouraged expression, then glances at the eagles. As he walks off, SOMEONE watches with heartbroken eyes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS344
Later, SOMEONE slides open the door to SOMEONE's enclosure and peers inside. He enters with a box of popcorn in one hand.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS345
With his back to the former zookeeper, SOMEONE sits facing the enclosure's far wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS346
SOMEONE checks his phone's caller ID.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS347
SOMEONE drops his pained gaze then returns it to SOMEONE who looks away. Shrugging his hands, the former zookeeper opens his mouth to speak then licks his lips and takes a step toward the door. He shoots the gorilla a final glance then leaves. Stepping into the corridor, he slides the door closed and starts.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS349
He strides over to him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS350
Shane shifts his weight.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS351
Under SOMEONE's firm gaze, Shane swallows hard then nods. He returns a can of pepper spray to its holder on a.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS353
Pushing the Ferrari's passenger seat forward, he indicates the trunk. His gray-haired customer gives an uncertain look. SOMEONE's smirk fades as a bus pauses on the street outside. It bears an.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS354
which reads, The eagles have landed.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS355
Now, at the zoo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS357
Now, Venom holds two lizards as he approaches SOMEONE who stares into SOMEONE's pit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS358
SOMEONE overhears and frowns.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS359
Venom gazes at her.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS360
Closing his eyes, he puckers his lips and leans toward her. As he draws closer, he opens his mouth.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS361
Later, SOMEONE enters a luxury condo and finds SOMEONE doing yoga.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS362
She beams at three balls in a row.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS363
SOMEONE sits on the middle ball.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS367
SOMEONE faces a floor-to-ceiling window and gazes out at the city. With a dispirited look, he trudges out of the living room. Now.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS368
Door to SOMEONE's enclosure unlocks and the gorilla.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS369
Hopeful eyes. He watches as it slides open and.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS370
Nail tipped stick. SOMEONE turns his back to the goateed zookeeper.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS371
Stepping closer, Shane rests his stick on his shoulder.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS372
He reaches into a pants pocket and withdraws an apple.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS373
He takes a bite then hurls it against the far wall. Apple chunks explode over SOMEONE's head.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS374
Pepper spray. At the dealership, a salesman talks to his colleague.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS375
The salesman's head swivel toward the customer. SOMEONE and Nimer exchange a look then both.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS376
He heads to the door as Nimer greets the high roller.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS377
SOMEONE stands by the door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS379
She opens a velvet box.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS380
Dropping to one knee, SOMEONE falters then straightens.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS381
As SOMEONE stares, a mariachi band enters.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS382
As she leaves the dealership, the band follows. Now SOMEONE sits in his enclosure with his back to the door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS383
He sniffs the air, his nostrils twitching.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS384
Turning, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE back in a zookeeper’s uniform. He smiles and SOMEONE gives a nod.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS385
The crow lands on the pit wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS386
SOMEONE runs off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS387
SOMEONE takes flight.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS388
In a parking lot, SOMEONE the Gorilla crosses to a van and open.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS389
SOMEONE stands behind a fence.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS390
Runs around to the passenger side.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS391
Rolls out, heads into the road and drives straight into the side of a parked.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS392
The van doors open and SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out to switch places. Manny unlocks the.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS393
The gorilla pulls the.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS394
Later, it cruises down a residential street.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS395
The van stops short.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS396
Right past her, he heads upstairs and.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS397
Shane gets up from a computer in his underwear.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS398
Wall which crumbles around him. SOMEONE marches out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS400
Steering wheel turning sharply around a bend.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS401
The road at the scene of an accident.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS402
Apartment buildings. It dead ends in a 15 foot wall. The van.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS403
To a stop and SOMEONE clambers out on all fours. He follows SOMEONE over to the wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS404
The zookeeper and the gorilla swap a look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS405
Now, SOMEONE flies over the wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS406
Meanwhile, SOMEONE steps out of her apartment.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS408
It rounds a corner.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS409
As it drives away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS410
SOMEONE holds a kayak over his head. He toss.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS411
As the taxi drives alongside the river, SOMEONE and SOMEONE row after it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS413
Support beams to find the kayak arriving below.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS414
Lifts the portly zookeeper up with one arm.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS415
They move for the support beam.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS416
He clings to SOMEONE's back as the gorilla climbs the beam which angles nearly 45 degrees outward. SOMEONE glances around.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS418
SOMEONE reaches back and pulls.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS419
Of a spotlight and rises to his feet with the zoo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS420
SOMEONE keeps climbing. Our view retracts.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS421
Bridge as they continue up the beam which now slants.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS422
Taxi inches along.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS423
The gorilla dangles above it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS424
To the road. SOMEONE gasps as he pulls himself up on the hood of her cab. She gets out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS425
She kisses SOMEONE then wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him again. Our view circles the embracing couple.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS426
In their cars.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS427
Gorilla then glances upward.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS429
Words appear, Six months later.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS430
View of the entire zoo and the.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS431
SOMEONE steps up beside him. SOMEONE blinks emotionally then.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS432
Standing on a tall mound of boulders.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS433
Gentle waterfall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS434
Smile with SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS435
SOMEONE wraps his arm around him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS437
A small screen shows the animals singing along with the music.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS31
Moving to the door, she looks at the head coach and grins.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS32
She steps out to meet SOMEONE in the hall.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS33
The bitter assistant coach shares a warm hug with her player.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS34
Now as we rove over a river toward a city, words appear.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS35
Arlington, Virginia a few days later.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS36
At a softball practice.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS37
Teammates throw balls to SOMEONE who drops them in a bucket beside third base.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS38
A cellphone rings inside an open duffel bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS39
As SOMEONE looks over, a ball hits her in the face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS40
Her mouth bloodied, she answers the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS41
A woman in a skirt suit barges into SOMEONE's office with a letter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS42
He accepts the letter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS43
In the office, the boyish businessman opens his letter to find a subpoena for a wire fraud case which reads, United States of America v. SOMEONE Madison.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS44
Now SOMEONE eats with a friend.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS45
Now in a classroom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS46
The professor steps out to find the businessman texting in the hallway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS47
In her office.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS49
SOMEONE exits the club with a blond man who stops to sign autographs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS50
His date continues walking down the alley.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS51
She turns back.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS52
He points her around a corner, then runs after her grinning.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS53
SOMEONE rounds the corner, grabs Lisa, and lifts her off of her feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS54
He backs away from her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS55
She nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS56
The gray haired doorman glances at SOMEONE, then takes three steps back to patiently stand beside him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS57
SOMEONE glances at each of them, then throws up her arms and starts inside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS58
She punches his stomach.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS59
The next morning, in a well-furnished bedroom with an adjoining balcony, SOMEONE lies alone in bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS60
She sits up and peers across the room, then grabs her slip from a nightstand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS61
He sets two frothy, white blender drinks on a ledge, opens a window, and shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS62
He hops on the bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS63
He hands SOMEONE one of the drinks. She eyes its garnishment of fruit and a blue plastic star, then takes a sip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS64
She sets it down.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS65
She grabs her dress and steps out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS66
SOMEONE looks around the huge bathroom, which leads to a massive walk-in closet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS67
She opens the drawer and finds it filled with unopened toothbrushes of every color and pattern.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS68
SOMEONE enters.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS69
SOMEONE takes a brush, then puts her bright red dress on over her matching slip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS70
He opens a cabinet filled with women's pink sweat suits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS71
Size stickers SOMEONE a stack of sweatshirts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS72
She heads out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS73
He watches her head out the front door. She starts to pull it shut behind her, then stops and reenters the apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS74
She storms back down the hallway and returns to the bedroom where SOMEONE sits on his bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS75
He beams.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS76
With a smile, she leans in.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS77
Now SOMEONE strolls down a sidewalk in her rumpled red dress, passing another pedestrian.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS78
A breeze rustles the green leaves of a bush nearby.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS79
SOMEONE crosses a street, then reaches into her purse as she approaches the front door of a columned apartment building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS80
Later inside, she sits at a laptop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS81
A USA softball website reads, Announcement of 2011 Team USA.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS82
SOMEONE clicks on the link and a notice appears, Selection of next year's team delayed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS83
SOMEONE deflates, then leaves the laptop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS84
Now pedestrians walk past an office building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS85
Inside, SOMEONE finds a bespectacled man drying his hands in a men's room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS86
He hands him the subpoena.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS87
The bespectacled man finishes drying a hand, then reads.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS88
The man's eyes widen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS89
He braces himself and takes a breath.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS90
In SOMEONE's office.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS91
A bespectacled man with thinning gray hair kisses him on the cheek.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS92
SOMEONE hands him the subpoena.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS93
The lawyer peers closely over his shoulder to read along.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS94
SOMEONE picks up his phone receiver and dials.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS95
A pregnant, auburn haired woman enters.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS97
SOMEONE furiously leaps up to punch him from behind, but SOMEONE stops her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS98
Ron sits with SOMEONE and dictates to her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS99
As SOMEONE exits the office, SOMEONE notes his dejected expression. Outside, SOMEONE crosses the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS100
He stops and presses a hand to his forehead.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS102
Glancing out a window, Ron spots SOMEONE sulking across the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS103
Rising from the table, he faces the window and takes out his cell. He makes a call.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS104
Outside, SOMEONE fishes his phone from his pocket and answers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS105
SOMEONE stares up at the fourth floor office window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS106
Ron hangs up, leaving SOMEONE staring up at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS107
Later in an apartment, SOMEONE makes a call.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS108
His girlfriend eyes him from behind a desk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS109
He hangs up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS111
She rises. She moves to SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS112
She moves to SOMEONE and squats in front of him, resting her hands on his knees.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS113
She briefly rubs his legs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS114
Gaping, SOMEONE leaves.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS115
Later, he grills a steak on a patio balcony, his tie discarded and his shirt untucked.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS116
He sprinkles seasoning on the meat, his hand jerking the container more and more aggressively as he loses composure.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS117
Stabbing a fork into the steak, he flips it repeatedly, then suddenly hurls it off the balcony.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS118
Now inside, he pours vodka into a shot glass and eyeballs it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS119
He pours half of the glass back into the bottle, then empties the remainder into a cocktail shaker.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS120
He adds a spoonful of horseradish, some Worcestershire sauce and tomato juice, then shakes it all up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS121
With a celery stalk, he stirs his glass of Bloody Mary, then takes a sip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS122
Later, SOMEONE fills his empty glass with more Bloody SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS123
The image dissolves to him clumsily refilling the glass with straight vodka.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS124
Now he points a remote control.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS125
He sings into a lamp like a microphone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS126
He grabs another drink.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS127
Now in the bathroom, SOMEONE urinates. He grabs his phone with his free hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS128
SOMEONE muffles his phone inside a towel.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS129
Holding it away from the toilet, he flushes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS130
He rinses his hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS131
She lifts her shirt and pats her enormous belly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS132
Heading down a staircase, SOMEONE trips and slides to the bottom on his back.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS133
With a grin, he rises, unharmed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS134
Hanging her head, SOMEONE squeezes her eyes shut.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS135
They tear up as she opens them.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS136
With a furrowed brow, SOMEONE hangs up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS137
He briefly presses his fingers to his forehead, then leans back in his chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS138
Rising, he straightens his T-shirt as he trudges out of his living room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS139
He pauses, opens his phone, and makes a call.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS140
Meanwhile, SOMEONE rides on a bus.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS141
She pulls her phone from her bag and answers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS142
SOMEONE frowns uncertainly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS143
SOMEONE leans on a wall and slips.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS144
He lowers his phone and folds it shut.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS145
The next morning, two women stroll across the street in front of SOMEONE's apartment building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS146
Inside, she lies asleep in bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS147
She bolts awake and glances around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS148
As she throws back her covers, her legs get tangled in the sheets and she wrestles them off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS149
She strides to a table and grabs her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS150
Its display reads, Missed call Coach SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS151
Frowning, SOMEONE runs a hand through her mussed hair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS152
She turns to her computer, which displays the softball team website, and clicks on the link for the announcement of the 2011 team.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS153
A window appears.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS154
Click to see next year's lineup.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS155
SOMEONE shifts her gaze to her phone, then picks it up and reads a text message from Riva, I'm coming over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS156
Setting the phone back down, she sits at her laptop and types frantically.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS157
She scrolls through the team lineup, but doesn't find her name.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS158
A blue asterisk blinks on the roster, indicating a new player.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS159
The position reads, Cam Austin, second base.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS160
SOMEONE drops her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS161
Pressing her lips together, she closes her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS162
She lifts her gaze back to the laptop and stares at it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS163
Her chest heaving then closes her eyes again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS164
She reopens them and stares at the blue asterisk, blinking beside her replacement's name.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS167
Now in her bathroom. SOMEONE grabs her electric toothbrush. The mirror is covered in inspirational quotes written on sticky notes, including, Obstacles are what you see when you lose sight of your goal.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS168
Blinking rapidly, SOMEONE starts to brush her teeth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS169
As her gaze scans the brightly colored notes, she stops brushing and closes her lips around her toothbrush.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS170
With sad eyes, she resumes brushing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS171
She closes her eyes and tears slide down her cheeks.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS172
As her face crumples, she lowers her toothbrush from her mouth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS173
Her hand dropping heavily on the counter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS174
Her mouth trembles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS175
A froth of toothpaste clinging to her lower lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS176
She reads two quotes; Courage is mastery of fear, not absence of fear.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS177
Don't judge anybody before you check yourself out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS178
You're lucky when it's your fault, because you can correct the situation.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS180
Her expression hardens.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS181
She leans over the sink. Eyeing her reflection, she wipes her mouth, then heads off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS182
Now SOMEONE leaves his building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS183
SOMEONE sprints away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS184
In his suit and dress shoes. SOMEONE blinks and stares.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS185
Now SOMEONE dons a skirt as her teammates visit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS186
She heads for the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS187
Now SOMEONE marches down a city street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS188
Pausing at a corner, she wipes a tear, ruefully checks her fingers for runny makeup and rolls her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS189
Now at an elegant restaurant, she approaches a well-dressed Maître d'.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS190
The Maître d' leads her onto a balcony and gestures down toward a solitary figure at a table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS191
SOMEONE sits slumped, his head in his hands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS192
The grinning Maître d' leads on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS193
He obligingly excuses himself.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS194
Heading along the balcony, SOMEONE regards her date uncertainly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS195
Now she arrives at his table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS196
He looks up pitiably.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS197
He springs to his feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS198
SOMEONE slips into the high-backed booth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS199
SOMEONE shrugs her brow and frowns.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS200
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS201
SOMEONE picks up her menu and SOMEONE nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS202
SOMEONE rolls her eyes, then studies her menu.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS203
SOMEONE stares helplessly at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS204
Smiling, SOMEONE stares at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS205
His eyes twinkle and he gives a stunned shake of the head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS206
He amiably shuts his mouth and faces his menu.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS207
SOMEONE fidgets her fingers, allows a small half-smile, and nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS208
Later, they dine on spaghetti and meatballs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS209
SOMEONE cuts a chunk of tomato and eats it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS210
SOMEONE sneaks glances at her as he chews.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS211
His date shifts her worried gaze, occasionally eyeing him impassively.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS212
Her features contorting in a pensive frown.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS213
SOMEONE stops eating and leans back in her seat.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS214
Her lips part and her stubborn chin juts forward.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS215
SOMEONE studies her intently.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS216
His brow lifts and he stops chewing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS217
Catching him staring, SOMEONE gives a nervous half-smile and looks down.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS219
SOMEONE's lips curl into a dreamy-eyed smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS221
He opens the restaurant door for SOMEONE and follows her out with a goofy grin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS222
He shrugs and beams at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS223
SOMEONE creases her lips, sizing him up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS224
SOMEONE watches her go with his boyish grin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS225
Now SOMEONE uses his cellphone as he leaves his building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS226
In a bar, SOMEONE talks on the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS227
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, the doorman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS228
The doorman chuckles, points, and steps away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS229
Now SOMEONE plods up a flight of stairs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS230
Entering her apartment, she finds a bouquet of flowers with an attached construction paper card, reading, We love you, Smalls. Dozens of other notes surround the gift, and SOMEONE sits behind the display.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS231
Now in SOMEONE's apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS232
He crosses to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS233
SOMEONE sulks into the living room. She halts abruptly and looks around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS234
He leads her to a couch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS235
As she sits, he lies down and puts his head in her lap.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS236
SOMEONE squirms an arm out from under his shoulder and sets her bag on the floor.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS237
Daytime. SOMEONE ushers SOMEONE through a dignified office building's thriving lobby.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS238
Reaching a reception desk, they peer at a vast wall mounted directory.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS239
SOMEONE brushes off his son's suit jacket as he guides him along.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS240
Now they sit side-by-side on a waiting room couch, both resting their hands on their parted knees and drumming their fingers. Later, SOMEONE faces a bearded man.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS241
SOMEONE's head droops forward and he bites his upper lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS242
Now SOMEONE arrives in a tasteful office where a man with a closely trimmed beard waits at a desk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS243
He gestures to a SOMEONE to sit on chair or ottoman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS245
SOMEONE perches on the ottoman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS246
As he takes a seat facing her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS247
The kind-faced man crosses his legs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS248
The psychiatrist patiently lifts his chin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS249
Narrowing her eyes, SOMEONE gives an appreciative nod and starts to leave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS250
She halts in the doorway and turns around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS251
SOMEONE leaves then reappears in his doorway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS253
As rain pours, party guests in summery clothes crowd a home.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS254
SOMEONE gets food at a buffet while SOMEONE waits on a covered terrace.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS255
Seeing her through a window he notices her watching the man beside him fondling a woman's breast.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS256
SOMEONE pulls the man's hand down and directs their attention to SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS257
The woman scowls and puts her date's hand back on her breast.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS258
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE food.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS259
SOMEONE glances toward the partiers inside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS260
SOMEONE shifts in his seat and gives a sheepishly obliging shrug.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS261
SOMEONE gives a meek, pleased smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS262
Now a bird's eye view shows an umbrella only half sheltering SOMEONE's plate of BBQ.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS263
He and SOMEONE share the umbrella.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS264
SOMEONE sadly throws the plate in a trash bin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS265
Later at his place.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS266
He grins and SOMEONE gives him an irritated look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS267
Standing behind her he wraps his arms around her waist.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS268
SOMEONE nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS269
He pours Cheerios.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS270
He adds Life cereal to their bowls
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS271
SOMEONE gives him a nod. SOMEONE pours blueberries over their cereal.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS272
SOMEONE gives her a bowl.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS273
With a mouthful of cereal, SOMEONE shifts her thoughtful eyes. She gives SOMEONE an expectant look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS274
SOMEONE shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS275
He slaps her shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS276
As he starts to eat his cereal, SOMEONE gives him an appreciative look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS277
SOMEONE stops eating and looks over with wide eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS278
He gives a disturbed look and she playfully punches his arm.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS279
Now our view tilts up from the lobby doors past the engraved entablature just below the second story.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS280
Bowlen building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS281
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie with their heads at the foot of his bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS282
SOMEONE claps and the lights turn on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS283
She points at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS284
As he leans over her, she punches his shoulder twice. The lights turn off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS285
On another day, SOMEONE sits on the bench in the National's bullpen smiling to himself.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS286
He stares off dreamily.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS287
He blinks himself out of his reverie.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS288
An opposing player rounds third toward home plate.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS289
A National's outfielder makes an amazing catch, right over the wall of the bullpen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS290
His teammates swivel their heads toward him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS291
Shrugging his hands a ball player rises.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS292
Starting his warm-up he catches a ball.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS293
SOMEONE catches the ball again, then leans toward him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS294
SOMEONE's shoulders heave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS295
Later in the National's training room, SOMEONE holds his phone to his ear as he runs in a pool treadmill.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS296
In her apartment, SOMEONE removes the bag from the trashcan.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS297
She lets the can fall as she goes to the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS298
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS299
Hanging up, SOMEONE glances around, then returns her attention to the trash bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS300
Grinning she flips open her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS301
A trainer brings him ice.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS302
SOMEONE's mouth lifts into a crooked SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS303
SOMEONE shifts her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS304
With a thoughtful look, SOMEONE hangs up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS305
Now she packs a duffel bag in her room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS306
SOMEONE shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS307
The assistant coach rises from the arm of a sofa and hugs her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS308
SOMEONE answers his front door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS309
She indicates a large stack of bags and suitcases.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS310
In his closet, SOMEONE opens a drawer that's only one third empty.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS311
She nods and they share a smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS312
Glancing back at the drawer she shrugs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS313
Now at an apartment above a bakery.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS314
SOMEONE rises from a desk at a bay window. Boxes and other packed items line his small living room and hallway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS315
He opens the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS316
SOMEONE carries in a grocery bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS317
SOMEONE loads the fridge.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS318
SOMEONE waddles to an armchair and sinks down in it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS319
She stands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS320
Standing in front of him, SOMEONE bites her lip and eyes him skeptically.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS321
She takes a few steps away and gives him a sidelong look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS322
With her thoughtful gaze still locked on his face
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS323
she cocks her heads and studies him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS324
She sets her hands on her hips.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS325
She juts out her jaw, then curls her lips together.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS326
SOMEONE stands ready to exit his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS327
She heads to the kitchen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS329
SOMEONE approaches the Bowlen Building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS330
Meanwhile, SOMEONE makes a call from the desk in his study.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS331
SOMEONE stops in the lobby.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS332
SOMEONE closes his eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS333
He shuts his phone then letting his upper body go limp, slams his head onto a decorative table and holds it there.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS334
The doorman and a concierge stare at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS335
Now SOMEONE trudges into an elevator.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS336
As he rubs his forehead SOMEONE rushes through the open doors.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS337
With a bag of groceries slung over her shoulder, she stands beside him as he rubs his face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS338
His hand descends to his mouth, pulling down his lower lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS339
SOMEONE glances over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS340
He looks at her, then quickly releases his lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS341
Later, SOMEONE follows SOMEONE into SOMEONE's apartment, carrying the bag of groceries.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS342
She takes it into the kitchen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS343
SOMEONE looks around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS344
He hurries over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS345
Entering, SOMEONE frowns at seeing SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS346
SOMEONE gives a comprehending nod, then smiles at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS347
SOMEONE wears a disgruntled look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS348
Smiling tightly, she jerks her to the side, then moves off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS349
SOMEONE follows with a long sigh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS350
SOMEONE peers after them as they enter another room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS351
SOMEONE stares with disbelieving eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS352
She blinks up at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS353
Following her into the hall, he glances at George, who looks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS354
Now SOMEONE packs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS355
SOMEONE opens the front door and SOMEONE stalks to the elevator with her bags and suitcases in tow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS356
She steps inside and hits a button. As the doors slide shut, SOMEONE shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS357
He pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS358
Now SOMEONE races down the stairwell, jumping onto each landing as he rounds the next flight.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS359
In the lobby, the doorman rushes to keep ahead of SOMEONE and opens the door for her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS360
She marches outside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS361
SOMEONE dashes out the main door. Spotting SOMEONE he skids to a stop and puts on a casual expression. He pretends to gaze down the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS362
He grins.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS363
He takes a bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS364
He tips the doorman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS365
He and SOMEONE start off down the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS367
As they head to a bus stop, the doorman answers an intercom phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS368
He sets down the phone receiver and jogs toward George, who waits behind SOMEONE a short distance away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS369
As the doorman opens his mouth to call him
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS370
he notices SOMEONE shaking his head giddily then looking skyward with a grateful smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS371
Grinning sympathetically, SOMEONE returns to the intercom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS372
He watches as SOMEONE follows SOMEONE on to a bus, hauling up her roller bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS373
Later at his downsized apartment, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE carry in her luggage. She sets down her bags, then takes out her cellphone and charger.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS374
She notes SOMEONE's boxes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS375
His fridge is packed with food from SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS376
He checks his cell and ignores a call from dad.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS377
He enters the kitchen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS378
She opens his fridge, finding the vast array of neatly labeled homemade items.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS379
As SOMEONE sets his jacket down she joins him at the counter and grabs a fork.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS380
SOMEONE leaves the galley kitchen and unplugs her cellphone from its charger. She steps aside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS381
He peeks at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS382
Rolling up his sleeves, he smirks. She faces him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS383
She tosses down her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS384
SOMEONE considers the idea.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS385
She frowns.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS386
He crosses to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS387
SOMEONE deflates.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS388
Left alone in the cluttered second floor apartment she glances around and wanders over to a bay window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS389
Peering outside she spots SOMEONE who holds up a six-pack of Guinness on his way back across the
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS390
He runs in front of an oncoming car.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS391
He barely avoids getting hit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS392
SOMEONE shakes her head and leaves the window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS393
Now on the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS394
SOMEONE slides open his cellphone and aims it at his sad face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS395
He checks the pic, then sets up a second shot.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS396
He tilts his head and milks the pout a little more.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS397
Now SOMEONE adds three dashes of bitters to highball glass, drops in a single sugar cube and measures some Maker's SOMEONE in a metal shot cup.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS398
In the living room, SOMEONE grabs her near-empty glass of Guinness and takes a sip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS399
SOMEONE squints as he stirs his creation, then smiles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS400
He shakes the drink.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS401
SOMEONE hears him singing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS402
She turns to eye him and he stares back, then enters the living room with two cocktails.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS403
SOMEONE downs the last of her Guinness.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS404
She accepts the cloudy, peach tinted beverage.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS405
SOMEONE sits across from her on the floor.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS406
He raises his glass.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS407
He taps her, then taps her again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS408
She sets her drink aside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS409
He stands. SOMEONE straightens her posture.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS411
She sits up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS412
SOMEONE sits beside her on the couch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS413
She squints distantly then gestures with her sleeve-covered hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS414
SOMEONE lowers her tearful gaze, then notes SOMEONE beside her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS415
She self-consciously stands up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS416
She tugs the hem of her shirt and rubs her nose.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS417
SOMEONE watches her pace across the room and take a seat on a cushioned chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS418
SOMEONE glances at her host.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS419
SOMEONE brightens.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS420
Laughing uncontrollably, SOMEONE hunches forward.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS421
She leaves her seat and crosses to her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS422
SOMEONE nods softly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS423
She unplugs her cellphone and
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS424
flips it open to check the caller ID.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS425
He finds a scrap of paper.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS426
His note reads, I went nuts when you left, I broke a lamp.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS427
A shade and exposed light bulb dangle crookedly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS428
With his back to her, SOMEONE purses his lips and sighs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS429
He regards her affably.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS430
She eyes him awkwardly as he stands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS431
Later on the street. SOMEONE raises his arm for a taxi.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS432
He smiles warmly, then resumes trying for a cab.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS433
Unseen by her, SOMEONE makes a fist and grimaces.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS434
He lowers his arm, then turns and faces SOMEONE squarely.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS435
A taxi stops.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS436
SOMEONE smiles, meeting his eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS437
They share a pleasant nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS438
SOMEONE taps on the rear of the parked taxi.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS439
He opens the trunk, then helps SOMEONE load in her luggage.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS440
He stows the largest first, then she helps with the two smaller bags.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS441
He smiles and shuts the trunk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS442
He nods and follows her to the passenger door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS443
SOMEONE smiles softly, with a touch of sadness, then gets in the cab.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS444
SOMEONE shuts the door, then impulsively leans close to her open window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS445
They share a warm smile, then he leaves the window and the cab drives away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS446
SOMEONE watches her go, tightens his lips, then plods back toward his apartment across the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS448
Pedestrians enjoy a sunny day by a lofty stone fountain.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS449
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a bench.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS450
SOMEONE glances at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS451
He buries his face in his hand and she wraps her arm around him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS452
Nighttime at the Bowlen Building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS453
Now SOMEONE stands tensely in an elevator.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS454
Now with his father.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS455
SOMEONE sits on a velvet couch facing his father.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS456
It's SOMEONE plainly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS457
SOMEONE paces.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS458
Arms akimbo the bespectacled older man glances at his son and nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS459
He shuffles back to his chair and retakes his seat.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS460
SOMEONE gesticulates.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS461
A devastated SOMEONE covers his moth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS462
SOMEONE gawks at his dad.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS463
Stands over SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS464
In SOMEONE's apartment
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS465
sitting alone he text messages.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS466
She enters the room to find him texting.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS467
He sheepishly pockets his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS468
He kisses her cheek.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS469
He picks up his bags.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS470
Leads SOMEONE to the couch and sits on the coffee table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS471
SOMEONE gets up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS472
Barefoot she marches to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS473
She crosses the outer hall.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS474
She presses the elevator button.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS475
She grabs his bags.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS476
She puts them on the elevator.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS477
SOMEONE notes her flushed complexion.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS478
He kisses her cheek.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS479
She walks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS480
The elevator door shut.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS481
SOMEONE shuts the apartment doors, then turns and rubs her face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS482
Back with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS483
SOMEONE sits on the couch between SOMEONE and a pillow decorated with a sand crab.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS484
SOMEONE gives a sympathetic pout then screws up his mouth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS485
He rubs his father’s shoulder,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS486
startling him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS487
He eyes SOMEONE's hand on his shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS488
SOMEONE looks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS489
His lips press tightly together, SOMEONE looks up sheepishly at his glaring son.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS490
Taking a breath he draws himself up and rubs his legs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS491
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS492
His gaze hardening, he purses his lips.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS493
SOMEONE gives a small, remorseful shrug.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS494
His son shifts on his feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS495
He rubs his face with both hands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS496
SOMEONE hurries out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS497
Now at a softball game.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS498
SOMEONE applauds from the sidelines.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS499
Fans behind her hold homemade signs and wear American flag patterned clothing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS500
On the field, her former coaches and teammates congratulate each other.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS501
SOMEONE's smile fades.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS502
The American players line up facing their opponents from Australia and they exchange sporting high fives.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS503
SOMEONE's brow knits and her chest heaves.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS504
She walks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS505
Later, she rides a commuter train, woefully biting her thumbnail and fidgeting her fingers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS506
Now words type out on a computer screen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS511
Facing his laptop SOMEONE pauses and reads his letter over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS512
He picks up his cell phone from a stack of papers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS513
He eyes his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS514
It's Lisa, down on the sidewalk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS515
She faces away from him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS516
He stares down at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS517
She turns, he ducks.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS518
Facing the street, SOMEONE pouts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS519
SOMEONE yields a comforted nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS520
SOMEONE grins down at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS521
Unnoticing, SOMEONE shifts on her feet nervously.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS522
Ending the call, SOMEONE smiles down at her again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS523
He springs from his seat.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS524
Rushing around his living room, he gathers up laundry and stacks books on a coffee table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS525
Downstairs SOMEONE paces before the Cafe/Bakery under his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS526
Later she leans against a display window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS527
Stepping forward
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS528
she cranes her neck to look up at SOMEONE's window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS529
Now in his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS530
The door opens to reveal a smiling SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS531
She turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS532
She pauses on the landing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS533
SOMEONE stares off with an embarrassed frown.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS534
She marches up, enters the apartment, and pauses to face SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS535
As he covers her mouse she cocks a fist.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS536
Releasing her he backs off, open hands raised.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS537
SOMEONE frowns, gives a small nod and turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS538
SOMEONE looks back and forth between her and his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS539
As she sits he answers the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS540
He glances at SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS541
SOMEONE faces Lisa, his green eyes sparkling.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS542
SOMEONE gets to her feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS543
Heading out she halts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS544
Now an older couple coos over SOMEONE and a newborn in a blue cap and blanket.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS545
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive in the doorway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS546
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE questioningly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS547
He kisses her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS548
His parents leave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS549
As SOMEONE to SOMEONE's side, the new mom regards SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS550
SOMEONE ventures to the bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS551
SOMEONE points at the newborn.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS552
SOMEONE gawks enchanted.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS553
She answers a phone by her bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS554
The baby's cap slides off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS555
SOMEONE gently slips it back on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS556
SOMEONE cues SOMEONE for a discreet exit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS557
SOMEONE's gaze darkens as SOMEONE walks in with two presents.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS558
Behind him, a tall burly man walks in with flowers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS559
The newcomer hands the flowers to SOMEONE. SOMEONE gives a relieved smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS560
He shakes SOMEONE's hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS561
SOMEONE shows the gifts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS562
He offers a blue present, then sets the pink one down too.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS563
SOMEONE faces his son cautiously.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS564
He turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS565
Eating ice chips with a spoon, SOMEONE looks back and forth between the father and son.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS566
SOMEONE strolls over to SOMEONE and greets her with a smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS567
looks to SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS568
He faces George, who gives a smirk and broad shrug.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS569
He faces SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS570
He leaves with a tense smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS571
SOMEONE leans on her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS572
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a camcorder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS573
He pulls the chair up to SOMEONE and his brand new son.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS574
They share a tearful loving embrace, their newborn between them.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS575
SOMEONE smiles wistfully. SOMEONE beams holding the aimed camera.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS576
SOMEONE's smile vanishes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS577
SOMEONE sits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS578
SOMEONE giddily bites her lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS579
Smiling SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE and finds him beaming tenderly at her, camcorder in hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS580
SOMEONE gives her fiancée an affectionate slug on the shoulder and they share a laugh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS581
SOMEONE flashes a bashful smile, and shuts the camcorder's display window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS583
He and SOMEONE stroll outside through the hospital's revolving door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS584
They walk close together, their hands swinging gently at their sides.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS586
The twosome approaches a bus stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS587
SOMEONE stands before SOMEONE as she sits on a bench.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS588
A wistful smile plays on her pixie-like features.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS589
He beams fondly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS590
A city bus turns into view and nears the stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS591
SOMEONE gets to her feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS592
Shifts his desperate gaze as the bus doors open.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS593
SOMEONE steps on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS594
SOMEONE storms off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS595
As he marches alongside the bus
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS596
SOMEONE watches him through a window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS597
His arms give an angry flail.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS598
Wearing a confused frown SOMEONE blinks at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS599
As the bus pulls away she averts her thoughtful gaze.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS600
Her eyes widen and she pulls the stop cord.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS601
The bus lurches to a halt at the curb.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS602
SOMEONE hurries off and moves around the front of the bus.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS603
Spreading her arms in a bewildered shrug, she strides briskly toward her friend.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS604
Step face to face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS605
Another bus arrives.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS606
SOMEONE's mirthful grin fades.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS607
SOMEONE faces the bus, and her wistful smile returns.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS608
She jerks her thumb at the hospital and shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS609
SOMEONE watches her climb aboard the bus.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS610
SOMEONE gives a small hopeful smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS611
Beaming tenderly, SOMEONE shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS612
SOMEONE faces the stout driver and sweeps her bus pass over a scanner.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS613
Now at home.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS614
SOMEONE eyes a list in two columns. The first headed, reasons against reads, I don't want to go to jail, I'm scared.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS615
The reason for column lists I don't want my father to spend the rest of his life in jail. He's scared.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS616
SOMEONE crumples the page and takes out his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS617
He puts the phone to his ear and sits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS618
In his study, SOMEONE pauses at some paperwork and answers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS619
He ends the call excitedly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS620
Back in her own apartment, SOMEONE munches a cracker as she lounges, facing her TV.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS626
In a well-tailored dark gray suit, SOMEONE arrives at his father's building. At the entrance, sexy model types in slinky clothes line up at a table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS627
Later he arrives at a door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS628
A legal team files out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS629
SOMEONE leads his son into his study and sits behind his cluttered desk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS630
He gestures to a chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS631
SOMEONE totes a brown paper bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS632
SOMEONE averts his gaze, his lips creasing emotionally.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS633
SOMEONE stifles his jaw from dropping.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS634
Grinning SOMEONE hurries out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS635
SOMEONE gives a half-hearted wave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS636
On SOMEONE's vast penthouse patio, elegant place settings line tables.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS637
Two vendors wheeling bushels of live lobsters.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS638
SOMEONE and SOMEONE chat in the walk-in closet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS639
He pulls out a chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS640
He hands her a box.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS641
He bends slightly and bobs his shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS642
He sits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS643
He unwraps it for her and hands it back.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS645
Inside, SOMEONE finds a diamond encrusted wristwatch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS646
As SOMEONE beams, SOMEONE's lips stutter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS647
She puts it on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS648
SOMEONE's shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS649
He leaves the adjoining bathroom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS650
In the hall they pass some guests.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS651
As a teammate leads SOMEONE away, SOMEONE snags SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS652
They walk out onto the vacant patio, and SOMEONE pulls out a chair for her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS653
He sits kitty corner from her and sets down the small paper bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS654
She uncurls the bag's crumpled top and reaches inside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS655
SOMEONE watches as she fishes out a present.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS656
Wrapped in polka dot paper, like a hard candy,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS657
it bears a cheerful red ribbon tied on each end.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS658
SOMEONE gives him a smile, then carefully unties one of the bows.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS659
SOMEONE shifts his anxious eyes between her and the present.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS660
SOMEONE very patiently slides the ribbon off the end of the tube shaped gift.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS661
As she moves on to the other bow, she pauses.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS662
Her eyes flicker over SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS663
He lifts his brow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS665
With a smile, he watches SOMEONE slide off the second bow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS667
Unwrapping the gift, she finds a child's tub of Play-Doh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS669
As she examines it, her diamond watch glitters on her wrist.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS670
He gives her a nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS671
He takes the Play-Doh from her and eyes it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS672
He stares into her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS673
She holds his gaze for a moment, then looks down with a touched expression.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS675
A hint of tears glistens in her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS676
She returns her gaze to him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS677
SOMEONE nods, her eyes glistening.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS678
Her gaze remains locked on him
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS679
and he gives her a tender smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS680
She glances at the Play-Doh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS681
SOMEONE nods, his eyes misty as well.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS682
She shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS683
She sets the Play-Doh back inside the paper bag and crumples down the top.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS684
Avoiding SOMEONE's gaze, she stands and he follows suit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS685
She walks back into the apartment, leaving him staring after her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS686
Inside, SOMEONE strolls past three chatting women.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS687
She shows them.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS688
As the three women chat, SOMEONE lifts her gaze from the watch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS689
On the patio, SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand, then hurries along.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS691
He pulls SOMEONE aside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS692
He winces. SOMEONE waves at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS693
He heads off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS694
SOMEONE watches with a curious look as SOMEONE opens the door and turns to her again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS695
He opens his mouth to speak.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS696
Brightly shrugs an arm and lets his fist open up in a self-deprecating flourish.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS697
He leaves.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS698
And SOMEONE's amused
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS699
smile fades.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS700
SOMEONE joins her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS701
They head away from their party guests.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS702
Outside by the bus stop a couple strolls by SOMEONE as he paces, his shoulders sagging.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS703
The headlights of passing cars cast their warm glow on the wet pavement.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS704
Inside the apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS705
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the vacant bedroom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS706
SOMEONE closes the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS707
He watches as she removes the diamond watch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS708
SOMEONE shifts her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS709
She turns to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS710
He nods, his eyes saddened.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS711
His lips fumble.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS712
SOMEONE rushes over and hugs him. He holds her tightly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS713
His shoulders heave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS715
SOMEONE touches her lips to his neck.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS717
SOMEONE continues to trudge back and forth by the bus stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS719
On a balcony above, SOMEONE talks on a phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS720
He hangs up then pockets his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS721
Looking down he sees his son on the sidewalk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS722
The lofty view shows SOMEONE fold his arms, bow his head, and stamp his feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS723
With a concerned look, he thrusts his hand on the balcony railing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS724
A lawyer behind him checks his watch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS725
Down below, SOMEONE exits the building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS727
She stops just outside the door as she sees SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS728
He gives her a relieved grin. SOMEONE takes a few steps toward him then pauses.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS731
Shaking his head, SOMEONE shrugs his hands and smiles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS733
SOMEONE quirks a smile and replies in kind.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS734
SOMEONE beams.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS735
As SOMEONE walks over
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS736
SOMEONE watches from the balcony.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS737
His lips spreading into a grin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS739
His mouth suddenly drops into a knowing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS740
He heads back into his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS741
By the bus stop SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS742
As she starts for the bus stop, SOMEONE grabs her by the shoulders and presses his lips to hers. Her brow lifts as he kisses her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS743
Then her shoulders relax and she wraps her arms around him, pulling him close.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS748
With her eyes closed, SOMEONE rests her face against his shoulder. SOMEONE leans his head against hers. His eyes close too.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS750
His smile fades and his eyes pop open.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS752
SOMEONE opens her eyes. She rolls them, then slides out of SOMEONE's embrace.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS753
She gives him an amused look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS755
She holds his gaze for a moment, Then walks to the bus stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS756
SOMEONE smiles, then follows.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS757
He sits beside her on the bench inside the glass shelter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS758
Facing her he squares his shoulders.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS759
He smiles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS760
SOMEONE blinks, then looks away, her brow furrowing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS761
As she returns her gaze to his,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS762
the corner of her mouth lifts into an
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS763
astonished smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS764
She eyes him for a moment, then turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS767
Reaching over, she places her hand on top of his hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS768
SOMEONE closes his fingers around hers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS769
With a tender expression, SOMEONE watches as she shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS772
She meets his gaze with a smile. SOMEONE grins.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS774
As they sit side by side holding hands,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS775
he leans forward and looks up the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS776
He turns to SOMEONE and gives her a nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS777
Still holding her hand, he rises.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS778
The bus arrives, eclipsing them from view.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS779
The bus pulls away, leaving the bench inside the quaint shelter empty.